Hi
Hi. Hi, hi. Hi. What is it? It's me. Hi, hi.
If you have any questions for me, please ask. I'll answer them all.
I'm nervous, too.
I was just wondering if you had any questions for me.
It's me. What are you doing now? I washed up and finished everything.
Fireworks? I didn't see it.
I feel good because I scrubbed my body today.
What are you guys doing?
I don't think there's anything.
Not everyone can see the tell-ing.
I think you can see it all.
Sing a song something crazy.
the alternative make me super crazy
It's home.
How was Daegu?
It was really good.
It's been a long time since I've done a voice live, so it's not like that, is it?
Do you want me to give you a spoiler? What do you want me to give you a spoiler?
What?
It was so much fun at the college festival.
We were promoting ON4.
I did it then.
It's been a long time since I've done a college festival.
It was so much fun.
Next song?
It's been a long time since I've done a college festival.
dialect?
It's really good.
Japanese?
Today, too...
Piana...
Today, too, fan signing...
Thank you so much for coming to the fan signing event.
Piana.
Am I right?
I don't know.
Isn't it Eun Chae?
Eun Chae.
I'm the first.
I did it first.
Eun Chae.
Crazy Red?
Back in the days.
Don't be crazy.
You couldn't be crazy.
I can't do it anymore.
Don't lie.
A word in Japanese for Kura.
Good morning.
Is it your birthday?
Who's birthday is it today?
Happy Birthday
You're here on the Krayz on the year-end Saturday.
You're here on the year-end Saturday.
Why?
Did you come out as a sea lion?
No way?
It's hard.
Oh, really?
Yoon Jin Ah's part?
Where is it?
Where did it come out?
I wrote a book on the neuron in my head.
Oh, wait a minute. But I suddenly
wanted to eat cherries so much.
I ate meat today.
n th
Is this a secret live broadcast?
No, I'm not doing it in secret.
Be proud!
You said you were going to sleep.
I want you to order cherries.
He he.
No.
I'm going to play with the piano, eat a little cherries, and go to bed.
Ferrari girl, what's wrong with you?
Kowakawa doesn't cry and speaks well.
Cafe
Ferrari girl
I
I can't buy a Ferrari, everyone.
I'm watching the drama that I recently watched now.
I'm watching it now.
I got it.
I didn't see the black and white cook.
Black and white cook.
I don't know.
It's so much fun.
Everyone around me, including the members,
They say it's so much fun.
They're all talking about it.
Just copy it.
And if I say I haven't seen it yet,
You're still happy.
That's what I'm saying.
So I thought it was a cooking and judging program.
I haven't seen it yet.
I'm not interested in it yet.
My name is...
I want to cry.
Eun Chae is singing.
It's so cute.
The comments are so cute.
Eun Chae is singing.
Touch, touch, touch.
I've tried my best to understand.
Please me too.
I don't know how to speak English well.
I can't just Estados.
Please me too.
Please sing a celebrity song for me.
When I sang a celebrity song, I sang the lyrics of the song.
But I didn't know the lyrics of the song, so I can't remember the lyrics.
That's it.
Do you like General Hong Yi?
Now I've called everything that starts with the name of the castle.
I borrowed it.
General Hong Yi.
Hongsam.
Hong Gildong.
You know, right?
Is that right?
China!
Jinmemba.
Speak Chinese, please.
Thank you.
Uh.
I love you.
See you in China.
Please sing.
You made me kiss me.
Uh?
You may kiss me, na na na kiss me
I don't know the lyrics
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Please kiss me
You may kiss me
Happy birthday
Oh, nemo nemo nemo nemo sign
Bunce munce
It's not a content if I sing
I'm not in the mood to sleep soon?
I'm still turning on all the lights in the room.
What's your favorite nickname these days?
I'm Hoonchae.
Who made that?
I don't know.
Did you like it?
Hoon High School?
Dae-al?
It's not Dae-al.
I'm sorry.
Eun-chae like Hoon?
No.
It's Hoon Hoon-han Eun-chae.
Isn't it?
It's Hoon Hoon-han Eun-chae, so it's called Hoonchae.
Hoon-hee Eun-chae?
Are you making fun of me now?
Eun-chae going to the training center?
What are you talking about?
Is it Hoon Hoon-han?
I miss you, Eun-chae.
I miss you, too.
Eun-chae, you're so cute.
Why do you remember the three name clubs in the nickname?
Why are you so cute?
I like cartoons.
Do you like cartoons?
I don't watch cartoons much.
Yes.
Wait.
Eun-chae.
Say something to the older sisters in a white hoodie.
What is this?
Ah, what is this? For real.
What is this? What is it?
What? What should I do?
That white hoodie was really amazing.
I could only see that one.
It's really funny.
You bought it? Really? A white hoodie.
Ah, really.
It's not a plotting.
It's crazy, right? It's red, right?
Why?
Why? What?
To be exact, it's not white.
You know that bright gray?
It's not gray, but it's really bright gray.
It was a hoodie.
That's why it's called a hoodie.
Really funny.
I saw it in detail.
I didn't see it in detail, but she was sitting in the first row.
I'm not plotting,
I'm really going
to explain what it is, everyone.
Don't say anything and listen. I'll explain.
You want me to speak like Hachu Pink? I'll explain.
It's been a long time since we had a university event, and there were schools that went far away.
We're on stage, but we're getting a lot of good energy and a lot of good things.
We prepared our signed album for each school.
I wanted to pick someone who enjoyed it so much and give them a gift, so I prepared a signed album.
Uh...
Now...
It's time to pick someone to give the signed album, right?
But...
I...
To start the anti...
But there are so many people now.
It was really hard to pick two or three people for this signed album.
So, it's really hard to choose.
Ah, I actually...
From the moment I came up on stage, I saw her.
There's a sister.
I said, and that's how it happened.
Everyone...
You talked too long.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
No, I'm not.
What's the next stage name?
And since it's a college festival,
If you're a college student, you're older than me.
And the fact that you're in the first row means that you're a college student in that school.
And I have a lot of affection for you.
Everyone, let's talk about something else.
What is your favorite member?
It's not that I have affection for you,
I just wanted to treat you like a family.
And we're all the same age.
I wanted to treat you like a family.
I'm sorry.
WILM SHI
Oh,
I don't cry.
Q.!
Do you have friends with 06?
96?
I think it's the last one.
It's October's birthday.
It's October 27th.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Miri.
Are you listening?
It's still October 5th.
It's October's birthday.
Congratulations, everyone.
Do you have anything you want to do?
Do you have a challenge you want to do?
A challenge you want to do?
I want to do a touch challenge.
What's the new challenge?
What is the new gender dance challenge to komen?
What is the new girl's challenge?
Hi.
Nemo Nemo Nemo Nemo
What are you doing?
Umbrini?
Maru? Maru Kung Kung
I did Maru Kung Kung Challenge
What is Umbrini?
Pick in a day challenge
There are a lot of people doing that
Im Ho Jung-ssi
I know I know
I'm glad.
It's going to be cut off?
I wasn't talking yet.
The weather is really nice.
The weather is nice.
What movie do you recommend?
For me,
It's a movie that's not serious at all.
It's a cute and fun movie.
There's a movie called Yes Day.
Was I really in elementary school?
I think it's a movie that my teacher showed me in class.
My family
once a year?
It's called Yes Day.
So that day,
No matter what,
I can only say yes.
So once a year
On that day,
I really wanted to do it.
There's something I can't even imagine.
Buy ice cream and eat it.
It's a day to try something like this.
Because I can only say yes, I have to follow everything.
Well, anyway, there's a lot of movies like that.
So it's just cute and not really serious.
Just when you're bored.
Yes, I like it.
It's so...
That's...
I was surprised.
But just like...
Just like others.
I'm just going to get the ticket myself.
I can't get a witness.
I didn't think I could get a ticket.
But I didn't know there would be so many articles.
Really.
I was so embarrassed.
I'm so...
I'm really bad at self-makeup.
I'm really good at self-makeup.
It was fun.
But I won.
The weather was really nice.
It was so much fun.
Really.
The父 et
And just for fun.
Just for fun.
My brother and I.
It's kind of a cliff.
So I won all of them, and I filmed it in time-lapse mode.
It's so funny.
And what else?
And I just met a lot of family members.
Not just my mom and dad, but also my relatives. I met a lot of relatives this time.
There are families that
I see often, but there
are also people that I
haven't seen in years.
I think I've met a lot of family members.
The picture of the moon...
It was near the sea near Sokcho.
I took a picture of the moon when I was on my way home from Sokcho.
I started bowling, too.
My bowling family...
Me, Eun-chae, In-cheol, Seok-oun, In- demonstrations took whole day.
Screen cap!
There is an importantOverodge.
I think I might be able to match it in a few years.
A baseball cheering song?
I sang the cheering song really hard that day.
I sang along to all of them.
But I forgot because I didn't go.
Doosan.
Together with Seungri.
How do I know all of them?
That's Crazy.
It's been a while since I worked out.
First diagnostics.
First.
I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything at all, so I worked out.
Yes, I did a lot when I did it, but it's been a while since I did it again.
It's so hard to start over.
I want to go again.
But I really want to go to the baseball field again.
I want to go to the baseball field again.
It's a shame, but I really have to go next year.
I really have to go next year.
It was really amazing. It was a fun game.
I posted it on Instagram.
Wow, it's been 30 minutes.
It's been 30 minutes.
It's so cool.
I...
I can't help it, but I feel sad.
Even if it was raining, I think it would have been like that.
I just came to play today.
It was fun, right?
What are you doing?
I always forget and always ask this.
The fans asked me so much about the Japanese I learned recently.
Now, how can I talk to my sisters?
If there's a new Japanese I'm listening to, I'm trying to memorize it.
If I memorize it and ask you
later, I'll answer
you like this.
That's what I do.
Oh, but I really forgot again.
There was something.
Do you know what a seal is in Japanese?
It was a seal.
What's a seal?
What was it?
I always remember this because it's so dark.
After I came, I was a cotton candy.
It's a seal.
What was the name of the seal you noticed in Jini?
I removed it because I said it after going to school.
But you were very serious.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, hello!
i know.
Oh, it was about dance.
That's it. I think it was Azarath.
What's your favorite snack these days?
I really like fried rice cakes and nurungji these days.
Nurungji. I like nurungji and fried rice cakes.
My manager bought me a really good fried rice cake yesterday.
It was really good.
Me and my manager and two other people ate it together.
You know, the long bag of fried rice cakes is usually sold in long bags.
I ate it all.
I ate it all on the spot.
It wasn't a human fried rice cake.
It's really good to put in your mouth.
It's really thin and sweet and savory.
It was really good.
How are you doing?
Isn't it almost 12 o'clock?
You should go to bed.
Eunchi, I'm going to bed.
All right.
I'm going to sleep.
Of course, I'm going to eat cherries and sleep.
I'm going to eat cherries and sleep, but you guys should go to bed early.
All right?
Did you have fun today?
I guess the cherries are all here.
That's right. We're almost there.
Bye.
Did you have fun today?
Good night. Have a good dream.
Bye bye.
I'll be back.
Bye.
Bye, Chu.