Kind Ye act
I want to see
so many songs
Ye ye ye ye ye
You're on my way
Hello
It's me
How are you, how are you
I'm going to go to bed.
Come on in.
I'll turn on the song.
What should I play?
How do I do this?
Wait
This is not my ID
I'll change it to my ID
Hello
Siwoo is so cute
So cute
As soon as I saw the shoes
I was shocked because they were so cute
Crocs are this small
So Siwoo can wear them
What was the password?
I did it
Okay
What is this face?
Please do this face
I don't know
Is it 3 a.m. in America?
Oh my god
3 a.m.?
Isn't it too late?
Just do it
Okay
I'll do it
What song should I dance to?
I'll dance to my favorite song
All right
Here we go
There's so much left to say
I guess I'm just a little bit by bit
I'm just a bit by bit
LUNIVERSE will be released at 8pm, so I'll turn it off before that because I have to focus on LUNIVERSE.
It's not black hair. I just toned it down, but it looks like black hair.
It's a little bit like an old-fashioned color.
My hair doesn't tie. Look at this.
What should I do? When will it grow?
Are you here because you're bored again today?
Yes, that's right.
Thank you.
Wait a minute. I want to tie my hair, but my hair doesn't come out like this.
I'll force you to tie it up.
The first
I'll cut the wood.
Do you want to die?
How do you cut it?
Like this?
You know what a summer rock is, right?
Oh, but because of this.
When you tie it up like this,
You know that taste, right?
hatred
Do you know what it is?
I like it.
I'll do it like this.
Eat a job
This is my favorite jelly lately.
It's crazy. This is so delicious.
Do I have to cover it?
This came out because I looked at it more than yuktae image.
This is how I feel.
Sherring
Go
Yes yes yes yes yes
It's a live video, so there's a clapping sound.
Can you hear the piano?
Hello.
This is really good.
There's a more delicious jelly left after the lizard jelly.
It's really good.
There's a more delicious jelly left.
Is it perfect?
I've got a good feeling now.
I feel good.
It's not perfect.
My clothes are...
I just did this.
The time has come to wear clothes, everyone.
I have to wear this.
I bought this jacket for this autumn.
How is it? Isn't it pretty?
Like this
I can't see my face
My posture
was my effort
I wanted to show it to you
The person who plays the song
is not playing the song
If you suddenly introduce the clothes
What are you going to do?
Seyeon
I'm not going to play the dance
I can play the dance
It's not fun
Funny
similar to reality
I'm going to comb my hair
My hair is short
I'm going to comb my front hair
OMG
Half dough
If you freeze it, it's more delicious.
What are you doing?
This jelly?
This?
You're going to freeze it?
Then how do you chew it?
What kind of schedule did you have today?
Today...
I'm filming right now.
I can't tell you.
You know I can't tell you.
Just take a pretty picture.
It ended too early than I thought.
It's been a while since I've done this.
I see.
I thought it would end so soon.
It's over a lot earlier than expected.
I was very happy.
So, uh, it's over early.
And right away.
I said, paradox live.
I was really happy.
What's wrong?
This is the first time I've seen this kind of music video in a long time, so I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Just fall into the trap!
These can be normal?
This shouldn't be possible.
So I'm ready to journey again
It's okay now
Really? I can't believe it's breaking
No way
Sing a band song
I really like band songs
Don't you think you know what I mean?
When I recommend a song
I recommend that kind of song a lot
I really like that kind of song
I want to try it one day
But it's breaking?
Oh my
Why is it breaking? Is it because it's in the basement?
Do I get a song request? Yes, I do
I totally get it
Give me a beer
It's really me
I'm really hungry
Let's think together
What should we eat for dinner?
Next song
It's really me
What should we eat for dinner?
We are fine
I need a beer
Pillow
Spicy ins Cooper
I love it
I want some soup
We are almost 8 am
but HBD?
Let's get ready.
I don't have time for this.
It's always been my plan.
I need to listen to our song.
Ms. La Femme's
1-800-HOT-AND-FUN
I really like this song.
It's my song, but I love it.
I love it!
I'm so hungry, FIONA.
I can sleep, I can sleep.
I really like this song.
Red Velvet
Play my favorite song, raise the roof
Let the dogs up, play something by Beyoncé
I'm not tryna leave until they kick us to the road
There's a flat scene of Kimchi-jjim and Spam-chun
I like to dance when I party
I like to kick everybody
Where the heck is that?
She's waiting down in the lobby
I'm tryna break it down, yeah baby
Get it, turn up the party
I like to dance when I party
But I've never been to a party
I like to kiss everybody
Actually, I hate kissing people
I learned this
She's waiting down in the lobby
I'm tryna break it down, yeah baby
Get it, turn up the party
1-800-HOT-AND-FUN
That's my number, it's in my line
Feel my rhythm every time
1-800-HOT-AND-FUN
I don't know how to tie this up.
I'm so into your hair.
I know what this is.
If you tie this up, will you be saved like this?
Lifted up the top, I play something by Beyonce
I'm not tryna leave until they kick us to the road
But if they do, it's cool to get an address, see my phone
I like to dance when I party
I like to kiss everybody
Where the heck is that?
She's waiting down in the lobby
I'm tryna break it down, yeah baby
Get it, turn up the party
Aw..
No. We have two minutes.
What is she recording?
I'm so nervous..
same time, same mark
Bon Appetite!
Ttura heart
I like udon
But I'm so hungry that I want to recommend Him some food
That's my girl
My baby
I want to eat them all
Let's listen to a calm song
A calm song
I'll show you a calm song
Why are you crying when you're at the academy?
It's good but sad
Sorry
The timing wasn't right
Why are you crying when you're at the academy?
What's in the bag?
I don't have anything in my bag
I really don't have anything in my bag today
SuA, please take a selfie today
Okay
I can still feel the fire of that dirty old town and it burns
The title of the song is I Left My Heart
She's waiting for me cause she knows that we need each other
I know we feel like we're left in a hurry
But that's just how she told me goodbyes
No doubt we will create what she's waiting for me
And I wish I could be there tonight
Oh, I wish I could be there tonight
I miss the faces and I watch the stories
From strangers that feel just like home
I use the same old one-liners he taught me
While dreaming of the future
Drinking until the bar is closed
But now when I go home I'm sleeping
I miss the faces and I watch the stories
From strangers that feel just like home
While dreaming of the future
I miss the faces and I watch the stories
ª
I want to master Japanese
Let's watch UNIVERSE together
I want to watch it together
But I'm so hungry
I'm so hungry
I have to go eat
I want to eat
She's so nice
There's only 3 minutes left
3 minutes?
No way
That's how fast it is, everyone
I'm pretty right now
Right now
I want to do it for a long time
Live
Really
I think it's the last song
I found something good
There's a song called
It's good
Yeah, it's
Love
Yes, it's good
It's been a while since I've seen the end of the world.
It was a very different day from yesterday.
The color and smell of the wind.
I don't know.
Oh, right.
I don't know why I brought my shoes to the basement.
I don't know.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
It was fun.
Oh, I can't speak.
It was so hot at that time.
I went there when it was really hot.
One minute left.
Taeyeon, it's about time.
I can't believe it.
Look at the mini version now.
I'll leave.
Bye.
Yay!
Bye! See you on LENIVERSE!
What?
See you!
Bye! See you on LENIVERSE!