Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
I brought this bread.
I know.
I'm doing it now.
I'm doing it. I haven't
been on the show for
a long time, so I want
to be on it one day.
I've never been on a roller coaster,
so I want to go out one day.
I'm eating salt bread.
I'm going to eat salt bread.
I haven't been live for a long time.
When was it?
During the promotion.
Last time I
did it for a short time.
Where did it go?
Someone said it was fun at
the fan signing event yesterday.
Thank you for coming to
the fan signing event today.
What should I talk about?
After the fan signing
event today... And...
I was shooting the content.
Why the practice room? Is it a concert?
I think you should wait a
little longer for the concert.
You have to have a lot of
songs to make it really different.
So...
I asked a lot of questions today.
Even at the fan signing event.
Wait a little longer.
I'll just wait.
Let's have a year-end performance.
Do it well.
Earlier... At the Han River...
They did a fireworks
They did a fireworks show?
Fireworks?
It wasn't a party.
It wasn't that much of a size.
Is it a firework festival?
So I went up to the rooftop.
I went to see it with my managers.
Yes, it's really amazing.
Really?
It's been a long time since I
saw the fireworks properly.
Ever since I was a student...
Ever since I was a student, I used to
see them a lot when I was in my teens.
But for me...
When I have summer break, I
go to see them with my family.
I saw them a lot when I was an idol.
Did you cry?
Wow, there's someone
who knows me from the past.
I didn't cry, but the
sound was really loud.
So I was a little scared.
But other than that, it was
okay. They were so pretty.
It's like...
I'm not the type of person
who just thinks they're pretty.
It's like...
I was wondering how many people
in Korea are watching these fireworks.
When I see these fireworks next year,
I was wondering what
kind of person I would be.
It was pretty, right?
There was a fireworks
competition at the Han River.
All the managers were watching it.
Oh, that's right.
I was told a lot about where I
went for the punishment game.
For now...
I can't do it in front of people
who don't know the flow.
I decided to do it at Weverse Live.
I'll do it someday.
I had a pack. I have to do it in Portugal.
But no matter how much I think about it,
I don't know the flow.
There are other fans.
It's not easy to do it.
I don't have the courage to do it.
I don't get the courage to do it.
Still, I had a schedule.
I had a schedule.
When I went to work, I
already had makeup on me.
This is what happened.
Unfortunately, I can't go to work.
I'll just do it someday at Weverse Live.
Please understand.
And I want to see pretty faces.
On the way to work.
So.
Compared to the other members,
it wasn't easy for me and Eunchae
I'll do it next time
Have you seen all the fireworks?
Pretty
I ate the soup, the
clam chowder? I ate it.
Long time no see.
I just ate it simply and ate it
properly after I got off work.
I ate it simply.
Can I play something I want to listen to?
Sabrina Carpenter did a live.
Seriously, so pretty.
Did you see that, everyone?
I think some people don't know.
Like this.
Wait.
I want to explain it properly. At this
Sabrina concert,
At first, it was a little...
It was a little late concept.
So I was covering my clothes like this.
I know, I know.
Does anyone know?
I came like this.
Show it like this.
I was so scared.
And then I looked at it like this.
The microphone didn't come out.
I'm doing this.
All the movements are so lovely.
How can it be so lovely?
But when I'm watching, it's so cute.
That's it.
Tiktok...
These days...
There was someone who did the challenge.
I should do it later.
This song is really...
We got a vacation this time, right?
At that time in Hawaii...
I went to Hawaii with my family.
But I went to the beach at night.
The beach is right in front of the hotel.
There's a place where you can lie down.
I was listening to this
song while lying down there.
I think the lyrics of
Sabrina's song are so cute.
It's like a lovely...
Feeling annoying?
I like it.
It's cute.
I can't hate it.
I was listening to this song
when I was on vacation in Hawaii.
I don't feel like I burned my hands.
My hands are burning.
I didn't burn my hands
a lot in other places.
I burned a little, but
my hands are burning.
My hands are burning.
I don't know why.
It's good that I don't eat.
It's good.
I want to go to the concert.
This Sabrina's set is so cute.
It was so nice to sing
while sitting at the heart.
It was good.
We went to VMA.
The set was... There
were two stages.
Really, here...
There are two stages.
But if you do it this way...
It leads this way...
Suddenly something really different...
It's a house
The set was amazing.
It was amazing.
It was like watching a musical.
It was VMA.
It wasn't our stage.
It was the stage at the awards ceremony.
The stage we were watching.
It was amazing.
I'm wearing it because I
want to talk about vacation.
Shall we talk about vacation?
We got vacation for the first time.
So...
It's like...
It's kind of...
Since I was young, There's
something about Japanese.
If you say
vacation, It's Hawaii.
It's a must.
There's something like that.
Something like that.
So I... There's
something like that.
Celebrities go to Hawaii on vacation.
Something like that.
Since I was in elementary school,
Ever since I was a student,
There was something like that.
The atmosphere was like that.
So I have to go on vacation there.
When I heard that
a vacation was coming this time,
I have to go to Hawaii.
I called my mom right away.
So... Mom, I have
to go to Hawaii.
I've never been there.
This vacation is in Hawaii.
So...
I went.
I'll explain in Japanese.
When I was told that I was
going on vacation for the first time,
Something like... Vacation?
Vacation equals... Celebrities'
vacation equals Hawaii.
It's been like that for a long time.
That kind of atmosphere.
Something like that.
It's just my imagination.
I've never been to Hawaii.
Once.
I thought I'd definitely go to
Hawaii on my first vacation.
So I went to Hawaii.
At first,
There was a hotel called Kahala Hotel.
There was a hotel where they
were building dolphins in the hotel.
But it's about 10 minutes
away from Waikiki.
There's not much people there.
From the hotel to the swimming pool.
It's all connected to the sea.
Next to the swimming pool.
Are you raising a dolphin?
So you can just see the dolphins.
If you make a reservation there.
From 9 o'clock.
A little bit.
Experience.
Swim with the dolphins.
Play with the dolphins.
There's something like that.
So I made a reservation for that, too.
And there's a restaurant in the hotel.
It's a really famous restaurant there.
Just in Hawaii.
So I ate there.
It was really good.
So what was it?
On the first day.
I don't remember.
All of a sudden.
Wait a minute.
Oh, right.
On the first day.
This is.
It's really a little bit.
It's my first time.
Anyone can see.
I wanted to be like a
person who came to travel.
Everyone is famous.
It's like a minor.
It's not like a person who
lives in Hawaii is going.
For the first time in Hawaii.
Like a person.
I wanted to do it.
Famous in Japan.
From CF.
There's a really big tree.
It's called Konoki Nanoki.
I went to see that tree.
What did I do on the first day?
I really don't remember.
All of a sudden.
First.
I did that.
The next day.
Oh.
Snorkeling?
That.
I got on a yacht.
The sea.
I think it's a crab.
I went pretty far.
There.
This.
I'm wearing goggles.
Like this.
Watching the sea.
Swim with the fish.
And there's a turtle.
There's just a turtle.
Next to it.
But we can't get close.
But if you come
from there. Well.
You can see it from a distance.
I've experienced that.
I did that.
I did a lot of things.
It was really fun.
I saw a turtle.
I examined a turtle.
That.
Surfboard.
Not really surfing.
Like this.
There's something like
a canoe, and that too...
I uploaded a picture, so it
was there, but I also did that...
Oh, that's right.
I'm not that good at English...
I went with my mom
and younger brother, right?
My dad was going to go too, but
he suddenly got sick and
couldn't go, so the three of us went.
Oh, by the way he's okay now.
Are you worried? Are you okay?
My dad is the best at English,
but he couldn't do it, so I was like,
what should I do?
I had no choice but to speak English,
so I tried my best to speak English.
When I was on the surfboard, it was
at the same time as this Korean person.
I made a reservation for the same time.
They didn't recognize me,
but I kept speaking in Korean.
They were good at English,
so I spoke in English.
The English was a bit faster back
then, so I couldn't understand it.
I took a picture
and there was some explanation about whether
to save it to them via USB or SD card.
It was difficult, so I
asked them in Korean,
But by any chance... this...
Just once, how do you say in English...
Can you translate
that for me? He said...
In Korean...
I switched to Korean, and
they were really surprised.
They were like, wasn't that Japanese?
I said, I'm living in Korea,
so I can speak Korean.
We could communicate in three languages.
I explained it to my mom in
Japanese, and when she replied,
I translated it to Korean.
Then the Koreans
translated it into English.
There were so many languages at that time.
But I was relieved that
I could speak Korean.
They said they just like traveling.
Recently, I went to Fukuoka.
They said, wait really?
Fukuoka is my hometown.
We talked about it.
It was fun.
It was amazing.
English...
It was really hard.
The most I can talk about is...
I was the only one there.
My brother said he didn't want to talk
because he was embarrassed.
I had no choice but to speak.
My younger brother also speaks English.
Well, but still?
Did you go to kindergarten
when you were young?
In terms of...
I went to kindergarten
Did you?
And you're learning this in school
now, if you're a middle school student.
So, I had no choice but to do it.
He kept saying it's embarrassing...
I had no choice but to do it.
But it's understandable.
And you saw all the pictures, right?
It's almost all my brother's pictures.
My mom is really bad at taking pictures.
Really.
Seriously, seriously.
There's nothing you can do about it.
There are things that people are good at.
That's true.
But it was such a pretty scene.
No, like this landscape was so pretty
like this is so real I
need to take a picture...
It's really cool.
Really.
So I told my mom.
Please.
Like this, I said, Mom, try it.
I set the angle.
Mom, mom, now, now.
You know this angle, right?
But my mom moved it.
Yeah... right now...
well...
I was going to tell you...
I guess there are some difficulties.
My younger brother was
watching it from the side. So...
But...
Let my little brother take the picture.
He was right next to me, so he
was listening to what I was saying.
He understood everything... so...
So, my brother took a picture of me.
But the funny thing is that...
I uploaded it on Instagram.
My mom called me and said,
Oh, but, I think I took such a good photo!
I said, Mom, that's my brother's picture.
She said, Oh, really? No?
I said, No, it's not.
She was like, Ah, I took
all these pictures, so...
I had a lot of fun.
My little brother was taking a picture of
me.
My brother is better at
taking pictures than I thought.
My mom really can't take pictures.
It's really horrible.
It's a picture that looks like a lie.
Even if I say stay in the
middle, Is that difficult?
That's why my brother
kept taking pictures of me.
My younger brother took this photo.
It's been a long time since
I've talked to my brother.
We talk a lot.
I used to hang out with my brother often.
After my brother became a student,
I've never really hung out with him.
When I came to Tokyo,
Sometimes I just looked at the picture.
It was my first time
seeing him for a long time.
We talked and it was fun.
We're the same age.
It's difficult.
He seems like he'd be
good at being a photographer.
But...
But I was always shy about taking pictures.
Photographer, are you interested?
But about myself...
But I was embarrassed
to shoot my own picture.
It's fun.
I want to try to do my hair in this style.
Why am I so shy?
I guess it's because of that.
But I was even more shy.
It wasn't during the middle school,
but when I was in elementary school,
I went to eat.
Moms would ask me to
help with something like this.
I like it.
So that I could greet them well.
But I was so bad at it.
I was so shy. I cried there.
I was so shy.
So my mom saw that and said I was too shy.
So I went to learn musicals.
That was the beginning.
So my brother...
I think he's better than me.
It was really bad.
Now I'm not as shy anymore.
But it was really bad then.
I was like that when I was young.
It's okay.
It's not always the same.
I realized that when I lived my life.
I was so different from
what I was when I was young.
Even though I was in
a different environment.
So I wasn't really worried about it.
I was like, I'm just a person.
That's how it is when you're young.
You learn as you go.
That's what I think.
When I went to Hawaii,
there were a lot of
people who recognized me.
But that was... Even if I
wasn't Korean or Japanese.
A lot of people recognized me.
They spoke to me in English.
I went to a steakhouse.
It's really famous.
Everyone in Hawaii goes there.
What's the name?
Joyce?
Jaws?
Jays?
It was a steakhouse.
The staff there.
They were like, Are you Sakura?
It was so... It was amazing.
My mom was watching.
She said that she was touched.
My daughter... Wherever
she went, she recognized me.
It's not that much.
It's amazing.
But she recognized me in English.
She talked to me.
So... It was amazing.
It was amazing for me, too.
Where do the members want to go next?
Members?
Members... It would
be fun to go anywhere.
Next... If I get a vacation,
I want to go to Jeju Island.
I want to go nearby.
Next time.
Or I want to go to Hawaii again.
I love Hawaii.
If I get a vacation
next time, I want to go...
I want to go to a nearby place.
I want to go to Jeju Island.
Or I want to go to Hawaii again.
A warm place... It
feels like a vacation site.
I don't like cold places.
It's a little...
It's a lot of luggage.
Do you know what I mean?
Luggage becomes like that.
But if you go to a warm place,
You can just take a t-shirt or a one-piece.
You can just take thin clothes.
So... I like light clothes.
It was a very T statement.
Right?
I think you know what I mean.
I'm a realistic person.
Because... There are a
lot of things I want to get.
If I just pack a
padded jacket, It's over.
I'm so sad about that.
I wonder if it's still possible in Japan.
Certainly, not at all.
What should I do?
You don't know, do you?
Please wait a little longer.
Just a little bit more.
I bought this hat because it's too cute.
I want to see you wearing it.
There were a lot of
people who wore it today.
This is a wink.
Happy birthday, Seulgi and I.
Happy birthday!
These days...
Culinary Class Wars is really popular...
Do you watch them all?
I haven't watched it yet.
I heard it's really fun.
I haven't even seen the meme.
I only know what the members say.
I'll think about it.
I'll think about it for a while.
What is this?
I'm going to cover my eyes and eat it.
I heard the explanation of what it is.
I was going to watch it,
but I haven't seen it yet.
I made a lot of posters.
Who did you see?
Chaewon and Yunjin and Zuha.
I think so.
When we go to local events...
We missed Zuha.
Right.
We went to the university
festival this week.
It was really fun.
The university students had a lot of fun.
It was so much fun.
We went to the festival as
soon as the vacation was over.
So... Something...
It felt like we were performing
for the first time in a long time.
I had a lot of fun.
And...
We went to Busan and Daegu.
Is it the first time for us to go?
As a schedule?
I went to Busan once in the past.
This time, On the day
we arrived in Busan,
It was dawn.
We went to eat grilled clams.
The next day, I woke up.
I had beoguk... beoguk?
Beoguk. Burger and soup.
It was really good.
I really like it.
Bugeoguk soup.
Right.
We had a burger there.
Bugeo... And...
We had fried food.
I really like burgers.
It's been a long time since I had it.
I was so happy.
After eating that,
We went to the beach.
We saw the sea.
The next day, We went to Daegu.
It was dawn.
We had to eat something delicious.
So, We had makjang (pork offal).
It was the first time I had
makjang at a restaurant.
It was really delicious.
It was a little serious.
It was so delicious.
Does it taste the same
when you eat it in Daegu?
Or, Does it taste the same
when you eat it in Seoul?
I really want to eat it.
It was so delicious.
I ate it in Daegu.
It was delicious, really.
In our WIZONE team,
There's someone who
knows Daegu well, So,
Does it taste the same
when you eat it in Seoul?
Does it taste delicious because it's Daegu?
Then, I have to go to Daegu.
If you want to eat it with that taste,
Do I have to go to Daegu?
I should go.
I should go right away.
I really should.
It was really good
It was my first time eating
makjang at a restaurant
It was crispy and so
good It was so good
After that, I went to Busan
after the fan signing event
As soon as I arrived in
Busan I ate clam kalguksu
I ate a lot of delicious food
After that, I did pilates
in Seoul yesterday
I almost died It was so
hard It hurts even when I walk
Really... Walking hurts, too.
My muscles hurt so much
Do you want to eat
kalguksu? It's really good
I like it
I didn't see the fireworks festival
I saw it when the 500
million subscribers were up
I saw it I didn't do it
Oh, right. I went to see IU's concert.
It was the first time.
We... We were guests this year.
We couldn't watch it because it was
in the middle of the music show.
So we went.
It was really fun.
It was crazy.
They were so pretty.
They were so good.
It was like Disney.
All the directors.
They sang all the songs I knew.
After that, I went to say hello.
They said, I wanted to
say thank you for the hat.
I'll meet you in person.
That's why I talked about it.
I was like, that's right, and the hat...
My house is still... I've been
keeping it in a really pretty place
I've been keeping it
in a really pretty place
I'm so happy that you're saying that.
Oh, my God.
It's really...
They said they're keeping it well.
It was so good.
Thank you
Thank you.
So I'm carrying a key ring in my bag.
This... But it without the top.
I love you so much.
My mom went with me.
Since my mom was young...
No, not since my mom was young.
Since I was young,
we watched a lot of Korean dramas together.
My family really liked it,
so I watched it with them.
We watched it together.
I really liked it.
It was so much fun.
It's already been 35 minutes.
I'm hungry.
I worked so hard on my lower body.
It really hurts.
I really hate muscle pain.
Do you have a hobby these days?
I'm still looking for a hobby.
I don't have anything specific.
Come to a Japanese
cultural festival.
There aren't many
festivals like that in Japan.
There's a talk show.
I've never heard of an
idol coming and performing.
I wish I could.
Is it difficult?
Not really.
I'm waiting for the day off.
I haven't taken the day off yet.
When is it?
My heart is beating.
There's a place that I've been
to, wow.
I want to go there, it's fun.
When is fimlog?
Fimlog, this time, at
the university festival,
I recorded while walking around.
But it's really...
It's not one by one, it's just...
Difficult Fimlog?
Same?
I don't know when it will come out.
I hope it's one day soon.
Of course, I like that
kind of group fimlog,
I used to film it once a week
One person at a time.
It was really fun back then,
and I want to do it again.
It's like a real improvement.
It was a content where I could really
feel what kind of person I was on that day.
So I want to say, I want to do it again.
I think it would be nice to
do it at the end of the year.
Because I go back and
forth and go abroad a lot.
It was one of my favorite content.
And it was really fun.
I'm going to go now.
2 minutes left.
Up to 40 minutes.
1 year later, I'm doing a fimlog?
Really?
You didn't do it by yourself, did you?
I'll do it a lot.
They told me not to go.
I don't want to.
Yes, I haven't gone yet.
I don't know when I'm going to go.
UNIVERSE has...
I'm filming that
Actually, for UNIVERSE...
Even before our promotion for CRAZY...
Is that all? Halmyungsoo...
What I was filming...
I have a lot of games.
And this Leniverse is a bit...
A new...
시도가 많아 (sidoga manh-a).
I'm sorry.
It's been a while since I've been on
Weverse Lab.
Bless you... me.
Bless me.
So...
Please look forward to it.
I think it's going to be fun.
I don't know how it's going to turn out.
But it's going to be fun.
It's been a while since I did Weverse Live.
I'll get closer to you again.
It's been a while since
I've been on Weverse Live.
I'll be back again.
It's 10 o'clock soon I'm tired.
Go to sleep.
Let's do our best tomorrow as well!
Fearnot go to bed early.
Fighting!
Fearnot, I'll go to bed early
and do my best tomorrow.
Fighting!
Bye bye.
Subscribe!