Who do they like & who are they worried about?
Hi
Hello
Everyone gather, gather, gather
You didn't expect it, right?
I didn't expect it either
We just came back from doing the choreography
So it's a little bit like that
All of a sudden?
All of a sudden
All of a sudden, it's okay, right?
Because it's going out
That's right, that's right, I practiced
What are you doing right now?
It's Friday afternoon
Hello
Hi
Thank you for your hard work
Wait a minute
It's time
I wanted to play with Fiona, so I put it on after a long time
What is it? Why is it so black here?
How are you? I'm good
How are you, Fiona?
Hi
Are you all busy right now?
Are you going home after work?
There must be a lot of people
Or are you still working?
Every day
Just living is really amazing
Um
Oh, I'm studying, but I came to see you
I came to see you
I'm going to study
Oh right
Next month
I'm going back to Osaka
Oh, it's getting a little cold in Japan
In Korea too
Recently
It feels a little cold
Then the bangs
This is the bangs
Now
Here
The bangs
Welcome
I
No banks
Oh
Yes
I cabeça
Originally, I wanted to go to Italy or somewhere like that.
At first, I wanted to go.
I wanted to go to a country that I had never been to before.
I thought about it.
I wanted to go to Paris for my first vacation.
When I was studying abroad,
Before the quarantine started,
I had a vacation at a ballet school.
At that time, my mom and dad came to the Netherlands.
So I was there for about a week.
I took a train with my parents and went to Paris for the first time.
I have a really good memory of that time.
I wanted to go there again.
I had to eat lunch.
Two years? Three years?
What was it?
The name is,
a kind of food named Cascade?
In three years, I'm going to go again.
It's been 3 years since I went back to Paris.
I went to Paris for the first time with my mom and dad as a foreign student.
We had dinner together.
I'm eating the same food in the same restaurant with my mom.
I felt very strange.
I think it's a very meaningful restaurant for me.
When will LUNAVERSE come out?
LUNAVERSE?
LUNAVERSE...
You can look forward to it.
LUNAVERSE is really...
It's really...
It's amazing.
I think LUNAVERSE knows loyalty more than loyalty.
LUNAVERSE staff.
Thank you so much.
Thank you and I love you.
There's going to be a lot of fun content.
It's always been like that.
More...
In a variety of ways.
More new...
I think I'll be able to see loyalty.
Today's fashion show is totally comfort.
The theme is comfort.
That's right.
I said that, and it suddenly came out.
Marion's more embarrassed.
So, I was surprised, too.
It came out well when I took it upright.
It's really funny.
I didn't even imagine it then.
I didn't know I'd take the shoe thief.
I became a real thief.
Jaewon.
The other members are on their separate schedules.
We've been together until now.
Spoiler? What spoiler?
I really like spoilers.
What kind of spoiler?
The lighting.
It's working.
Another episode.
We took a TikTok together.
Please wait a moment.
Is the monitor the lighting?
Yes, it is.
The monitor.
My PC.
The white background is my lighting.
It's a white background.
Like this.
The blue background.
The blue background is fine.
No, the white background.
It's too white.
The white background is too white.
The blue background is fine.
Kaza, your eyes are so shiny.
Really?
So the shot is considerate like this.
As expected, I want to eat something warm because it's getting a little chilly.
Recommend me ice cream. Ice cream.
The one at the convenience store.
Dubai chocolate ice cream.
It's sold these days.
Yoonjin told me about it.
It was good.
I don't know what Dubai chocolate is.
My teacher bought it for me and I ate it.
It was really good.
Dubai chocolate.
Is it popular in Japan?
Is it popular all over the world?
I don't know.
I really want to eat chestnut tiramisu.
What should I do?
Chestnut tiramisu.
I think it will be really good.
I really respect it.
Dubai chocolate is popular.
Um.
Can you do an impersonation of your sister?
Whose impersonation is it?
Short hair? I want to try it once.
I want to try it once.
But if I do it, it's a little...
How should I say it?
It's a little embarrassing.
No.
I think it's going to be a little embarrassing.
It's not like that.
I think it's going to change my image.
That's how it is.
Honey, it's not short hair.
It's not short hair.
You're so sure.
That's good.
Honesty.
It's over there?
Yeah.
Ah.
It's done.
How tall are you?
I haven't tried it lately.
When I first debuted, I was 74cm tall, so I was surprised.
Is it there or not?
What should I say?
I don't know if it's there or not.
It's hard to say in Korean.
Is it there or not?
Am I taller than Eunchae?
Uh, but, I don't know.
Isn't it similar?
Be careful of the bread. Why are you being careful?
I'll be on MINA's LIVE next time, and I'll be asking you to compare my height in front of the fans.
Show... Show...
Comparison.
I'll do that.
It's really not easy to work out.
I worked out thinking about soy sauce marinated crab today.
I think I'm going to eat with the members later.
I worked out thinking about soy sauce marinated crab.
Hamstring.
You know, the thing you do like this.
The machine that you bend in the back.
I did that.
Soy sauce marinated crab.
I was doing it, and it gave me strength.
As expected, the power of appetite.
I recommend you to do this.
Think about what you want to eat and exercise.
But I think I'm a bit tanned these days.
Sometimes I look tanned.
I told YUNJIN that.
I said, I think I'm tanned these days.
YUNJIN said, ZUHA, do you know this?
I think I'm tanned.
But T says I don't think I'm tanned at all.
So you're tanned.
That's what she said.
Oh, I see. Then I'm tanned.
I guess I'm tanned.
I guess I'm tanned from the thought of it.
Should I doâ?
You have to have a Доji.
I...
from Busan, from Daegu.
I ate makjang and daechang and it was so good
I used to like daechang a lot
Not daechang, makjang and...
What's makjang and?
Makjang and...
Not makjang and...
What's makjang and?
Let me know
Makjang...
Right, right, there's makjang-gori in Daegu
Gopchang, makjang, daechang
Right, I ate gopchang and makjang
It was really good
It was better at the restaurant
I'll recommend Gopchang to Fiona today
Chipotle
I saw chipotle in Paris
So...
I was going to go
I wanted to go but I didn't
I wanted to introduce it to my mom
I wanted to introduce it to her
Did you enjoy Zimline?
Shh
It's still a secret
We know everything
Right, Fiona knows everything
Really
I still remember Zimline
That's sooo cute
What?
Did you know that?
You can make a heart
ribbon heart
The person who thought of the ribbon heart is amazing.
What?
"It's just a pose even if you stay still."
You're cool.
cheek fat
Congratulations on your birthday.
"Where's all the cheek fat?"
Where did it go?
Yes.
I wanted to hang out with you for a while.
It's already been 25 minutes.
It's really fast.
Something's coming out at 5 o'clock.
I don't think it's a big deal.
I'll go now.
Is it enough?
I'm sure there's something big enough.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
See you again.
Have a good dinner.
Bye, I'll have something delicious.
Bye-bye.
See you again.