Hi, FEARNOT
FEARNOT, gather around
Where did ZUHA go?
ZUHA? ZUHA is here
ZUHA is here
FEARNOT
Let me go
I was wrong
Hi
What was that?
I haven't asked yet
FEARNOT, it was our last show
It was our last show
It was our last show today
You didn't know, right?
Our last show
We want it
I'll take a picture
Don't look
Thank you
I can't say anything
Congrats
Last show
This time
I think
We played well
Why?
We went to the US
Because we all went to New York together.
That's right.
There's that too.
Mission positive.
Ah, MICHIN(positive).
MICHIN(positive).
Yeah.
It was so MICHIN(positive).
So MICHIN(positive).
But I think we went there really fast.
Really.
It was Friday.
Ah, right.
That's right.
So if we count it as one week, it's almost two weeks.
Actually,
But actually,
That's right.
It's a joke.
It was short.
But you guys wanted to see it a lot.
That's right.
It's sad, but well..
There's no need to be sad.
We'll see it someday.
So,
I'll show it someday.
Of course.
Don't you think so too, FEARNOT?
FEARNOT also thinks about it now.
Someday we'll go.
I mean, you guys know what it's like.
Now,
Ah, this song...
Ah, you sang it back then.
Ya.
This song is definitely,
this.
And we read it.
Since it's our last show today,
we're going to put something on our feet.
We didn't do it right now, but...
During the music show,
we put something on our feet.
That is...
HOT.
Lightning.
That is...
Our hearts.
This crazy...
Hearts.
This crazy positive three weeks.
Three weeks.
Thank you for being with us for three weeks.
Our love.
Did you enjoy it?
What?
Really?
This?
Yes.
That's it.
I'm sorry.
We...
Thank you.
What did you just say?
No.
What did you say?
When did you pass?
When it passed,
we played VLIVE in the same background in New York.
When did it pass?
Now?
When?
When...
It passed.
Before we met each other.
It passed like this?
Yes.
It really passed.
About this time.
You said you don't remember.
Five of us sat down here and played VLIVE.
Yes.
Let's do it again.
We played VLIVE in the U.S.?
No.
Was it in the U.S.?
Before Dishonored West came,
Dishonored West?
Oh, right!
It was Dishonored West!
That's right!
When we entered, we kept saying hello to the FEARNOT.
I don't remember.
You must have been very nervous.
No, the three of us were more nervous.
I was fine.
I fainted after it was over.
I remember early.
It was a really busy day.
It was probably the busiest day of the three days.
Was it the first day?
It was the first day.
Why?
I couldn't wait.
Between schedules,
the time was a little empty.
But I was lying on the floor for a minute.
I can't do it.
5 minutes?
But I had to do it right away.
Hi!
It was really new.
It's so funny.
How did that happen?
There was about 5 minutes.
I couldn't sleep.
I couldn't do it.
As soon as I lay down,
I said,
Hi!
Nice to meet you.
I can't do it.
What should I do?
There's nothing to do like this.
I don't have much time.
I was the first person to ask
Really, everyone.
Thank you so much for the votes.
Thank you so much.
This was a special vote.
It's a real vote.
Thank you for the votes.
Me?
Thank you!
The voting was very special.
Right, and we always post our proof shots too.
The two of us are like this.
We're like, you voted? You voted? We voted for you.
That kind of atmosphere is so...
Cute and lovely. Thank you so much.
It was so much fun.
It was a great week.
It was really fun.
Wow.
There were a lot of things that happened in these three weeks.
We didn't have a lot of fans, but...
What was it? M Countdown and...
Right, M Countdown.
Right.
Thank you.
But we didn't have any fans.
How do you feel?
How do I feel?
Actually, the first place is...
LESSERAFIM!
Yes, thanks to FEARNOT,
we were able to have a great time.
Thanks to FEARNOT,
FEARNOT is crazy!
Right?
Yes.
Crazy?
FEARNOT is crazy!
Did you believe it?
Thank you.
Thanks to FEARNOT,
we had a lot of unbelievable moments.
Thank you so much.
We'll do our best and show you a good performance.
We'll make you happy.
And our SOURCE MUSIC!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
SOURCE!
All the staff worked really hard.
Yeah, right.
For our team...
For MSM...
Right.
The three of you worked really hard.
MS was so pretty this time.
She's crazy!
It was a crazy positive!
A crazy positive!
Thank you so much.
Yes.
It's a great award.
Thank you, members.
Yes, yes.
The members are working hard too.
You all worked hard.
Isn't that it?
It is.
It's a little bit...
I'm going to go up there.
Visualizer? Visualizer?
Right, right, right. That's really funny.
Oh, what's that?
That's really funny.
But in the middle, it's so funny that she's wearing clothes.
It's the same.
It's the same color as the chroma key.
What's that? I don't know.
I don't know.
I was just going to do it.
So I pretended to wear it.
But it came out so well.
It came out the same as the picture.
But it was so much fun.
It was so real.
Thank you.
I keep watching it even though there's nothing.
It's so funny.
Is it all out now?
Now...
It came out at 6 o'clock today.
Call Me On Zero.
That's right.
I took it a long time ago.
Sunny doesn't come out.
I'm curious.
What kind of concept did you like the most?
For me...
It's hard.
It's really hard.
It's hard, but...
The stage was fun.
VMA
The FEARNOT was amazing.
No, I never had a pre-recording with FEARNOT so close.
I felt the energy from the bottom of my heart.
I felt the energy from the top of my heart.
I was so touched.
The youngest members...
There's another world here.
We're in another world.
It's hidden in the middle.
It's in the middle.
The lights are perfect.
V, V!
V
V, you have to be quiet.
Even if you're doing a V,
Even if I go this way,
I go this way.
It's really hard.
I hope you do well.
How did you do it?
EUNCHAE, are you okay?
EUNCHAE, you try it.
EUNCHAE, you're good at this.
She's really good at this.
No, no.
No, that's not it.
What was it?
Start!
No, no.
It didn't come out like that.
It came out really well.
I'll do it again.
I'm sorry.
MICHIN(positive)
Right, right.
It's the same.
We did weverse live in the practice room.
Right.
It was during the promotion.
I was surprised to hear that.
But it was really effective.
FEARNOT and LESSERAFIM must be together.
There's a lot of support.
That's right.
We won't do that.
We will do it with Weverse Live
Let's do it like that from now on
Then we will do it next time
Yes
From Chuseok
Have a good Chuseok
That's right
Chuseok
It's Chuseok holiday
Drive safely
Eat a lot of delicious food
I hope you come back safely
Yes
Stay healthy
Thank you, FEARNOT
Thank you so much for this promotion
Thank you so much
Thank you so much, FEARNOT
We have the end of the year
Let's cheer up until the end of this year
Let's cheer up
Bye bye