ENG TRANS & JLML718
Hi!
It's me.
Observing Alex's voice
Come on in
Mmm, it's good
Let me turn the music on
What am I playing?
Won't it work?
Wait
This is not my ID, so I'll change it to my ID
I'm going to change it to my ID.
Hello.
Siwoo is so cute, right?
So cute.
As soon as I saw the shoes,
they were so cute.
It was a shock.
Crocs are this small.
So Siwoo can wear them.
I'm going to change it to my ID.
I'm done.
Okay.
What's that face?
I don't know.
Is it 3 a.m. in America?
Oh my god.
3 a.m.?
Isn't it too early?
What song should I play?
I'll play my favorite song.
All right, here we go.
Excuse me.
I got it done, but it looks like a flower.
It's a bit like a year-old.
My hair doesn't tie. Look at this.
When are you going to grow it?
Are you bored again today?
Yes, that's right.
Wait a minute. I want to tie my hair, but my hair comes out like this.
I'm going to force it to tie it up.
First
Cut the wood?
Do you want to die?
What should I do?
It's so different.
You know what a summer rock is, right?
When you tie it up like this,
You know it tastes good, right?
Do you know what it is?
I like it.
I'll do it like this.
This is my favorite jelly these days.
It's crazy. This is so delicious.
Should I cover it?
I don't know why these days.
It's been a while since I heard the sound of a rock.
I've been hearing it's the best.
It's a live video, so there's a clapping sound.
Can you hear the piano?
Hello.
This is really good.
There's a more delicious jelly that's like the lizard jelly.
Is it perfect?
Okay, I'm going to go now.
I'm going to go now.
Is it perfect?
Okay, I've got the hang of it now.
I feel good.
What should I do?
Show me the outfit of your mind.
Okay.
Today's outfit is...
Ta-da.
Just like this.
It's time to wear my clothes.
I have to go around like this.
For this fall.
I bought this jacket.
How is it? Isn't it pretty?
What should I wear?
I'll take it off like this.
ðŸ“ž
Where's your pose...
What should I wear?
It was my effort.
I wanted to show you my hard work.
Wait, the person who's playing the music
is not playing the music right now.
If you suddenly introduce your clothes,
what are you going to do?
I'll play you my playlist.
Let's start.
Trust me.
If you freeze it, it tastes better.
Freeze what? This jelly?
This?
Freeze it?
Then how do you chew it?
What kind of schedule did you have today?
I just filmed it.
You know I can't tell you.
I just took a pretty picture and took a pretty video.
It ended earlier than I thought.
It's been a long time since I've done this.
It ended earlier than I expected.
I was so happy.
I finished early.
The picture quality is so good right now.
Isn't it good?
Is it not working?
It's not working right now.
It's not working?
It won't work.
There's me who put me in
So I'm ready to journey again
Even if I leave here and change
Deep in my heart, in my small island
There's me who put me in
So I'm ready to journey again
It's okay now
Really? It keeps breaking
It doesn't make sense
Make a band song!
I really like band songs
Don't you think you know what I mean?
When I recommend a song
I recommend that kind of song a lot
I really like band songs
I want to try it someday
But it's breaking?
Why is it breaking?
Is it because it's underground?
Did you get the song request?
Yes, I got it
I really really got it
Please give me a beer
It's really me
I really got a beer
I'm so hungry right now
Let's think together
What should I eat for dinner?
What should I eat for dinner today?
Folks
I want to eat soup like this.
But it's almost 8 o'clock.
I'm so...
But Looniverse is important.
I don't have much time.
It's always my plan.
I'm on a OLED TV set.
The stage is good.
I
I don't know.
Don't you prepare anything?
You need to work hard.
I think these music videos are easy to make classes.
Let's ã„ã¿
All right.
It's raining all day
I can't breathe
Oh I'm drowning
You're taking my heart
Really, I'm honestly just sad about my shoes
I like to dance when I party
I like to kiss everybody
Where the heck is Saki?
She's waiting down in the lobby
I'm trying to break it down, yeah baby yeah
Turn up the party
I like to dance when I party
I'm trying to break it down, yeah baby yeah
Turn up the party
Run it back, yeah, I like this track
Drop it, drop it back
Louis V, been around my neck do ya
Cuz I'm so classy
Let's get, break it down, girl
I bet you can get past me
Hopae, sweet angel, I'm so good
I'm so nerdy, so sassy
Oh shit, oh my god
DJ play my favorite song
Raise the roof, let the dogs
I played something by Beyonce
I'm not trying to leave until they kick us to the rock
What's this?
There's a flat scene of kimchi jjim and a spam chun.
I've learned this.
I really like the hair I just tied up.
I think I know what this is.
If you tie it up again, it won't be tied up like this.
No, we have two minutes left.
Bagel cream cheese looks delicious.
Oh, my God.
I'll show you the video with you, not confident.
After choosing the set of the outfit, I should take a break and go shopping.
But I came on the side.
I don't know anything.
Her love is no joke.
So please look at the other side too.
It's too hard to see.
el 2000
her
Her favorite song!
Please subscribe and like.
I'm ready to run, where my girls
So where my, where my girls at
Where my, where my boys at
Let's have a cup of coffee together
We're just like a man and a woman
Three of us, three of us, three of us, three of us, three of us
I'm so hungry right now
I want to recommend you something and eat it all
That's my girl
Like mine, like mine, like mine
Today is my day and night
That's my girl
We're just like two of us
Let's listen to our calm song
I'll sing a calm song
I honestly just sat on my shoes
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm in the middle of a dream.
I'm sorry.
Why are you crying when you're in the academy?
It's good, but it's sad.
I'm sorry.
The timing wasn't right.
What's in your bag?
I don't have anything in my bag.
What's in my bag today?
Just take a selfie for me today.
I will ask.
The title of the song is
I Left My Heart.
She's waiting for me cause she knows that we need each other
I know we feel shy after no hurry
But that's just how she told me goodbyes
No doubt we were crazy when she's waiting for me
And I wish I could be there tonight
Oh I wish I could be there tonight
I miss the faces and I watch the stories
From strangers that feel just like home
I use the same old one-liners you taught me
While drinking until the bar closed
But now when I go home I'm sleepin' in the desert
I miss the faces and I watch the stories from strangers that feel just like home
What was it?
Not these days
I started watching it today
The one with Lee Seyoung and the one after the love story
That one
I watched it
You were excellent
What would you like to do when you grow up?
I'll slowly learn
I want to use Japanese
To improve
And I want to learn Japanese
Let's watch LUNIVERSE together.
I want to watch it together, but I'm so hungry.
I'm so hungry.
I have to go eat.
Now I'm so hungry.
I have to eat.
V.
Half of it? I want to do it for a long time, but live...
Really...
I think it's the last song.
I found a really good song among Yena's songs.
There's a Yena song called,
It was so good.
Oh, that was love.
Right?
It was so good.
Oh, that's right.
Why did I take my shoes to the basement today?
I think it'll come out.
It was fun.
Oh, should I say it?
The family came out.
It was fun.
It was really hot then, everyone.
I went there when it was really hot.
There's one minute left.
Hyeyeon, it's about time.
Bye, everyone.
Hi.
Bye.
Hey.
Bye, see you at LENIVERSE!
What?