Hello, this is Ahsin.
Guys
please be understanding
I made this video for songchu
I will watch the video
I really like the song BODYS more than SOFT SPOT.
I'm going crazy.
I'm so sorry.
I messed up the melody for that.
This is Keshi.
I'm so sorry.
Is that Keshi?
It's Riri.
Put it in theuras that I shared with you and try it when you go out.
16 garlic ilurs
Let's also taste it.
It was better than I thought a lot of noodles.
Does the visual come off as hard?
If you hide to someone
Go and change their mind
It's all out today, you know
If it's a long waste of time
It's a use to have it all
I have a lot of glasses.
I only bought glasses from Axel.
This feels a little cool.
This is what I've been using at SIS.
This is a real glasses.
There's a number of them, so my eyes are a little smaller.
Oh, look at the dirt.
It's been a while since I've used it.
Wow
I need to organize my glasses.
Among these, I still have the most
I'm going to organize my glasses.
The best
The best glasses for this look right now.
First of all, the song is so good.
I think I need to put it in the oven.
180 degrees for 30 minutes
What I think is the most important thing is
Cooking
We're going to be tight.
I don't think Roon's hand is I'm going to bring it to you.
We were able to say that Re-mon
No, bear too big
This is really good.
Well, today ofRY
Since I made a pretty makeup,
I'm going to do it on my own
I really like that song too
The song is so good
It's so good
Isn't it so good?
What other songs do you think there will be?
Ah!
Wait a minute
Try writing it
It's so funny
This is
I'll show you the guitar
I got it
This is
I can get this
Great
It's a deep-frozen expression.
Do you know this song, everyone?
It's like I'm company.
I can't lose my feet.
He's saying he's gonna win.
Let's get to the pytorch point…
Okay, my guitar is still out of tune, though.
I love this song.
I love ceilings.
Okay, I'm still practicing, so I don't think I can show you like a full cover, but,
Guys, are you curious about the jellyfish song?
Let's see.
Okay.
Should I show you the track first?
Let's see.
And there's another story about jellyfish.
No, yesterday, I gave Eunchae something to give him.
So I went to find Eunchae.
So I was going to give something to Eunchae and come back down.
Suddenly, Eunchae opened this.
Eunchae said he had a hard time with BMA.
So I bought this for him.
I gave him this.
No, that's why it's so...
Isn't it so cute?
But this isn't the end.
You said you still have something to give him.
It's so touching.
I'm going to put it in my bag again.
I was so touched.
Okay.
Then, I have something to do tomorrow.
Look at the time.
It's already 12 o'clock.
Yes.
I'll go.
I'll listen to a song for the last time.
And then I'll go.
Oh, Chae Won's mood light.
What happened?
I saw it.
And then...
That...
Battery?
What are we talking about in Korean?
I can't fingertips.
I still haven't installed it.
are you going to put that up again when you do that, too?
No, when I get it, it's really...
No, I have been moving too much.
That's the only thing that came to my mind.
How can you give me such a sensible gift?
It's the same for Eun Chae.
I mean, that's what I like.
Oh, it's obvious.
It's obvious.
I'm a bit of a transparent person.
But I thought about giving it to you.
I'm so touched.
Really.
It's really my type.
Aha, okay.
Then let's end it with this.
It was a good song, right?
It was a good song.
Is it a song by MCR?
I love it.
Libra season is here.
Oh my God.
I didn't make a congratulatory post about Libra season.
I'm going to have to do that in honor of Libra season
Taemo
And then
This song is about
Yoo Jae Ah sunbaenim's
I'll cover you
Yoo Jae Ah sunbaenim
Yoon Jin Ah, when your parents listen to that song
I'll remember when I was young
Should I turn off the lights?
It's too dark
I'll turn off the light
It's time to put the peace to rest
With this
Should I go to bed?
Jenna girl behind you
Who is it?
Hank?
Isn't it time to sleep? Is it raining?
Is this the sound?
I feel like this is the best
After cars
Weren't you lonely
When you embraced me
Dear, are it memories of Dec trouver
To be given to me
Is it okay to find
Yeah, I'm a fan of V.
switches on
The Ju-en working while pretending to sleep
ihre
Winter's Ghana
She can't even see a stream
We are so different
win-win
I can't
Go
We are come, you are come
The sunset is blooming flowers
Our hearts that are different from each other
I'm trying to make it one
Because it's beautiful
The sun that started the day
The sounds of the rain on the ground
Tell me to be a light
Following the sun
My heart is filled with
My heart is filled with love
Let's go back to where we were
Happy birthday!
Today is your birthday?
I like all five of you
I agree!
You look good on me
Thank you
Happy birthday!
HyunA why
Aren't you going to sleep?
The world is brighter after meeting YunJin?
The color got brighter?
No way, it's the same for me
How is it?
I really like this song
No way, it's the same for me
Until you disappeared
I couldn't even move my steps
What kind of person I was
What kind of pain I had
Now I regret it
After I turned around
I regret it again
Because of someone else
I was faltering
But you protected me
I didn't know why love came
I just opened my ears and cried
My tears flowed to my heart
You hurt me
I pushed you away
Why did love leave
It's turned off?
I'm going crazy
Hey, I shouldn't sing
Ah, I'm going crazy
Really?
Then, before the last song
I'll sing a song
Now, the last song.
I'm going to do one more encore song after the last song.
This is a song I really, really, really cherish.
It's a song that I really, really, really love.
With the love of Wave to Earth.
Please listen to it.
And fill the my poems and earphones.
Here's the standard wrong way.
Please listen to the lyrics.
Listen...
If I put it down
Love will end
Is worth future
It's so good
This ring is so pretty.
If you're watching this, I love you.
Now, the last song.
Jihyo.
It's blue because you're in love
I don't know what to do with you anymore
I don't want to let you go in front of me
To the end of that young dream
And I know it's not the same
Everything changed
It's like I'm trapped in a maze
I'm still looking for something
Don't you feel we all love something
It's a dream, a dream, a room full of scent
I want to open it to everyone
Play with me the more it hurts
Will you tell me something precious?
I'm crazy
I'm crazy for you
Feeling more
I can go crazy
It's blue because you're in love
What's crazier
Than loving more
I can't go crazy
Still beautiful
If I love you like crazy
Someday I'll look back and see
A flower blooming on a thornbush
I love you
I think I did it for a really long time
About an hour and a half?
I'll put you to sleep tomorrow morning
I hope you sleep well
I'll clean up my room, remove my makeup, and wash up
I'll go to bed now
I love you
Bye