(O.O)
Fearnot!
It's not a rehearsal, right?
Oh, here it is!
Hi
Hello
Everyone gather, gather, gather
You didn't expect it, right?
I didn't expect it either
We just came back from
doing the choreography
Right now
So my hair is a little bit like that
All of a sudden?
All of a sudden, it's okay
We'll do the choreography tomorrow
Golden Wave
the day after tomorrow.
Right, right I practiced
Fearnot, what are you doing?
It's Friday afternoon
Hello
Hi
"I'm going home."
Thank you for your hard work
Wait a minute
I wanted to play with Fearnot
since I haven't played it in a while.
What's it?
"How are you?" I'm good.
How are you? Fearnot.
Hi.
Are you all busy right now?
There must be a lot of people
who are going home after work.
Or are you still working?
Every day.
Just living is amazing.
We...
"I'm studying, but I came to see you."
"I came to see you."
No.
Go study!
Oh, right.
I'm going back to Osaka next month.
It's getting a little cold in Japan.
It's been a little cold in Korea lately.
Zuha, These are my bangs.
I have bangs here.
Welcome
"Bangs or no bangs?"
No bangs.
Vacation?
Oh yeah, I...
I went to Paris with my mom.
I really wanted to go,
Originally, I wanted to go to
Italy or somewhere like that.
I wanted to go to a country
that I've never been to before.
I thought about it.
I wanted to go to Paris
for my first vacation.
Croissant Kkurasan
When I was studying abroad,
What was it?
Before the quarantine started,
I had a vacation at a ballet school.
So at that time,
My mom and dad came to the Netherlands.
So I was there for about a week.
I took a train with my parents there.
It was my first trip to Paris.
I have a really good memory of that time.
I wanted to go again.
So this time,
On the last day,
For lunch,
I had to eat.
At that time,
Two years?
Three years?
I went with my mom and dad.
What was it?
What was the name?
Cascade?
It's a type of food.
In the name of that,
That kind of food.
I went there.
I went again.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Well, so,
It's been 3 years since went to Paris.
As a foreign student,
with my parents,
We had dinner together.
But this time,
the situation was changed completely.
I'm eating the same food at the
same restaurant with my mom.
I felt very strange.
I think it's a very
meaningful restaurant for me.
It's moving.
Zuha, when is Leniverse coming out?
Leniverse?
Leniverse is...
You can look forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
Leniverse is really, really amazing.
Really, really.
I think Leniverse knows
loyalty more than loyalty.
Thank you so much.
Thank you and I love you.
There will be a lot of fun contents.
It's always been like that.
More...
I think we'll be able to see a new
side of us
in a more diverse way.
Today's fashion?
Today's fashion is totally comfort.
The theme is comfort.
"The shoe thief."
Right. That...
I was surprised when it suddenly came out.
It came out suddenly.
So, I was surprised, too.
But it turned out well.
I took it like this with the flip-flops.
It turned out well when I took it upright.
It's so funny.
I didn't even imagine it.
I didn't know the
shoe thief would take it.
I really became a thief.
Chaewon.
The other members are on
their separate schedules.
We've been together until now.
"Spoiler?" What spoiler?
Fearnot really likes spoilers.
What kind of spoiler?
The lighting is...
It's working
Another episode.
We took a TikTok together
Please wait for a moment
"Is the monitor the lighting?"
Yes, it is
The monitor...
My PC
The white background is my lighting
It's a white background.
Like this
The blue background...
The blue background is fine.
It's too white.
The white background is too white
The white background is okay
The white background is definitely
It's weakening the reflection
Kazuha, your eyes are so shiny.
Really?
No, really.
I wanna just
So the shot is considerate like this.
As expected, I want to eat something
warm because it's getting a little chilly.
Recommend me ice cream. Ice cream.
Pistachio ice cream.
I ate that last time.
The one at the convenience store.
What was it?
Dubai chocolate.
Dubai chocolate ice cream.
It's sold out these days.
Yunjin unnie told me about it.
It was good when I tried it.
To be honest, I don't really
know what Dubai chocolate is.
My teacher bought it for me and I ate it.
So I tried it.
It was really good.
Dubai chocolate.
Is Dubai chocolate popular in Japan?
Is it popular all over the world?
I'm not sure.
"I really want to eat chestnut tiramisu."
I think it will be really good.
I really respect it.
Is it popular?
Does that mean it's already popular?
Is it already popular?
You've seen it, right?
I want to eat croissant
Unnie please do an impersonation of me
Whose impersonation is it?
"I want to see short hair"
Short hair? I want to try it
I want to try it once.
But if I do it, it will be a little...
How should I say it?
I think it will be a little embarrassing
No
It's not like that
I think my image will change
That's how it is.
Honey, it's not a short hair
It's not a short hair
Fearnot you're so sure.
All right, then.
Honesty.
Is there something in the back?
Ah
Is it that again?
Don't catch a cold
Yes
Fearnot, these days,
The season is changing
Please be careful of cold
My lighting
It's gone
Unnie, what's your height?
I haven't tried it lately
Isn't it 170?
At the beginning of my debut
What
174?
I was surprised
It's not that tall
Is it there or not?
What should I say?
Shouldn't it be 170?
I don't know if it's there or not.
It's hard to say in Korean.
I didn't go to an interview
Is it there or not?
Please
"Are you taller than Eunchae?"
Wouldn't it be similar?
Isn't it similar?
Or maybe Eunchae is a little bigger.
What do I do?
My baby is tall.
"Zuha, be careful of the bread."
Why are you being careful?
"Next time when Eunchae's live is on"
Show... Show...
Comparison
I'll do that.
Eunchae is a tall baby
Eunchae recently
"Did you work out today?"
I did it before coming here,
but it's been a long time since
I've done it, so I'm really tired.
It's really not easy to work out.
I worked out thinking about
soy sauce marinated crab today.
I think I'll probably eat
with the members later.
I just thought about soy sauce
marinated crab and worked out.
You know the hamstring thing?
It's that thing in the back.
The machine that does this.
I was doing that, and it gave me strength.
As expected, the power of appetite.
I recommend you do this.
Think about what you
want to eat and exercise.
That way, it works out well.
"MBTI?"
I'm an INFP.
But I think I'm a bit of a T these days.
Sometimes I feel like a T.
I told Yunjin that.
I said, I think I'm a T these days.
Yunjin said, but Zuha, do you know this?
F means I think I'm T
but T means I don't think I'm F
So you're an F.
That's what she said.
Oh, I see. Then I'm an F.
I guess I'm an F.
I'm thinking about it.
I guess I'm an F from now on.
Jeomhaechu?
Should I say Jeomhaechu?
Fearnot.
I want to eat meat.
What do you want to eat, Fearnot?
I...
Well...
In Busan, Daegu,
I ate makjang and daechang.
It was so good.
I used to like daechang a lot.
Makjang and...
I said daechang.
Not daechang.
Makjang and...
What's makchang?
Makchang and...
No, not that.
What's makchang?
Tell me.
Makchang...
Oh, right.
There's a makchang street in Daegu.
Gopchang, makchang, daechang.
Oh, right.
I ate gopchang and makchang.
It was really good.
It was better than when I
ate it at the restaurant.
To Fearnot,
I recommend gopchang today.
Chipotle
I saw Chipotle in Paris
So...
I was going to go
I wanted to go but I didn't
I wanted to introduce it to my mom
I wanted to introduce it to her
Did you have fun with the zip line?
Shh!
It's still a secret, right?
We know everything
Right, Fearnot, knows everything
Really
Capture time
I don't know any poses these days
What do you think?
Make a heart
Click
Flirting smile
Ribbon heart
The person who thought of
the ribbon heart is amazing.
What did you say?
"It's a pose even if you stay still."
You're cool
"Show me your cheek fat"
Cheek fat
Happy birthday
"Where's all the cheek fat?"
Where did it go?
Okay
I want to play with Fearnot for a while
Wait
I came
It's already been 25 minutes
Really fast
Something comes out at 5 o'clock
Little bit
I don't think it's going to be like that.
So,
I'll go now.
Is it enough?
I'm sure there's something big enough.
Thank you for coming at this time.
See you again.
From tomorrow.
No.
Eat something delicious for dinner.
Bye.
Bye. I'll have something delicious, too.
Bye bye.
I'll be back.
[Please Consider Subscribing]