Wow, this is the last one.
It's the last one.
I don't remember.
What is it?
Let's go.
It's Kira.
Kira! Kira!
Watashi Wa Star!
Hello.
Today is a little...
It's a little...
It's a clear team.
Unnie, what's this?
Did you drink?
It's that kind of time.
What time is it?
It's...
45 minutes.
Why is it 45 minutes?
It's 12 o'clock.
It's late at night.
It's going to be the 28th.
How has our day been?
Eunchae?
I'm going to ask Eunchae this question.
So sad.
Why, why?
Congratulations.
Graduation congratulations.
It was...
Because today.
Because...
Graduation.
I graduated.
From Music Bank.
Oh my god.
Everybody, applause.
Applause.
Thank you.
Well, today,
more people came in than usual.
It was the last time.
Really?
Really.
Why are you misunderstanding?
I'm still...
I don't want to be too sad.
I want to have a happy, happy day today.
I've been holding back my tears.
I've been having a lot of fun.
But Fearnot keeps crying.
But she was holding back her
tears at the end of the speech.
I know.
Really?
Because the signs in front of me
on the paper
They said they love you so much.
They said a lot of things.
I thought I was going to
cry, so I tried not to see it.
I didn't see it until the end.
So I didn't see what it said.
I love you so much.
Thank you.
Fearnot wrote something.
I posted it.
Don't forget.
Eunchae, I love you so much.
Of course I don't forget.
I can't forget these times.
I can't forget.
I'll cherish it in my heart.
When we make a comeback,
I think I'll be happy.
I'm going to make a comeback soon.
When I watched it,
Eunchae looked so happy.
I think I'm having a lot of fun.
I was so proud.
I was so sincere.
Eunchae's teenage years.
That's right.
It's really amazing.
It's really Eunchae's style.
She wrote me a letter.
I read one on my way here today.
Writer
Eunchae's precious teenage last
Thank you for being with
Music Bank for a long time.
There were these words.
Thank you so much.
They're really good people.
Really.
I love you.
Thank you so much.
Everyone was sincere.
Star Diary, too.
Star Diary is on my own.
I was a guest today.
I was alone.
It's so sad.
I thought I was going to cry.
Did you hold it in then?
I held it in.
I cried after I finished.
Star Diary cried after the music video.
You cried after Star Diary.
I cried then, too.
We really didn't know they were coming.
We really didn't know at all.
We were really excited.
We always had expectations.
But we really didn't know.
So
We kept saying that we were sad
because there were no makeup artists.
But we knew they were coming.
So we were like,
it's going to be hard for Eunchae.
No, today
we told them to do well
at the end.
But they couldn't go
because they had to
prepare for the festival.
So the staff couldn't go with them.
The staff who were always with us
couldn't go with me.
So we were like,
it's really sad.
But we were really surprised.
Really.
It was fast, but we couldn't go.
It was a huge success.
Because we couldn't go
in the first class.
I forgot about it in the first class.
We had dinner.
Wow, seriously
your bangs...
You're so short.
It's commanding one step forward.
That's recommended?
That's cool.
I think we'll have to put that part
in our local...
I think what's coming up
will be...
It's the same.
It was really cute.
It's been a year and seven
months, but it's so different.
I was surprised too.
The writers took my waiting room
like the X-Rom of Hwanseungnyeon.
Like X-Rom.
They took all my pictures
and put them on the wall.
In 2023 and 2024, they compared similar
pink clothes and put them on the wall.
It's really different.
It's really big.
You look like Eun Ji-won.
Is the speed too fast?
It's pretty big.
Time is fast.
Isn't the height still growing?
It's grown a lot since then.
And I prepared for the building today.
But the staff couldn't go with me.
So I ordered a cake while
I was in the bathroom.
Really?
They ordered a cake for me.
And I had a ribbon on my
head when I was in WORLD.
I had a cake with the ribbon on my head.
I was so surprised.
I was really surprised.
I got a cake to congratulate my graduation.
It was the best.
So on my way to work today,
I listened to WORLD's 7MEN's songs.
It's a song of memories.
Yes, it's a song of memories.
You did a great job.
Thank you so much.
If you're watching this at home,
please give her a round of applause.
You did a great job.
After finishing the music video,
we went to the university festival.
That's right.
It was really fun.
How was it?
I think it's been a year and
a half since we went there.
I think it's been a year and a half.
There were much more songs than then.
I think there were much
more songs than then.
There were more famous songs.
That's right.
That was so cool.
All the students sang along.
The energy.
College festival is a college festival.
It was so fun.
The weather was perfect.
Oh, today's Gwagidae
festival was so much fun.
Really? Thank you.
Today's Gwagidae festival was the best.
It was fun today, too.
It's been a long time
since we've done Antifragile.
It's been a long time.
We did it during the tour, but we
didn't do it during the fan meeting.
It's definitely a representative song.
There was Gwagidae.
Thank you.
There were a lot of people.
Gwagidae has a lot of people.
And overseas.
Are they foreign students?
There are a lot of foreign students.
I was surprised.
They sang all the songs.
That's right.
They sang it for us.
The first person to come from Seogangdae.
I heard that they waited from 6 a.m. today.
I was so surprised.
Thank you.
Let's go next week.
Right.
There are a lot of festivals planned.
There are a lot.
Seven.
Seven?
We'll go meet a lot of foreign students.
It's our first time to
visit a house in Korea.
It's our first time.
We're doing a fan signing event.
That's right.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've never been to a fan signing event.
It's finally fun.
I think it's going to be fun.
Everyone, don't get sick until that day.
Please wait for us.
I'll take care of my health.
I promise not to get hurt
while enjoying the festival.
That's right.
Keep it real.
Members, too.
That's right.
Stay healthy every day.
Let's have fun memories.
Yes.
Fun memories.
It was so much fun.
It's too late.
Good night.
I woke up.
It's 54.
It's too late.
It won't happen again, right?
Finally, Eunchae.
Well done.
You did a good job.
Thank you.
You worked so hard.
Wow.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
What?
I'll give you a box of these.
How did you get so many colleagues?
You worked hard today.
Thank you.
Rain, too.
Really.
Let's go.
The sleep was good.
Good night.