Hello? Are you there?
Hi.
Hello, hello.
Don't be angry.
Thank you.
Hello.
No.
I dropped my phone.
On my face.
It's night, so I'll be quiet.
I dropped my phone on my face.
This big galaxy.
I'm so bored.
I took a shower and lied down.
I was so bored.
So I turned on the V LIVE.
Samuachi.
In Japanese, samuachi.
They sent it to me.
Good night.
What did you do today?
Today?
I filmed all day.
There was a shoot.
A story about vacation?
I went on vacation.
I went to Naturang with my family.
But they recognized me a lot.
I went on vacation.
Most of the Koreans
were Korean.
They came to travel.
So many people recognized me.
They called me a fan.
I was afraid I'd feel uncomfortable.
When I eat?
They don't pretend to know.
When I was about to leave, she said she was a fan.
So, I was so thankful.
That little consideration.
I was thankful.
I was so happy.
Because she said she was a fan.
And what was it?
I played with the scuba diving and snorkeling like a package.
But until then, I said,
This is overseas.
Because it's overseas, no one will recognize it.
I was so thankful.
I didn't care about anything with her.
If she cut my hair, it would be the worst.
That's what I did.
But there were so many tourists in the boat.
They were calling me.
So I was so flustered.
So I was like,
Please, this is...
This is...
I was so thankful that they recognized it.
But if they took a picture, I wish they didn't upload it.
That's what I thought.
But thankfully, they didn't upload it.
I think when they saw it,
Chaewon said,
I shouldn't upload it for that.
Really...
Please keep it for yourself.
I'm drunk.
I'm drunk because of JinBin.
I'm drunk because of JinBin?
How much did you drink?
You can't drink.
What did you have for dinner?
I think I'm going to get in trouble.
I didn't have dinner.
What's with the sound of the motorcycle?
I left the window open.
Can you hear the motorcycle?
That's amazing.
JinBin, it's whiskey.
There's whiskey and highball.
I thought you were talking about highball.
Whiskey makes you drunk.
How many cans of JinBin can you drink?
I haven't counted it.
But it's so good.
It went in.
It's good. Isn't it really good?
Job satisfaction is the best.
What did you learn in Japanese?
In Japanese...
Japanese...
I learned something today.
I don't know which one is better.
No.
I learned this.
Cute.
Everyone in Japan...
Always...
To me...
It's cute.
Even when we're shooting,
Cute.
The piano is cute.
Thank you.
In Japan...
Is the weather hot right now?
Is it cold?
I...
Soon?
What's soon?
What was it?
I forgot a lot of Japanese.
I...
I'm going to Japan.
Is it cold?
It's cold in Korea too.
Soon.
I'm going to Japan soon.
How is the weather in Japan?
It's cold, right?
I understand.
Isn't the weather so nice right now?
I really like this weather.
It's a cool weather.
It's cold in some ways.
It's hot in some ways.
Is it too cold?
But I...
It's colder in winter.
I think it's perfect right now.
I'm sorry.
I can't read Chinese characters.
Is it warmer than Korea?
It's warmer than Korea.
I'm sorry.
It's warm.
I can't hear you.
What did you say?
I'm sorry.
I can't read Japanese.
What?
Recommend me a late night snack.
What should I recommend?
I love ssambap these days.
Today, at lunch...
Is it lunch or breakfast?
I had ssambap.
But these days,
Ssambap is so good.
You can eat it in one bite.
It's wrapped in ssam.
So it was so delicious.
I want you to sell a lot of ssambap.
There aren't many places to deliver ssambap.
I'm hungry.
I'm not always hungry.
I'm hungry before I go to sleep.
What's wrong with you?
Recommend me a good song to listen to when you study.
When you study, just study.
Don't listen to the song.
Or
Listen to the sound of concentration.
ASMR
Is there a hair color you want to try on?
I want dig placing next time.
I want to try this kind of電그레이.
I want to try this kind of Monthly 24 chest.
Now, maybe I was a little j uses this picture.
How can I grow my hair?
I don't grow my hair just because I want to grow my hair.
That's why I got hair extensions.
But it hurts when I get hair extensions.
Then, P.E.O.N.
Can you wait for me to grow my hair long?
P.E.O.N, you've never done an album promotion with long hair.
Oh, my God. You're right.
Oh, my God. Don't try to fool me.
I suddenly want to do an album promotion with long hair.
I'll wait for you. I really want to do an album promotion with long hair.
I'll wait for you. Really?
I really want to grow my hair long.
But it's going to take a few years.
Short hair is perfect for you.
Wait a minute, P.E.O.N.
Let's unify.
Let's unify. P.E.O.N, let's unify.
Can you wait for me?
Grow your hair first.
Okay.
I want to grow my hair long, too.
Did you fall in love with short hair?
Oh, my God.
Short hair is right.
I'll do anything.
You like everything, P.E.O.N.
Tell me you like everything.
All right.
I'll decide now.
I've heard a lot about P.E.O.N.
I'm going to think about it a lot.
I'll think of a way to satisfy both long and short hair.
Other members?
I think the other members are resting or sleeping in their rooms.
I caught a cold.
I think your voice caught a cold.
I didn't catch a cold.
It's my voice.
P.E.O.N, you scored a goal in Korea.
Congratulations.
What about playing soccer?
Can you speak English for me?
Yes.
Of course.
ASMR?
How is it?
This sound.
My evil sorry.
Man.
My evil...
Yes, it's good.
Me?
Chaewon, do you watch it on Black and White?
I watched it on Black and White.
I watched it all.
But I think you're really amazing.
How can you cook like that?
I mean, it's amazing that you're so good at cooking,
but when I saw the ingredients,
I thought, I should cook this.
I should cook this new dish.
How did you come up with that idea?
I think it's a good idea.
How can I think of cooking something new?
I think you're amazing.
What's your favorite song from Sabrina Carpenter's songs?
Me?
There are so many.
There are so many. What do I do?
Among them...
I can't choose.
Ah, I'm hungry.
Let's make a big spoiler.
Just one.
I'm really sorry, but I don't have anything to spoil.
Ah, wait a minute.
Should I raise the ramen fire?
How about cooking ramen?
Don't do that.
I really don't eat.
If you do, you do.
If you don't, you don't.
It's too late now.
Because tomorrow is a little early.
Did I catch a cold?
Did Chaewon catch a cold?
Why? I didn't catch a cold.
Did I catch a cold?
Why is that?
What is it?
Is my voice weird?
Do you know the number of views when you cook ramen?
Don't say that.
I really don't eat.
My voice is weird?
Oh, my God.
No, because I'm before I go to bed.
No, it's because I don't know your calm voice.
Right?
It's my voice.
I always talk in high tone.
Is that so?
Can you turn on the camera?
I'm sorry.
I'm not ready for my face right now.
Chaewon, can I propose to you if I run into you by chance?
Please do.
Then I think it'll be a really good memory.
Oh, and I really have something on my mind.
Someone recognized me at the airport when I went on a family trip.
Someone recognized me at the airport.
She followed me.
I was walking with my mom and sister.
I was walking with my sister.
She hit me and said,
Are you Kim Chaewon?
I was the first person to recognize her when she started her trip.
I was so embarrassed.
I said, No, I'm sorry.
I went to her.
It's obviously me.
So I want to call her.
Actually, I was Kim Chaewon.
I'm sorry.
I was so surprised.
I lied because I was so surprised.
That's what I thought.
I'm sure she came to me with courage.
I said no, but she just left.
That hurt my heart more.
So I was right.
Please recommend a drama or movie that Chaewon picked.
Do you know the movie, Moonlight?
You're watching it again.
I used to watch it a lot of fun.
The feeling I saw then and the atmosphere.
The content is really fun.
That's right.
It's really fun.
The content is really crazy.
That's really sad, right?
That's right. It's hard because it's sad.
The last one.
It's so much fun.
I'm watching it again.
I fall asleep when I hear your voice.
Is that a good thing?
It's a good thing, right?
Do I have to do this?
Radio or something like that?
No, there's a voice live.
I'll turn on the voice live often.
Let's count sheep.
I don't count sheep.
When I can't sleep.
I don't think there are many times when I can't sleep.
What do I do when I can't sleep?
I read books.
I fall asleep when I read books.
Is it because I keep writing my eyes like this?
Or is it because I fall asleep when I use my cell phone?
Is it because my eyes are tired?
I'm good at sleeping.
Do I fall asleep well even if I drink coffee?
I think I get a lot of sleep.
I don't drink that much coffee.
I'm lying down.
People keep asking me when I'm going to sleep.
I guess I'm sleepy.
I go to sleep when I'm sleepy.
You know you can get a good sleep when you're sleepy, right?
How are you doing these days, Chaeyeon?
You don't like me?
I don't listen to you.
Gemeinsam cool肶
Gemeinsam cool
Have you ever been bitten by Siro?
I've never been bitten by one before.
Chae-won, please tell me the combination of Yo-hwajeong.
I don't know the combination of Yo-hwajeong.
But I like fruit drinks.
Choco shell, choco pop, and fruit drink.
It's delicious no matter how you eat it.
What is Yo-hwajeong?
Oh, my God.
There's someone who's worse than me.
Chae-won, marry me.
Marry me.
What was this song?
I'm suddenly singing this song.
Oh, that's right.
Chae-won, I want to see the dance challenge.
Dance challenge?
Chae-won, do you already know that there are less than 90 days left this year?
No way.
Isn't time too fast?
When did the year go by so fast?
Why are you showing me this?
In 90 days, my sister will become an adult too?
You're right.
Oh, time goes by so fast.
What I felt was that there was a piano that I had seen for a long time among the pianists, and there were pianists who just came in, and they were all so precious and thankful.
It's been about six years since I debuted in the entertainment industry.
So, the piano that I've been watching from the beginning, and the piano that you've been supporting me so far was really amazing.
Thank you so much.
It's been a long time since I've been with all the pianists.
If we stay together for a long time with all the pianists, we're going to fall in love.
It's a big deal if we don't have each other anymore.
I'm going to do it until I'm 50 years old.
Oh, yes.
I'll do my best until I'm 50 years old.
I work out a lot and eat a lot of nutrients, so I'll do it until I'm 50 years old.
I'm 50 years old.
Can you give me a few lessons?
Oh, that was amazing, too.
There's a friend who's been liking me for a long time.
I was a pianist, and he was a pianist, too.
We grew up together, and it was so amazing to find out what kind of job he had and what kind of company he was in.
It was so much fun to hear the stories of each pianist at the company.
Can I look forward to Golden Wave? Please look forward to it.
Shall we go to bed now?
I'll go to bed now.
Oh, no.
Why? No, it's because it's late.
It's just before midnight.
This is like someone's planning, right?
Is it 12 o'clock?
It's late, because it's the next day.
I'm sorry, but it's time to sleep.
It's early, isn't it?
That's right.
It's the earliest time.
Chaeyeon, hurry up.
It's not dinner yet.
It's early in the morning.
You have to wake up and eat.
It's starting now.
Oh, my.
I'm the scariest.
Amechu?
In the morning...
Oh, bagel?
Bagel.
Ssambap.
There's only ssambap on my stomach right now.
London bagel looks delicious.
Lemon.
I don't like bagels.
I don't eat bagels.
Then I eat rice.
You don't really like bread, do you?
Recommend me a friend's taste.
The ginger that came out this time was really good.
But the comments got faster.
I don't like bagels.
What? It's greasy.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Don't get hurt.
I'm kidding.
Then I'll go to bed.
Why?
I'm really early tomorrow.
The person who sleeps from now on is a fool.
Then I'll be a fool.
You did a great job today.
Let's all be fools together.
Let's be fools.
If you sleep now, you'll be happy tomorrow.
If you sleep now, you'll sleep well.
I'm in good condition, so I don't regret it tomorrow.
Bye bye.
See you next time.
I'll really go.
Bye bye.