Hello?
Are you there?
hi
Hi, hi
Oh hi
Hi
I dropped my phone
On my face!
It's night so I should be quiet
I dropped my phone on my face
This big Galaxy
Unnie, I finished my schedule
I washed and lay down
I was so bored
So I turned it on
Samuachi
In Japanese, Samuachi
Good night
"What did you do today?"
Today?
I filmed all day
There was a filming
"A story about vacation?"
I went on vacation
I went to Nha Trang with my family
But they recognized me
Because it was a vacation
And it was a holiday
So most of the Koreans
Most of the Koreans
Most of the Koreans were Koreans
Those who came on a vacation
So many people recognized me
They called me a fan
Because I was uncomfortable
When I was eating
When I was eating?
They didn't pretend to know
At the end, when we got a seat
They said, I'm a fan
And left
So
I was so thankful
That little consideration
I was thankful
I was so happy
Because they called me a fan
And what was it?
I didn't have to show
I thought I was awesome
Didn't become like a big fan
Which is...
Did you think it was a good song?
I think so
Balanced
Because
I didn't have to hide
From my family
I just walked around like that, but there were a lot of tourists in front of me, and they were calling me.
Oh, that's why I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, so, wow. Oh, please, this is...
Oh, this is... Thank you so much for recognizing me, but if you took a picture, I really hope you don't post this.
I thought like this, but they didn't post it. Thank you.
I think when they saw it, they would have said, Oh, I shouldn't post this for Jaewon's sake.
Maybe...
Really...
Yes, please take care of me personally.
"I'm drunk after eating Jinbin. Huh? I'm drunk after eating Jinbin?"
How much did you drink?
You can't drink well.
Okay.
"Chaewon, what did you eat for dinner?"
I really think I'm going to be scolded by Fianna, but I didn't have dinner.
"What's the sound of a motorcycle?"
I just opened the window in my room.
Can you even hear the sound of a motorcycle?
That's amazing.
Jinbin, it's whiskey.
There's whiskey and highball.
I thought you were talking about highball.
Fine.
It's a lot of free beers, so it's perfect.
"Do you think you could hold faded."
I'm thinking about it.
You don't think you should brutally hold it.
I'll press statusisé, so I won't do that voice ciassi.
How about JinBin Market?
How can I know that?
Jinbin Market.
No response so far.
It's okay.
The lastSEV as this %.
Satisfaction is the best
"What did you learn in Japanese?"
Japanese...
I learned something today
I don't know which side of my hair should I put on
No
This side or this side?
So cute
Japanese people always call me kawaii
kawaii
Piana is also kawaii
In Japan, is the weather hot right now?
Is it cold?
I will go to Japan soon
It's cold in Korea too
Soon, soon
Right, right
I will go to Japan soon
Is it cold?
It's cold in Korea too
Soon, soon
I will go to Japan soon
How is the weather in Japan?
I understand
Isn't the weather so nice right now?
I really like this weather
It's a cool weather
In a way, it's cold
In a way, it's a cool weather
"Is it too cold?"
But for me
Winter is colder
I think it's perfect now
Sorry
I can't read Chinese characters
It's warmer than in Korea
Is it warm?
Ah, it's warmer than in Korea.
It doesn't make a sound?
"What did I say?"
I'm sorry.
I have a Japanese piano, so I spoke Japanese.
What?
"Do you recommend me a late-night snack?"
I really like ssambap these days.
I had ssambap for lunch today.
But ssambap came out so well these days.
You can eat it in one bite.
It's a wrap.
So it was so delicious.
I want to sell a lot of ssambap.
Ssambap.
There aren't many places to deliver ssambap.
I'm hungry.
I'm not hungry all the time.
I'm hungry before I go to bed.
What's wrong with you?
"Recommend me a good song to listen to when you study."
Just study when you study.
Don't listen to music.
Or listen to something that focuses well.
I want to do black hair or brown hair instead of bleaching next time.
I just happened to see a picture of me with long hair.
So I want to grow my hair.
How can I grow my hair?
I can't grow my hair because I want to grow it.
That's why I have hair extensions.
But it hurts when I have hair extensions.
I want to grow my long hair with my own hair.
Q. What do you want to do next time?
Can you wait for me for a while?
Can you wait for me?
"Q. Chaewon, have you ever done a long hair album?"
Oh my god.
That's right.
Don't keep seducing me.
I suddenly want to do a long hair album.
I'll wait for you.
Really?
But I really want to grow my hair.
I think it takes a few years.
You look good in short hair.
"You're short too?"
Wait, Piyeon.
Let's be united.
Piyeon, let's be together.
"Okay. I want to grow it, too."
"I'll do anything."
You like everything.
Sorry.
Tell me you like everything.
Okay.
I'll decide now.
I've heard a lot of opinions.
I'm going to think about it a lot.
I'll think of a way to satisfy both long-haired and short-haired people.
What about the other members?
waterproof
Yes.
"I'm going to take care of my makeup with them this year."
Oh, my gosh!
"Chaewon, you scored a goal in Korean!"
Congratulations!
What about soccer?
What do you think of this sound?
Yeah, that's nice.
I've seen it in my previous videos
You've all seen it, right?
But I think you're really amazing.
How can you cook like that?
I mean, it's amazing that you're so good at cooking,
but when you look at the ingredients,
Oh, I'm going to make this dish.
How can you think of making this new dish?
I think you're really, really amazing.
"What's your favorite song among the songs of Sabrina Carpenter?"
Me?
There are so many.
But there are so many.
What should I do?
Among them,
I can't choose.
I'm hungry.
There's nothing wrong with the fire and turn it on.
It's just the fire.
HOLY dressed
I have to make another turn.
"It doesn't matter."
Anyways.
I won't be able to mesmo this story.
If you don't do it, I won't do it.
It's too late now.
No.
Did I catch a cold?
"Did I catch a cold?"
"Why?"
I didn't catch a cold.
Why is that?
Is my voice weird?
"Do you get more views when you cook ramen?"
Don't say that.
I don't eat ramen.
"Oh my god."
No.
"No."
Because it's before I go to bed.
Right?
It's my voice.
I always speak in a high tone.
"Can you turn on the camera?"
I'm sorry.
I'm...
I'm not ready for my face.
But my face is so pretty when it's hot.
"The color is so pretty."
You care terribly when you're hot.
Oh, this is really hot.
So hot.
Is that all?
Oh, is it?
I was walking with my mom and my sister, and they knocked on my door and asked me if I was Kim Chaemon.
I was the first person to recognize him when I started traveling.
I was so embarrassed that I said,
No, I'm sorry.
I went there, and it was me no matter who saw it.
So I want to call him.
Actually, I was Kim Chaewon.
I'm sorry.
I was so surprised that I lied.
It caught my heart.
I'm sure he came with courage.
He just left, and it hurt my heart more.
I was right.
These days, do you know the movie, Moonlight?
You're watching the movie again.
I used to watch it a lot.
The feeling and atmosphere I saw at that time.
The content is really fun.
That's right.
It's really fun.
The content is really crazy.
"It's really sad."
That's right. It's hard because it's sad.
I'm watching it again because it's so fun.
"I can't sleep when I hear my sister's voice."
It's good, right?
What should I do, Ha Eun?
Radio or something like this.
No, it's because I have a voice live.
I'll turn on the voice live often.
I can't sleep.
I'll turn it on for you.
Let's count the sheep, Chae-eun.
I don't count sheep.
When I can't sleep,
I don't think I have a lot of times when I can't sleep.
What do I do when I can't sleep?
"I read books."
When I read books, I can't sleep.
Is it because I keep writing my eyes?
Or I can't sleep when I use my phone.
Is it because my eyes are tired?
Today's
I don't drink coffee that much.
I'm lying down.
You're sleepy, right?
If you're sleepy, let's go to bed.
You know you can sleep well when you're sleepy, right?
Siro?
He doesn't listen to me.
He's a troublemaker.
I've never been bitten by him.
"Chaeyeon, please tell me about the combination of Yoa and Jung."
But I like fruit ring.
I like chocolate pop and chocolate shell.
Fruits ring!
It's delicious even if you eat it.
"What's going on?"
Oh my god.
There's someone who's older than me.
Chaewon, marry me!
Marry me!
What's this song?
I'm suddenly singing this song.
Oh, right.
"Chaewon, I want to see a dance challenge."
Dance challenge?
Chaewon, do you know that there are less than 90 days left this year?
"Chaewon, do you know that there are less than 90 days left this year?"
No way.
Isn't time too fast?
This year...
Then is Eun-chae an adult, too?
Oh my god...
It really is
Oh time is super fast
What I felt was...
Among the Pianas,
there are Pianas that I've seen for a long time,
and there are Pianas that just came in.
They're all so precious and thankful.
It's been six years since I debuted in the entertainment industry.
That's how long it's been.
So, from the beginning,
I've seen...
I've seen so many Pianas that have been supporting me.
And the Pianas who have been supporting us
until now...
It was really amazing.
It was amazing.
Thank you so much.
It's good, right?
If we stay together for a long time,
We're awesome.
If we don't have each other,
"Chaewon, you have to do it until you're in your 50s."
Oh, yes.
50s...
50 years old.
I work out a lot.
I take good care of my nutrients.
Until I'm in my 50s.
I'll do my best until I'm in my 50s.
Can I dance to Fearless again?
That was interesting.
Because maybe you it was interesting after having done it for a long time.
Should I go to bed now?
"Oh, my."
Oh, my.
It's 12 o'clock.
And it is next day.
Wow, that's right. It's early.
Chaeyeon, hurry up and eat that cabbage.
It's not dinner yet. What kind of cabbage is it?
It's early in the morning.
It's just the beginning.
Amechu?
Bagel.
Ssambap.
I can only have ssambap on my stomach right now.
London bagel looks good.
Nemo Nemo. Nemo Nemo.
"I don't like bagels."
Don't eat bagels. Then eat rice.
You don't really like bread.
"Recommend me the steamed bean paste flavor."
The comments are going faster.
"What? It's greasy."
Thank you, Vianna.
Don't get hurt.
I'm sorry.
I'm kidding.
Then I'll go to bed now.
Why?
I'm really early tomorrow.
"From now on, the person who sleeps is a fool."
Then I'll be a fool.
Let's all be fools together.
Let's be fools.
Vianna, you know what?
If you sleep now, you'll be happy tomorrow.
You have to sleep now to sleep well and have a good condition.
I have no regrets tomorrow.
Bye bye.
Bye.
Good night.
Bye bye.
Bye.