hi
it's me
Hi.
Hurry up and come in.
Delicious.
I should play a song.
What should I play?
How do I do this?
Wait
This is not my ID
I'll change it to my ID
Hello
"Siwoo is so cute"
So cute
As soon as I saw the shoes
I was shocked because they were so cute
Crocs are this small
So Siwoo can wear them
What was the password?
I did it
Okay
What is this face?
Please do this face
Is it 3 a.m. in America?
Oh my god
3 a.m.?
Isn't it too late?
LUNIVERSE will be released at 8pm, so I'll turn it off before that because I have to focus on LUNIVERSE.
It's not black hair. I just toned it down, but it looks like black hair.
It's a little bit like an old-fashioned color.
My hair doesn't tie. Look at this.
What should I do? When will it grow?
"Are you here because you're bored again today?"
Yes, that's right.
Thank you.
Wait a minute. I want to tie my hair, but my hair doesn't come out like this.
I'll force you to tie it up.
The first
I'll cut the wood.
Do you want to die?
How do you cut it?
Like this?
You know what a summer rock is, right?
Oh, but because of this.
When you tie it up like this,
You know that taste, right?
Like this.
Do you know what this is?
Oh! I like it.
I like it!
I'll do it like this.
It's my favorite jelly these days.
It's really crazy. It's so delicious.
Do I have to cover it?
It's a live video, so there's a clapping sound.
Can you hear the piano?
Hello.
This is really good.
There's a more delicious jelly left after the lizard jelly.
It's really good.
Is it just right?
Okay, I've got a good feeling now.
I feel good.
"Show me your mind."
My outfit today.
Ta-da.
Just like this.
It's time to get dressed, everyone.
I have to wear like this.
For this fall.
I bought this jacket.
How is it? Isn't it pretty?
Like this
I can't see my face
My posture
was my effort
I wanted to show it to you
The person who plays the song
is not playing the song
If you suddenly introduce the clothes
Seyeon
I'll play my playlist
"If you freeze it, it's more delicious."
What are you doing?
This jelly?
This?
You're going to freeze it?
Then how do you chew it?
"What kind of schedule did you have today?"
Today...
You know I can't tell you.
Just take a pretty picture.
I went straight to Music Book and did Live.
This is the first time I've seen this kind of music video in a long time, so I'm looking forward to it.
Looking at the music video, you're looking at the music video instead of me?
"I really like band songs."
Don't you think you know what I mean?
When I recommend a song,
I recommend that kind of song.
I really like it.
I want to try it someday.
It's getting cut off?
Oh my.
Why is it getting cut off?
Is it because it's underground?
"Do I get a request?" Yes, I do.
I totally get it.
I really like the song.
I really like it.
I'm so hungry.
Let's think together.
What should we eat for dinner?
Next song.
Spicy which makes my stomach'll unusual panic.
Spicy with a familiar odor.
I really like it.
I want to eat soup and such.
But the time ring still becomes 8 p. m.
it's the right moment.
I fell in love again
As boring as it gets
It rained all day before
You were filled up to the end
The night when I was out of breath
The words that hold my heart
Deeper and deeper
Oh I'm down and it's raining on
Take it, I can't breathe
Take it, I'm down and it's raining on
Do you want to listen to our song?
Miss Lafim's
1-800-HOT-AND-FUN
I really like this song
It's my song but I love it
1-800-HOT-AND-FUN
2-800-HOT-AND-FUN
Drop it, drop it back
Louis V background
My night view, yeah
Cause I'm so classy
I still break it down though
I bet you can get past me
Hot place, we angel
I'm so cute, I'm so nerdy, so sassy
Oh shit, oh my god
DJ play my favorite song
Raise the roof, let the dogs
I play something by Beyonce
I'm not trying to leave until they kick us to the road
It's a flat scene and a spin-tune of Kimchi-jjim
I like to dance and I party
I like to kiss everybody
Where the heck is Saki?
She's waiting down in the lobby
I'm trying to break it down, yeah baby
Get it, get it, get it, get it
Turn up the party
I like to dance and I party
But I've never been to a party
I like to kiss everybody
Actually, I had kissing people
I learned this
I can tell you baby
Get it, turn up the party
1-800-HOT & FINE
That's my number, hit my line
Feel my rhythm every time
1-800-HOT & FINE
I really like this hair tied up so roughly, Gaeun
You'll see what this is
If you tie it up again, it won't get tied?
Lift it up, dog
Say something by Beyonce
I'm not trying to leave until they kick us to the road
But it doesn't matter, it's cool, it's cool, it's cool, I'm flyin' like the wind in my pants
But it doesn't matter, it's cool, it's cool, it's cool, it's cool, I'm flyin' like the wind in my pants
They do what's cool, don't get it, never see my phone
I like to dance with a party
I like to kiss everybody
Where the heck is Saki?
She's waiting down in the lobby
I'm trying to break it down, yeah baby
Get it, turn up the party
I like to dance with a party
I like to kiss everybody
Where the heck is Saki?
She's waiting down in the lobby
No, we have a little bit left.
Baby, get it, turn up the party
Bagel and cream cheese looks good.
Oh my gosh.
Let's just do it cause it's fun
I'm running around with my focus tied up
After the same day
They say whoa whoa, I'll bite it later and work
I want to wake up in my quiet heart
Good girl, I'll be a doll
So be town man, like a balloon
Slowly blow it up, make it pop
Pop pop pop, I'm ready to run, where my girls
So where my, where my girls?
Pure heart
I like Udon
But I'm so hungry right now
I want to recommend something that's good for all of us
That's my girl
Let's listen to a gentle piece
Rude song
She like it
Just out of my shoes
I'll show you how it's done
Why are you crying when you're at the academy?
I'm sad because I'm happy
Sorry
The timing wasn't right
In the bag? I don't have anything in my bag
I really don't have anything in my bag today
Seoeon, please take a selfie today
Okay
The title of the song is
I left my heart
Show me your nails
I don't have any nails
I'm embarrassed
I can't see anything.
I don't like this place.
I think there's a lot of cute things here.
I'm watching that show.
What was it?
Not these days.
I started watching it today.
There's a song called...
I saw Lee Seyoung with her in the new film
I saw her 꽂아왔어요
I want to learn Japanese one day
I want to become good at Japanese and master it.
Let's watch LUNIVERSE together.
I want to watch it together, but I'm so hungry.
I'm so hungry.
I have to go eat.
I want to eat.
V is so nice.
There are still three minutes left.
There are only three minutes left?
No way.
Time flies so fast.
I'm pretty right now.
I want to do it for a long time.
Live.
Really.
The last song.
I think it's the last song.
I found a really good song among Yena's songs.
There's a song in Yena's album called Love.
It was so good.
Oh, that was love.
Love.
When did this come out?
That was a nice challenge.
The last song.
Oh, this is the last song.
Oh, that was nice.
Love.
Love it!
This is the last song.
Iyan's the youngest.
It's just been holding me for a while.
I'll change that.
Is your heart berated?
So then...
I know.
I'm so emotional.
I think it'll come out.
It was fun.
Oh, I can't say it.
Kim Millie came out.
It was fun.
It was really hot then.
I went there when it was really hot.
It was really hot.
Hyeyeon, it's about time.
Let's watch the mini-verse now.
There's only one minute left.
Bye.
See you in the mini-verse.
What?
You have to watch it.