Hi
It's Yunjin
It's going well, right?
What's up
I'm in my room
It's not a perm
I have a shoot today
I have a shoot
I took off my hair
A perm?
I had my hair curled
That's right, I had a shoot today
What's up
Where are you this late?
I'm at home
I'm at the dorm
Do you have time?
Yes, I have time
Time is
Like this
I always come when I have time
What shoot do I have today?
Today
I washed my hair
To my house
I'm coming
Did you do your hair?
Yes
How do you feel?
Everybody
Ye turtle
You have asta hair
Yes
It's good
Fantastic
Yes
Do I play any games? I
unfortunately don't play any games.
Can you introduce me to
one of the books in the back?
Okay.
Hold on a second.
Let me see.
Hmm.
Yeah.
What's up?
Oh, what did I think of the UK?
It was so great. I had such a good time.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
The Book Thief.
I've talked about this book a lot, but
I think it's actually
like a modern
book that will become
a classic,
I think.
It's very, very good.
It talks about...
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, there's so much
mungy.
Yeah.
It's about
the power of
like reading and books
and imagination in
really harrowing times
because it's, you know,
based off of a real historical event.
How many books are in that book tower?
I don't know.
It's six movies.
Thank you.
You know,
I think so.
It's cool.
This.
And it's,
I don't know.
There's a lot of like
generational stuff which
is something that feels
really familiar to me.
Like immigrants.
Buy a bookshelf? I do have a
bookshelf but that's already stacked.
What's the most recent
Japanese word I remember?
Giri giri (just barely)
But what if it falls over?
It won't fall over.
Because it's a steel bookshelf.
It's not just like this.
It's vertical.
How do you say it?
It's like lying down.
Hair? I didn't dye my hair but
Fiona kept telling me that I dyed my hair.
I think I get a lot of light.
I didn't dye my hair.
I think it's the same blue.
It's the same blue but if
it's dark it looks like black.
How was Swiss?
Switzerland
Oh my god.
Switzerland was so beautiful
We were really
Since I became a trainee, for
the first time in a long time, I spent
time with my family, and it was
really, really,
really, really good.
It was so good.
What do you drink? I drink Yonana.
(banana yogurt??)
I shouldn't
drink coffee at this time
but I drank it because I love it
so good
But I still sleep well. Don't worry.
But don't drink coffee at a late
time, especially when you're young.
Do you understand?
Drink decaffeinated coffee.
It's a little hard to order again.
Do I sleep well? I
think I sleep fairly well.
Do I miss Rachel? Yes,
I miss Rachel so much.
What is my coffee order?
Just an iced Americano.
Black. I like black coffee.
Make a heart?
What country do you want
to go to after Switzerland?
There are so many
countries I want to go to,
so I think I need to
write a bucket list.
There are so many.
Anywhere. Any new country.
Any new city. Anywhere. I love everything.
London was really good too.
Fish and chips are good.
And a lot of curry as well. I love curry.
I love curry so much.
Can you do a heart?
Oh, so comfortable. Thank you.
Because you are here
while I'm eating. I love you.
Aww.
Yeah, everybody, I hope you can
get a good snack while you watch.
Favorite topping on pizza?
Broccoli and ricotta cheese.
Or...
I don't know. I like, I like me
a white pizza with broccoli.
Or, like, greens and, um, I don't
know, cheese. Like, ricotta cheese.
And also, I just like a margarita. Like,
basil, basil leaves. That's really good too.
Have you read The Seven
Husbands of Evelyn Hugo?
I have not, but Rachel is obsessed with
that book. She, it's her favorite book.
So, hopefully one day I will.
"Broccoli" Yall are hating on broccoli?
Ricotta does go crazy on pizza.
It goes what?
Can I eat the jjapaghetti on Yunjin's head?
It's blue. Would you be okay with that?
Ribbons.
It's dessert.
The Girl With the Dragon Tattoo is good?
My mom used to have that book
back at home
How does it feel to perform
at a festival after a long time?
Really really really fun.
Seriously...
I kept talking to the members
and they said it was really fun.
It was really really fun.
It was really fun and...
Really...
The energy and the heat
were no joke.
Really...
For me, when I watch a performance
or when I perform,
everyone in that space feels liberated
and really...
become one mind, one body
just...
Forget about that moment
and just enjoy everything.
That's how I feel.
It's like...
Everyone enjoyed it so much
so it was really...
good and if we could give
a little bit of good energy,
I don't think there's
anything better than that.
Really really...
I'm looking forward to it in the future
and I'll do my best.
Ah! I'll look forward
to the Hoseo Festival!
I'll look forward to it!
I'll definitely...
go and see it!
The college entrance exam!
There's 47 days left, nuna.
Fighting!
Fighting fighting! Fighting!
Fighting for the college entrance exam!
I also...
The US...
college entrance exam?
A few years ago...
I really...
prepared for it.
But it was really...
really hard.
Studying all day long...
oh...
Really, the stress...
I tried to control it as much as I could
but...
I remember studying with a lot of stress
because it was so intense.
Really, all the students...
really...
I sincerely support you.
You're really amazing.
Being able to do something so passionately
is really really amazing
and cool.
So...
Have pride.
Don't get too stressed...
Fighting!
You can do it.
I'm still not...
Do you think pineapple belongs to pizza?
I don't know.
Do you think I belong...
Wait, no.
I was trying to say
do you think I belong on the syrup
but that would mean
I think pineapple belongs on pizza.
Yeah. The answer is no I don't think
it belongs to pizza.
Would you like to come to Italy?
Yes, I would love to go to Italy.
Yunjin are you in London?
No! I'm not in London! I'm in... Seoul!
Yongsan actually
Do I like Daniel Ceaser?
Yes, of course!
Have you ever been to Texas?
I have not.
Ah! Oh, Yunjin, did you eat pho? I
actually just had pho with Chaewon
and Zuha.
Put some decorations up on my room?
This is actually the plainest
part of my room.
Like, my room is actually a mess. I
cannot show you anything more.
Like, this is, it's such a bad,
it's in such a bad state right now.
My ukulele's here, and like...
Oh, it's still fairly in tune.
Oh, there's my guitar.
Yeah.
Sounds like my morning
alarm. Yeah, that is true.
Double take.
In the midst of the crowds
In the shapes in the clouds
I don't see nobody but you
Also, this book.
(red helicopter)
I forgot, I brought it over
just to show you guys.
This book is so good.
I've mentioned it a few times, but...
It's so good.
Very relatable.
Do I play Minecraft? I
used to play Minecraft.
But like the mobile version.
This is not a real plant.
Have you tried using Kaymak?
Kaymak?
Have I ever tried Kaymak? Kaymak?
I have. It's very good.
It's very good.
I had it with Zuha.
Girl, buy a bookshelf. Those
books are gonna tip over.
That is a bookshelf.
It's a bookshelf, but like, it's just where
you have the books, like, sideways.
So there's like a shelf there.
You just can't see it because
it's between the books.
I'm so scared of
long-term flights. It's tiring.
What are you
doing in a plane, Yoonjin?
Uh, me? I...
I either sleep.
I usually sleep.
I either sleep or...
I don't know.
I think I listen to music a lot while
reading books or listening to music.
Do I have a name for
my guitar and my ukelele?
I used to, you know I actually
did! I used to, but I don't remember.
I think I listen to music a lot while
reading books or listening to music.
JenJen mwah hyejong
mwah
Guys, we should listen to some music
or like do something fun. Gimme a sec.
Oh, everyone, look at the black and white
cook these days.
It's so much fun.
It's so cool.
Almost all the people who appear
on the show are really, really cool.
Totally respect.
What song should I listen to?
Then...
Everyone, do you have a song request?
Have I tried kompokoki yet?
Yes, I did. I had some with Rachel.
Last time, we were in the States.
Oh my god
Have you listened to this song before?
Okay
it's a song that I'm... like
currently obsessed with
It's so good.
It's Orion Sun's.
Already Gone
I really love this song.
It's so cool.
Oh, her hair looks mysterious.
Oh well I did like science in high school
I wonder if she doesn't
use these fun glasses.
I bought this plate at a vintage shop.
Glasses! Glasses!
What should I say?
I'm using this as a display.
I'm going to turn the BGM
down and listen to some music.
What should I listen to?
Already gone
Glasses!
Now what should I say?
What should I say?
Try On?
I'll give it a shot.
This song is so...
it's Hailey Knox Eleventh Hour
It's Hailey Knox... Knox? Knox?
It's Knox.
I'm obsessed with her.
First glasses.
These are the glasses.
[Stream began to lag here]
I have glasses like this.
I think I wore this once when I danced.
Chaewon wears this often.
This one, too.
I think I wore this in America.
By any chance...
Is the video not good?
Is the picture not good?
Is it done?
Is it okay?
Is it okay now?
I think it's okay.
I can't see it?
The picture quality?
I'll turn it back on.
Hold on. Hang on.
Are you okay?
Okay.
Here we go again, okay.
This is...
These are glasses that
I've never worn outside.
Okay, wait.
This is a good part.
This too.
These are my glasses.
This is so cool,
but it hurts when I wear it.
Because I can't see it well.
There's a delay.
I'm going crazy.
The sync doesn't work
because I'm going crazy?
The sync doesn't work?
What's going on?
Really?
Hold on.
I'm going crazy.
The place you can go.
Really?
No.
No?
Is it cut?
Oh, my God.
Really?
Can't you hear the sound?
What's wrong with you?
I can't even put it in color.
Okay. End.
Ah!
Is this some kind of punishment?
Everyone
please be understanding
It's a livestream
I will check the video later
there is a bug in the livestream.
Let's not worry about
it too much. It's a bug.
Keshi
Bodies
아민 처 버린다
(?) Oh, seriously, toss it!
Sorry
I messed up the melody for that.
This is Keshi.
These are my lenses.
goodbye, I really don't know
Accessories like glasses, besides
buying glasses, this has that flavor.
This is what I've been using.
This is a real glasses.
There's a number of them,
so my eyes are a little smaller.
Oh, look at the dirt.
It's been a while since I've used it.
Wow
I need to organize my glasses.
Among these, I still have the most
I'm going to organize my glasses.
The best glasses for this look right now.
First of all, the song is so good.
I think I need to put it in the oven.
180 degrees for 30 minutes
What I think is the most important thing is
Cooking
We're going to be tight.
pretty good at that
no, it's really kinda
the taste is very rich
Well, today
Since I made a pretty makeup,
I'm going to do it on my own
cool sound
I really like it
Isn't it so good?
It's called see through
by Amelia Moore
What other songs do
you think there will be?
Ah!
Wait a minute
Try writing it
this...
I'll show you the guitar
it's difficult
Do you know this song, everyone?
Okay, my guitar is
still out of tune, though.
I love ceilings.
Okay, I'm still practicing, so I don't
think I can show you like a full cover,
but,
Guys, are you curious
about the jellyfish song?
Let's see.
Should I show you the track first?
And there's another story about jellyfish.
No, yesterday, I gave
Eunchae something
gave her something.
I went to find Eunchae.
So I was going to give something
to Eunchae and come back down.
Suddenly, Eunchae opened this.
Eunchae said he had a hard time with VMA.
So I bought this for him.
I gave her this.
No, that's why it's so...
Isn't it so cute?
But this isn't the end.
You said you still have
something to give her.
It's so touching.
I'm going to put it in my bag again.
I was so touched.
Okay.
Then, I have something to do tomorrow.
Look at the time.
It's already 12 o'clock.
Yes.
I'll go.
I'll listen to a song for the last time.
And then I'll go.
Oh, Chaewon's mood light.
What happened?
I saw it.
And then...
That...
Battery?
What are we talking about in Korean?
I can't fingertips.
I still haven't installed it.
Are you going to put that up
again when you do that, too?
No, when I get it, it's really...
No, I have been moving too much.
That's the only thing that came to my mind.
How can you give me such a sensible gift?
It's the same for Eunchae.
I mean, that's what I like.
Oh, it's obvious.
It's obvious.
I'm a bit of a transparent person.
But I thought about giving it to you.
I'm so touched.
Really.
It's really my type.
Aha, okay.
Then let's end it with this.
It was a good song, right?
Play a song by MCR?
I would love to.
Libra season is here.
Oh my God.
I didn't make a congratulatory
post about Libra season.
I'm going to have to do
that in honor of Libra season
Te amo
And then
This song is about
Yoo Jae Ha sunbaenim's
Milestone
Yunjin ah, when your parents listen to
that song I'll remember when I was young
Should I turn off the lights?
It's too dark
I'll turn off the light
It's time to put the Fearnot to rest
Jen a girl behind you?
Who is it?
Hank?
Isn't it time to sleep? Fearnot?
Is this the sound?
I feel like this is the best
Happy birthday!
Today is your birthday?
Lesserafim Two!
하 성면 파 쳐
(?) Let's face against the tide.
I agree!
You look good on me?
Thank you
Happy birthday!
Fearnot why...
Aren't you going to sleep?
The world is brighter after meeting YunJin?
The color got brighter?
No way, it's the same for me
How is it?
I really like this song
It's turned off?
I'm going crazy
Hey, I shouldn't sing
Ah, I'm going crazy
Really?
Ah, I'm going crazy Really?
Then, before the last song
I'll sing a song
Now, the last song.
I'm going to do one more
encore song after the last
song. This is a song I
really, really, really cherish.
Seriously.
I sincerely love Wave to Earth.
Please listen to it.
Wave to Earth
Love
It's so good
This ring is so pretty.
Wave to Earth, if you're
watching this, I love you.
Now, the last song.
I love you
I think I did it for a really long time
About an hour and a half?
I'll put you to sleep tomorrow morning
I hope you sleep well
I'll clean up my room, remove
my makeup, and wash up
I'll go to bed now I love you
Bye