Mm-Hmm...
Hello?
Are you there?
Hi. Hello hello.
Hello
Good evening
Hi
No...
Aigo! Aigo!
I dropped my phone
On my face!
It's night, so I should be quiet
I dropped my phone on my face
This big Galaxy
I finished my schedule
I washed up and laid down
I was so seriously bored
So I turned Live on
Samuachi
In Japanese, Samuachi
Please send it
Good night
"What did you do today?"
Today?
I filmed all day
There was a filming
"A story about vacation?"
I went on vacation
I went to Nha Trang with my family
But Fearnot recognized me
Because it's a resort
And it was a holiday
So most of the Koreans
There were a lot of people,
mostly Koreans.
Those who also came on vacation
So, many people knew about me
They call me a fan
I was worried that I'd be uncomfortable
When was it? While I was eating?
They pretended not to recognize me,
but when we were leaving at the end,
They said, "I'm your fan!"
And simply left.
So
I was so thankful
That little consideration
I was thankful
I felt so happy
You said you're a fan.
And what was it?
Scubadiving and
Snorkeling and a lot of
Other water packages.
But I can't bear it
But up until then,
I figured no one would
recognize me since I'm overseas.
I didn't care about anything with her
You know that it's really the
worst if your hair is all wet, right?
I just walked around like that,
But there were a lot of
tourists in front of me,
and they were calling me.
I must have been so flustered.
Oh, so, "Wow. Oh, please!
This is, oh, this is."
"Thank you so much for recognizing me,"
"but if you took a photo,
I really hope you don't post this."
That's what I thought,
but they didn't post it.
Thank you.
I think when they saw it too,
"Oh, this is Chaewon."
"I don't think I should post
this for Chaewon's sake."
Really...
Please just keep it.
"I'm drunk after drinking Jim Beam."
Huh? "I'm drunk after drinking Jim Beam?"
How much did you drink?
You can't drink well.
"Chaewon, what did you eat for dinner?"
I really think I'm going
to be scolded by Fearnot,
but I didn't have dinner.
"What's with the sound of the motorcycle?"
I just opened the window in my room.
Can you hear the sound of a motorcycle?
That's amazing.
Jim Beam, it's whiskey.
Oh, there's whiskey and highball.
I thought you were talking about highball.
It's good to drink whiskey.
"How many cans of Jim Beam can you drink?"
I haven't counted it,
but it's so delicious
that it's easy to drink.
It's delicious.
Isn't it really delicious?
I'm really satisfied with my job.
The best.
"What did you learn in Japanese?"
Oh yeah... Japanese?
Japanese?
There's something I learned today
[JP] I don't know which
side of my hair is better
Ah, no
[JP] I don't know which
side of my hair is better
I learned that.
[JP] This side or this side?
[JP] Yes
[JP] So cute
[JP] Japanese people always call me cute
[JP] Even when I'm shooting
[JP] Cute
[JP] Fearnot is also cute
[JP] Thank you
[JP] Is the weather
hot in Japan right now?
[JP] Is it cold?
[JP] I'm...
[JP] I'm going to Japan soon
What's it?
What should I do?
I forgot a lot of Japanese
[JP] I'm going to Japan soon
[JP] Is it cold?
[JP] It's cold in Korea too
[JP] Soon, soon
Ah, right, right
[JP] I'm going to Japan soon
[JP] What's the weather like in Japan?
[JP] Ah, it's cold, right?
[JP] I understand.
But isn't the weather so nice right now?
I really like this weather
It's a cool weather
Well
In a way, it's cold
In a way, it's hot
Hot weather
"Is it too cold?"
But for me
Winter is colder
I think it's perfect now
Sorry, I can't read Chinese characters
[JP] "It's warmer than in Korea"
Is it warm?
Oh, it's warmer than Korea.
It doesn't make a sound.
[KR] "What did you just say?"
I'm sorry.
I'm speaking Japanese
because I have Japanese Fearnot.
Wat?
"Do you recommend me a late night snack?"
What would be good?
I really like ssambap these days.
Is it lunch or breakfast?
But ssambap is so good these days.
Delivery.
You can eat it in one bite.
It's a wrap.
So it was so delicious.
I hope they sell a lot of ssambap.
Ssambap.
There aren't that many
places that deliver it.
I'm hungry.
I'm not hungry all the time.
Before I go to bed,
I'm hungry.
What's wrong with you?
"Recommend me a good song
to listen to when you study."
When you study, just study.
Don't listen to music.
Or listen to something that focuses well.
What do you think?
ASMR
"Chaewon, what hair color
do you want to do next time?"
I want to do something calm next time.
I don't want to bleach my hair.
I want to dye my hair black or brown.
I just happened to see a
picture of me with long hair.
So I want to grow my hair.
No, but how can I grow my hair?
I can't grow my hair just
by wanting to grow hair.
That's why I have hair extensions.
But it hurts when I have hair extensions.
It's uncomfortable.
Then, Fearnot.
Can you really wait for me
while I grow my hair out?
Can you wait for me for a while?
Can you wait for me?
"Chaewon, you've never
done an album with long hair."
omg.
Actually true.
What to do? I suddenly want long hair.
I want to grow my hair long.
"I'll wait for you."
Really?
But I really want to grow my hair,
Fearnot.
But it will take a few years.
"You look good with short hair.
Do you have short hair, too?"
Wait a minute, Fearnot.
Let's unify.
Let's unify. Fearnot, let's unify.
Can you wait?
"Grow it first."
Okay.
I want to grow it, too.
Did you fall in love with short hair?
Oh, my.
I do have short hair, though...
"I'll do anything."
You like everything, Fearnot.
Huh?
Tell me you like everything.
Okay.
I'll decide now.
Fearnot,
I've heard a lot of people's opinions.
I'm going to think about it a lot.
I'll think of a way to satisfy
both long-haired and short-haired people.
"What about the other members?"
Wouldn't they be resting
or sleeping in their rooms?
"You caught a cold.
I think your voice is sick."
I didn't catch a cold.
It's my voice.
"Chaewon, you scored a goal in Korean!"
Wow.
Congratulations.
What about soccer?
Can you speak English for me?
Yes!
Of course!
ASMR?
How is it?
This sound?
My evil sorry
Man
Evil
Yes it's good
- "Chaewon, did you see
Culinary Class Wars?"
- I watched all of it.
All of it.
However, I think their
cooking skill is extraordinary.
How made they cook like that?
I mean,
Their cooking skill is
really extraordinary.
When I saw it, I thought,
I have to do this dish,
I have to do this new dish.
I think they're really, really amazing.
"What's your favorite
Sabrina Carpenter song?"
Me? There are so many.
But there are so many. What should I do?
Among them...
I can't choose.
I'm hungry.
Let's give a big spoiler
One.
I'm really sorry,
but there's nothing to spoil
"Wait, should I put some ramen?
How about ramen cooking?"
No, don't.
Don't eat it.
If you don't do it, I won't do it.
No, I won't.
It's too late now.
But it's too late.
Because tomorrow will be early.
"Did you catch a cold?"
"Chaewon said, did I catch a cold?"
Did I catch a cold?
Why?
I didn't catch a cold.
Did I catch a cold?
What's wrong with me?
Is my voice weird?
"Will the views go up if you cook ramen?"
Don't say things like that.
I really won't eat ramen.
"My voice is weird?"
Oh my god.
No, because I'm...
Because it's just before bed.
"No, it's because I don't
know your calm voice."
Right?
It's my voice.
I always...
Something...
Is it because I'm talking in a high tone?
"Can you turn on the camera?"
I'm sorry.
I'm not ready to show my face right now.
"Chaewon, can I say hello
if I run into you by chance?"
Please do it.
Then I think it will be
a really good memory.
Ah, right now, there's
something that's really on my mind.
When I was on that family trip,
someone recognized me at the airport
I was walking with my sister.
He tapped me and said, "Kim Chaewon".
I...
He was the first person
who recognized me when I arrived.
I was so flustered that I said,
"No! I'm sorry!"
I went there, and it was definitely me.
So I want to tell him
Actually, I was Kim Chaewon
I'm sorry.
I was so surprised that I lied.
That's what I thought.
I'm sure he came with courage.
When I said no, he just left.
That hurt me even more.
So...
I was hit. I'm sorry.
"Chaewon recommend a drama to watch."
I like "Lover of the Moon" these days.
I'm watching it again.
I used to watch it a lot.
So I will.
But the vibe that I saw then,
The feeling and the atmosphere,
And the content is really fun.
That's right.
It's really fun.
The story is crazy.
- "It's really sad, isn't it?"
- That's right. It's
hard because it's sad.
The last one.
It's so much fun that I'm rewatching it.
"I fall asleep when I hear your voice."
Is it a good thing?
That's a good thing, right?
Do I have to do something like this?
Radio, content like this?
No, there's a voice live.
I'll turn on the voice live often.
"Chaewon, let's count the sheep."
I don't count sheep.
When I can't sleep.
When I can't sleep,
I don't think I have a lot
of times when I can't sleep.
What do I do when I can't sleep?
"I read a book."
If I read a book, I can't sleep.
Is it because I keep
using my eyes like this?
Or when I use my cell phone,
I can't sleep.
Is it because my eyes are tired?
"Do you sleep well even after coffee?"
I think I sleep well
even if I drink coffee.
I don't drink that much coffee.
I'm lying down.
Are you sleepy now everyone?
If you're sleepy, go to bed Fearnot.
If you're sleepy, go to bed.
To have a good night's sleep,
You know you can sleep
well when you're sleepy, right?
Chaewon, how is Siro these days?
Siro?
He doesn't listen to me.
He's a troublemaker.
"Have you ever been bitten by Siro?"
I've never been bitten by Siro.
"Chaewon, please tell me the
combination of Yoa and Jung."
I don't know the
combination of Yoa and Jung.
I don't know that combination well,
actually.
But I like fruit rings.
Choco shell, choco pop, and fruit ring.
It's delicious if you eat it.
- "What's going on?"
- Eh?
Oh my god.
There's someone who's older than me.
Chaewon, marry me.
Marry me~
Marry me.
I'm singing this song all of a sudden.
Ah, that's right.
"Chaewon,
I want to see a dance challenge."
Dance challenge?
Ok.
"Chaewon, did you know that there
are less than 90 days left this year?"
No way.
Isn't time too fast?
When did the year go by so fast?
Time flies so fast, doesn't it?
Then is Eunchae an adult, too?
OMG. I suppose so.
Oh time is super fast.
But what I felt was that
Really, really really,
Among the Fearnots,
There's Fearnot that
I've known for a long time,
There's Fearnot who are new,
I'm so thankful and
precious to all of you.
It's been about six years since I debuted
in the entertainment industry, right?
I saw it from the beginning
And I'll keep on going.
And it's amazing that Fearnots
have been supporting me all this time.
I'm so grateful.
If I stay with all the
Fearnots for a long time,
we'll be amazing.
I think we're going to fall in love.
We're in trouble if we don't
have each other anymore.
That's right.
"Chaewon,
you have to do it until your 50s."
Oh, yes.
50s...
I'll try my best so that I'm strong.
50 years old.
I exercise a lot.
I eat a lot of nutrients.
I'll do it until I'm in my 50s.
Le Sserafim, I'll try my best.
I'm in my 50s...
Can I do fearless?
Oh, that was interesting,
too. Those who liked me for a
long time was also a Fearnot,
but what kind of job I got, listening
to the stories of each Fearnot.
- "Can I look forward to Golden Wave?"
- Please look forward to it.
Should I go to bed now?
I'll go to bed now.
"No."
Why? No, it's late Fearnot
Someone planned it.
Right?
Is 12 o'clock late?
It's late.
Why?
Let's go to bed.
I'm sorry, but it's time to go to bed.
"Isn't it early for the market now?"
Right.
It's the earliest time.
"Chaewon, hurry up."
It's not dinner right now.
What do you mean, fortune teller?
It's a fortune teller. (?)
I'm going to eat after I wake up.
This is the beginning.
Oh my gosh, that word is the scariest. (?)
Amechu?
In the morning...
I can't think of anything right now.
Bagel?
Bagel.
Ssambap.
There's only ssambap
in my stomach right now.
London bagel looks delicious.
Nemo Nemo Nemo Nemo
"I hate bagels."
Don't eat bagels then. Eat rice.
Is there something wrong with bread?
"Recommend the best Jimbeam then?"
The ginger that comes out this time.
Wow, but the comments are getting faster.
"I like you more than bagels."
What was that? It's so cheesy.
????????
Thank you, Fearnot.
Thank you, thank you. Don't get hurt.
I'm just kidding.
Then I'm going to go to bed now.
Why? Because I have an early day tomorrow.
"From now on,
the person who sleeps is a fool."
Then I will be a fool.
Fearnot...
You've done a good job today.
Let's all be fools.
Fearnot, you know what?
If you sleep now,
you'll be happy tomorrow.
You have to sleep now to sleep well
and have a good condition, so you
won't have any regrets tomorrow.
Anyeong. Bye bye.
See you next time.
Bye.
Bye bye.
Good night.
I'm really going.
[Please Consider Subscribing]
Bye bye.