Hi
Wait a minute.
I was looking at the filter.
It's already on.
Is this better?
Hello.
I just...
I just got off in Korea.
So...
I'm waiting for my suitcase.
I came to play for a moment,
everyone.
For a moment.
I went to Japan.
It's not an airport. It's my room.
Last time, I was going to bed,
I was lying on my bed.
I only did voice live.
At that time,
Fearnot always asked me to show my face.
Today,
It's not before I go to bed.
My face is ready.
I turned it on.
It got pretty cold in Korea.
To say that,
I've only been in Japan for a day.
Fim's Club. I saw it.
Why am I the smallest?
I don't know either.
Why?
I was the smallest.
Right?
Was Chaewon the biggest?
I saw it too.
Today, I was on the plane.
I usually sleep on the plane.
But today, I didn't sleep
and watched the best baseball game.
It's my first time watching a game.
Almost all of them are
watching the game together.
I was watching the best
baseball game alone.
My heart was beating so fast.
I watched the best
baseball game alone like this.
I was watching the
best baseball game.
I finished it and got off the plane.
Did you really succeed in ticketing?
It's in the script.
When is the last time
you learned Japanese?
When was the last time
Today...
I remember.
Do you remember?
When?
My hair is short.
My eyes look tired?
Why? Do my eyes look tired?
Really?
I remember.
Today...
I remember today.
Where is it?
This is my room.
Welcome to my room.
This is my bed.
Do you want me to show you?
Ta-da.
Do you know this?
It's not the lion doll from
our first documentary.
It's a lion doll with a hood.
It's cute. I pulled it like
this and my eyebrows split.
I still have my eyes on
it and I still wear it a lot.
Yeah, I'm busy and going out.
Is there something you're curious about?
My room?
I don't have much in my room.
My bed,
my standby thingy from the Leniverse,
TV, TV, and
I'm sorry, but I'm not ready yet.
"Show me anything."
There's a computer
right next to my bed.
When I was really
crazy about Overwatch,
I didn't want to live
without this computer.
I don't play games now,
so I just use it as a desk.
Did you cut your hair today?
I'm sorry, I just untied it.
Please speak Japanese.
Today...
Today,
To all the Fearnot,
I would like to thank everyone for coming
to the fan signing and press conference.
I'll always be enjoying
watching your moves.
Today's TMI: I cut my bangs
today because it was a little long.
It's a little long.
Perfect!
"Are you good at Japanese?"
Me?
Are you good at Japanese?
Not yet.
Apartment.
It's a perfect night.
Thank you. Perfect night.
Perfect night.
It's the best.
"I'm going to take an
English exam tomorrow."
Fighting.
Fighting!
Make me super crazy
"Do a capture time"
Capture time?
Okay, since I turned on the camera,
let's capture time
How should I do it? Capture time
Please read the
comments after the wink.
I think my wink skills
have decreased.
Why is this eye so closed?
I can do it,
but I can't do it pretty.
I can't do a pretty wink.
I don't like it.
"V, please." V.
V.
Next.
Hurry up.
Capture time.
Quack's face.
Wait a minute.
Next.
Cat heart.
Ta-da.
Cat ears.
End.
Guys, really.
I just wanted to say good night.
Good night, everyone.
I'm ready someday.
I'll be ready someday.
If you're ready,
I'll introduce you to the room.
Bye.
Good night.
Thank you.
I love you.
Don't catch a cold.
Bye, everyone.
Good night.
Bye.