Hello, everyone.
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
I brought some rice.
I know.
Mi is...
I know, right?
I've never been on the show before.
I want to be on the show someday.
I'm eating salt bread.
It's been a long time since I've been on the show.
When was it?
During the promotion.
It was the last time I did it for a short time.
Where did it go?
Someone said it was fun at the fan signing event yesterday.
That's great.
Thank you for going to the fan signing event today.
Thank you for coming to the fan signing event today.
Thank you so much, everyone.
What should I say?
After the fan signing event today...
And...
I was shooting a video for a content.
Why a practice room? Is it a concert?
I think you have to wait a little longer for a concert.
You have to have a lot of songs to make it different.
So...
I asked a lot of questions today.
Even during the fan signing event.
Wait a little longer.
I'll do my best for the end of the year stage.
I heard that there was a fireworks party at the Han River today.
A fireworks party?
It wasn't a party.
It wasn't that big of a party.
Is it a fireworks festival?
So I went up to the rooftop.
I came to see it with the managers.
It's a festival, right?
Yes.
It was amazing.
Really?
It's been a while since I saw it.
The fireworks...
I saw it properly.
Since I was a student...
I saw it a lot when I was in my teens.
I think...
If I have a summer vacation,
I go to see it with my family.
I saw it a lot when I was an idol.
Did you cry?
Wow, there's someone who knows me from a long time ago.
I didn't cry, but the sound was really loud.
So I was a little scared.
Except for that, it was okay.
It was so pretty.
Something...
I'm not the kind of person who just looks pretty.
So I wondered Some Korean people us watching this fireworks together.
What kind of person would be there to watch this fireworks next year?
I was thinking like this.
It was pretty, right?
Just now, um...
There was a fireworks competition at the Han river.
We watched it with ourimmigrant height.
with ourimmigrant height.
Ah, right.
I get asked a lot about where I got the packs for the punishment game.
For now,
I can't do it in front of people who don't know the rules.
So I decided to do it at Weverse Live.
I'll do it someday.
I had a pack in Portugal.
I was so nervous to do it in front of other fans who don't know the rules.
I always had a schedule.
I was already wearing makeup when I got to work.
I couldn't do it on the way to work.
I decided to do it at Weverse Live.
Please understand.
And I wanted to show you my pretty face on the way to work.
So...
Okay.
It wasn't easy.
It wasn't easy for me and Eunchi compared to other members.
I'll do it next time.
Did you see the fireworks?
It was so pretty.
I ate rice.
I ate soup.
I ate crumb chowder.
Long time no see.
I ate it simply.
I ate it after I got off work.
Can I do what I want to hear?
Eunchi's voice.
I'm the leader.
I'm a leader, too.
It was my belief.
No one guessed I was serious.
I've never done it before, but I'm trying hard these days.
Vol.1
It doesn't matter if you didn't do it from the beginning.
Come on.
And now...
Sabrina Carpenter was on the live show.
It was so pretty.
Did you see that, everyone?
I think some people don't know.
Like this.
Wait.
I want to explain it properly.
At Sabrina's concert,
At the concert,
At first,
I came with the concept of being a little late.
So I'm covering my clothes like this.
I know, I know.
Does anyone know?
I came like this.
Show me like this.
I was so scared.
And then I saw it like this.
The microphone didn't come out.
I'm doing this.
But I throughout,
Everything
Everything is so lovely.
How can we be so lovely?
Anybody who knows it, can understand me completely.
Do you know?
Through tik-tok.
Recently.
There's people who do challenges.
I'll do it later.
Let's go.
This song is really...
We took a vacation this time.
I went to Hawaii with my family.
I went to the beach at night.
The beach is right in front of the hotel.
There's a place where you can lie down.
I was listening to this song while lying down there.
I was listening to the lyrics of Sanurina.
I think Sanurina's lyrics are really cute.
She's cute.
You can't hate her.
We were so cute.
It was so cute.
I'll turn it off for a moment.
When I went to Hawaii on vacation, I listened to this song all the time.
It's not burnt at all.
My hands are really burnt.
I didn't burn much in other places.
Well, it's a little burnt, but my hands are burning.
My hands are burning.
I don't know.
I like Sabrina too.
I want to go to the concert.
This Sabrina set is so cute.
It was so nice to sing while sitting on the heart.
It was good.
I bought a VN-made one.
I bought a set.
I went to VN.
The set was so...
It's really...
I have two.
If I do it on this side, it leads to this side.
Suddenly, I have a different house.
The set was really amazing.
It was really awesome.
Then, something.
It felt like we were watching a movie together, so it was amazing.
During VMAs.
It wasn't our stage, but the stage at the awards ceremony.
The stage we were watching.
It was amazing.
I'm wearing this because I wanted to talk about our vacation.
Shall we talk about our vacation?
It was our first vacation, right?
When I was young, there was this thing about Japanese people.
If you say vacation, it means Hawaii.
It's a must.
There's something like that.
Something like that.
There's something like that too.
When celebrities go on vacation, it's Hawaii.
Since I was in elementary school,
since I was really young,
there was something like that.
The atmosphere was like that.
So I had to go on vacation.
When I heard that there was going to be a vacation this time,
I was like, I have to go to Hawaii.
I told my mom right away.
Mom, I think I have to go to Hawaii.
I've never been there.
This vacation is in Hawaii.
So I went.
I'll say it in Japanese.
When I was told that I was going to take a vacation for the first time,
I was like, vacation?
What do you call it?
Vacation equals...
The vacation of a celebrity equals Hawaii.
It's been like that for a long time.
It's just my imagination.
I've never been to Hawaii.
I thought I'd definitely go to Hawaii on my first vacation.
So I went to Hawaii.
So in terms of being in Hawaii,
Um...
At first,
There was a hotel called Kahara Hotel.
There was a hotel where they were raising dolphins at the hotel.
It's about 7 minutes away from Waikiki.
There aren't many people there.
From the hotel to the swimming pool and the beach,
It's all connected.
They're raising dolphins next to the pool.
So you can just see the dolphins.
If you make a reservation there,
From 9 p.m.
You can experience it.
You can swim with the dolphins.
You can play with the dolphins.
There's something like that.
So I made a reservation for that, too.
Right.
And there's a restaurant in the hotel.
It's a really famous restaurant.
Just in Hawaii.
So there,
I had a meal.
It was really good.
So after that,
What was it?
On the first day,
I don't remember.
Wait a minute.
Oh, right.
On the first day,
This is...
It's really...
It's my first time.
Anyone can see it.
One person came to Hawaii for the first time.
on which I is the highest number of domestic дв.
I'm the one.
There was a tree that goes down.
Everyone crispy but
There was a good książi.
So I wanted to be a person who's always tired,
That's not what I mean.
I think it's something I learned.
As a part of the trip,
I wanted to feel like that.
I want to go before I know.
Everybody looks famous.
I even ate it.
What did I do on the first day?
I really don't remember, all of a sudden
First, I did that
And the next day
I went on a snowmobile
I went on a yacht
I think it was a gecko
I went quite far
And there
I used a goggle
And I saw the sea
And I swam with the fish
And there was a turtle
There was a normal turtle
But we couldn't approach it
But if we approached it
We could see it from a distance
I experienced that
I did a lot of things, so I don't remember
It was really fun
I saw a turtle
And I did a test with a turtle
And
I didn't really surf the surfboard
I got on the surfboard
And
I did something like this
Like a canoe
The picture was frozen
But I did that
But I'm not really good at it
But
My mom
I went with my dad
I was going to go with my dad
But my dad couldn't go
So we went together
But
Are you okay now?
Are you worried?
My dad is the best at English
But
I couldn't do it
So I was like
What should I do?
I had no choice but to speak English
So I tried my best
But
When I was on the surfboard
I was at the same time as the Korean
I made a reservation at the same time
So
They didn't recognize me
But I kept speaking in Korean
And they were good at English
So I spoke in English
But my English was a bit fast
So I couldn't understand it
I took a picture
But I didn't know if I should use USB
Or SD card
So it was hard
So I asked them in Korean
What do you do in English?
Can you translate it for me?
I asked them in Korean
They were surprised
I was living in Korea
I can speak Korean
They were surprised
So we had a 3-part conversation
I explained in Japanese
My mom answered
I was speaking in Korean
And the Korean people
Translated it into English
There were many languages
I am so glad I could speak in Korean
I was so glad I could speak in Korean
They said
they like traveling
They said they went to Fukuoka
They said Fukuoka is my hometown
We had a conversation
It was fun
It was amazing
It was really hard for me to speak English, because I was the only one who could speak English.
My younger brother could speak English, but he said he didn't want to speak English because he was too shy.
So I had to speak English.
My younger brother speaks English, too.
When I was young, I went to a kindergarten that spoke English.
That's how it was.
And I'm still learning at school.
So I can do simple things, but he kept saying he was too shy.
So I had no choice but to do it.
But he understood.
It was fun.
You saw all the pictures, right?
Most of them were taken by my younger brother.
My mom is really good at taking pictures.
Seriously.
I can't help it.
There are things that people are good at and things that they're not good at.
She's such a pretty girl, but she wants to take pictures like this.
She's really good at taking pictures.
Really.
So I told my mom,
Oh, please.
Mom, try taking a picture of me like this.
I set the angle.
Mom, mom, now, now.
You know this angle, right?
But my mom moved again.
So I tried to teach her well, but there was a difficulty.
My brother kept watching it next to me.
So I said,
Oh, then take a picture of my brother.
So I took a picture of him.
But he's good at taking pictures.
He was watching it right next to me.
He understood everything I said.
So I took a picture of my brother.
But the funny thing is,
I posted it on Instagram.
Then my mom suddenly called me and said,
But I think I took a good picture.
So I said, Mom, that's almost a picture of my brother.
Oh, really?
No.
Then my brother next to me said,
Oh, I took all of these pictures.
I took a picture of my brother and sent them to him.
He took a picture of my brother better than I thought.
I really can't take pictures of my mom.
Really.
It's really bad.
It's a picture I like to take.
I was in the middle.
Even if I say I'm in the middle of the video,
it's hard for me.
So I was asked to take pictures of my brother.
It was fun.
It's been a while since I played with Nam Do-eun.
I used to play with her a lot when she was a baby.
But I never played with her properly after she became a student.
When she came to Tokyo, I used to look at her face a lot.
But it was my first time seeing her for a long time.
So it was fun to talk to her.
I don't want Kim Wh tantalum anymore.
You're still as young as me.
You're little.
You look really calm now.
You want me to face the camera?
I'm so embarrassed to film at this stage.
Are you interested in being a cameraman?
But I think it's fun to do my own thing.
I want to try this hairstyle.
Teacher, why are you so shy?
I guess it's not like that.
But I was even more shy.
It wasn't like that when I was in middle school.
When I was in elementary school,
I went out to eat.
My mom would ask me to say hello.
So that I could say hello properly.
But I was so mean.
I was so shy.
I cried there.
My mom said I was too shy.
So I went to learn musicals.
That was the beginning.
So when I saw you,
I thought you were better than me.
You were so mean.
Now I'm not shy anymore.
You were so mean back then.
You were like that when you were young.
You were fine.
But it doesn't mean that I'm still the same.
But when I tried it,
I realized that
I was so different from when I was young.
Even though I had different environment.
So I don't worry too much.
I'm young.
But people...
It's all the same when you're young.
We're learning more and more.
I think.
When I went to Hawaii, there were a lot of people who recognized me.
Even if it wasn't a Korean or Japanese person,
various people recognized me.
They spoke to me in English.
I went to a steak restaurant. It's really famous.
It's famous in Hawaii.
What's the name?
Jaws? Jaws? Jays?
It's a steak restaurant.
The staff there said,
Are you Sakura?
It was so amazing.
My mom saw it and said she was touched.
My daughter recognized me no matter where I went.
That's how much she recognized me.
It's not like that.
It's amazing.
But she recognized me in English.
She spoke to me in English.
So it was amazing.
It was amazing for me, too.
Where do you want to go after the members?
After the members?
After the members, it would be fun to go anywhere.
If I get a vacation next time,
I want to go to Jeju Island.
I want to go nearby.
Or I want to go to Hawaii again.
I love Hawaii.
If I get a vacation next time,
I want to go to a nearby place.
I want to go to Jeju Island.
Or I want to go to Hawaii again.
A warm place feels like a vacation destination.
I like cold places, too.
But it's a little...
There's a lot of luggage.
Do you know what I mean?
The carrier ends with clothes.
But if you go to a warm place,
You can just take a t-shirt or a dress.
You can just take a thin dress.
I like a warm place.
It was a very tea-like comment.
Right?
I think you know what I mean.
I'm a realistic person.
Because there are a lot of things I want to buy.
If I just put on a padded jacket, it's over.
That's too slow.
If I have a magazine in Japan...
Did you know this year?
You don't, do you?
Please wait a little longer.
A little more.
I bought this hat because it's too cute.
I want to see you wearing it.
There were a lot of people who wore it today.
This is Ego's wink.
Congratulations.
Black and white girls are so popular these days.
I haven't seen it yet.
It's really fun.
I only know what the members are talking about because I haven't seen it yet.
I'll think about it.
I'll think about it for a while.
What is this?
The girl who is eating with her eyes closed.
I heard the explanation of what it is.
I thought I'd see it, but I haven't seen it yet.
I'll see it.
Wow.
Did you see this?
With Chaeyeon.
I'm sure YUNJIN and ZEHA are watching this too.
We were at a local event and ZEHA was watching at this time.
Right, we went to a university festival this week.
It was so much fun.
The university students had so much fun playing with us.
We went there as soon as the vacation ended.
It felt like we were performing for the first time in a long time.
It was so much fun.
We also went to Busan and Daegu.
Is it the first time for us to go to Busan?
We went to Busan once in the past.
This time, on the day we arrived in Busan,
we went to Busan.
It was early in the morning.
We went to eat grilled clams.
The next day, we woke up and had a burger soup.
It was so good.
I really like it.
It was a burger soup.
We ate a burger sashimi there.
We also had a fried burger.
I really like burgers.
I was so happy to eat it after a long time.
After eating that,
we went to the beach.
The next day, we went to Daegu.
It was early in the morning.
We had to eat something delicious.
So, we had makjang.
It was the first time I had makjang at a restaurant.
It was really delicious.
It was a bit serious.
It was so delicious.
Does it taste the same when you eat it in Daegu?
Or does it taste the same when you eat it in Seoul?
It's because I really want to eat it.
It was so delicious.
I ate it in Daegu.
Makjang is one of Daegu.
Why?
Makjang is for Daegu's people.
Oh, I see.
It's a good restaurant, really.
Our mission team
has someone who knows Daegu so well.
Does it taste the same when you eat it in Seoul?
Does it taste good already?
Oh, so I have to go to Daegu.
If you want to eat it with that taste,
do you have to go to Daegu?
I should go to Daegu right now.
For real
It was so good
It was my first time eating makjang in a restaurant
It was so crispy
It was so good
After that
After the fan signing event
I went to Busan
As soon as I arrived
I ate clam noodles
No, kalguksu
I ate clam kalguksu
I ate a lot of delicious food
And then
Yesterday in Seoul
I had pilates for the first time in a long time
I almost died
It was so hard
Even walking hurts
My muscles hurt so much
I want to eat kalguksu
I like mung bean assert Isu
I like mung bean assert Ayu
I haven't seen the fireworks festival
I saw it
I went to the airport
I didn't mail it. I took it. I'll do it soon.
Oh, right. I went to see IU's concert.
It was our first time.
We were guests this year.
We couldn't see each other because of the music show.
So we went.
It was so much fun.
It was crazy.
They were so pretty.
They were so good.
It was like Disney.
All the directors.
They sang all the songs I knew.
I went to say hello after the concert.
I wore a hat.
I wanted to say thank you to them.
I met them in person.
So I said that.
They said,
That hat is still in my house.
It's so pretty.
I'm keeping it well.
I thought it was too much for me.
I was so happy.
I was so grateful.
They said that.
Thank you.
That's why I have kirin on my bag.
This is...
But I lost this.
I really love you.
I went with my mom.
My mom and I...
Not my mom, but when I was young,
we watched a lot of Korean dramas together.
My family really liked them, so I watched them with them.
I really liked it.
It was so fun.
It's been 35 minutes already.
I'm hungry.
I worked so hard on my lower body.
It really hurts.
I really hate muscle pain.
Do you have saliva these days?
I don't have saliva these days.
I don't have this.
Do you want to come to a Japanese cultural festival?
I want you to come to a Japanese cultural festival.
There aren't many cultures like that in Japan.
There's a talk show.
I've never heard of an idol coming to a talk show.
I wish I could.
Is it difficult?
Not really.
I'm waiting for the day off.
I haven't taken the day off yet.
When is it?
I'm excited.
There's a place where we can meet.
I want to go there. It looks fun.
When will the team log be released?
When?
That festival...
I took a film while walking around the house.
I didn't take full photos with one individual.
I took video with other members.
I don't know when that filming will be released.
It'll come out in theperformance format.
That film log is very great but...
Of course, I love it, but I used to film alone for a week or so.
One person at a time.
It was fun back then, too. I want to do that, too.
It's a real improvement.
I think it was a content where I could feel the day of this person.
So I want to say, I want to do it again.
I think it would be good to do it at the end of the year.
Because I went back and forth and went abroad a lot.
It was a content that Pimlog liked the most.
It was fun to wash up, too.
Shall we go now?
2 minutes left. Until 40 minutes.
is not today's bibliography late
It's who's wanna go to the Pimlog open-ended airport?
I didn't do it.
I'll do a lot.
Don't go.
I don't like it.
I don't know when I'll be able to go to the concert, though.
I'm filming UNIVERSE right now.
Because...
Actually, UNIVERSE...
Since before the crazy promotion...
There are a lot of things that I filmed.
And this time, UNIVERSE has a lot of new attempts.
Wait.
So...
Please look forward to it.
I think it's going to be fun.
I don't know how it's going to turn out.
So, it's been a while since I've done a Weverse rap.
So...
I think it's going to be fun.
I have returned to the V-Live after a long time.
I will get closer.
I will come again.
It's 10 pm in the future, right?
I have to go to bed early.
Hello, FIORA.
FIORA, you should go to bed early too.
Let's work hard tomorrow.
All the best!
Good night.
Thank you for watching.