Hi
It's Minjun
It's going well, right?
What's up
I'm in my room
It's not a perm
I have a shoot today
I have a shoot
I took off my hair
A perm?
I had my hair curled
That's right, I had a shoot today
What's up
Where are you this late?
I'm at home
I'm at the dorm
Do you have time?
Yes, I have time
Time is
Like this
I always come when I have time
What shoot do I have today?
Today
I washed my hair
To my house
I'm coming
Did you do your hair?
Yes
How do you feel?
Everybody
Ye turtle
You have asta hair
Yes
It's good
Fantastic
Yes
Do I play any games? I unfortunately don't play any games.
Can you introduce me to one of the books in the back?
Okay.
Hold on a second.
Let me see.
Hmm.
Yeah.
What's up?
Oh, what did I think of the UK?
It was so great. I had such a good time.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
The Book Thief.
I've talked about this book a lot, but
I think it's actually
like a modern
book that will become
a classic,
I think.
It's very, very good.
It talks about...
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, there's so much
mungy.
Yeah.
It's about
the power of
like reading and books and imagination in really harrowing times because it's, you know,
based off of a real historical event.
How many books are in that book tower?
I don't know.
It's six movies.
Thank you.
You know,
I think so.
It's cool.
This.
Queen of the Ice,
and it's,
I don't know.
There's a lot of like generational stuff which is something that feels really familiar to me.
Like immigrants.
Buy a bookshelf? I do have a bookshelf but that's already stacked.
What's the most recent Japanese word you remember?
What's the most recent Japanese word I remember?
Giri giri
But what if I fall over?
I don't fall over.
Because it's a steel bookshelf.
It's not just like this.
It's vertical.
How do you say it?
It's like lying down.
Hair? I didn't dye my hair but
Fiona kept telling me that I dyed my hair.
I think I get a lot of light.
I didn't dye my hair.
I think it's the same blue.
It's the same blue but if it's dark it looks like black.
Itv
Sweden.
Switzerland was so beautiful
We were really
Since I became a trainee, for the first time in a long time, I spent time with my family, and it was really, really, really, really good.
It was so good.
What do you drink? I drink Yonana.
But I shouldn't drink coffee at this time, but I drank it because I love A.
But I still sleep well. Don't worry.
But don't drink coffee at a late time, especially when you're young.
Do you understand? Drink decaffeinated coffee.
It's a little hard to order again.
Do you sleep well?
Do I sleep well? I think I sleep fairly well.
Do you miss Rachel?
Do I miss Rachel? Yes, I miss Rachel so much.
What is my coffee order?
Just an iced Americano. Black. I like black coffee.
What country do you want to go to after Switzerland?
There are so many countries I want to go to, so I think I need to write a bucket list.
There are so many. Anywhere. Any new country.
Any new city. Anywhere. I love everything.
London was really good too.
Fish and chips are good.
And a lot of curry as well. I love curry.
I love curry so much.
Can you do a heart?
Oh, so comfortable. Thank you.
Because you are here while I'm eating. I love you.
Aww.
Yeah, everybody, I hope you can get a good snack while you watch.
Favorite topping on pizza? Broccoli and ricotta cheese.
Or...
I don't know. I like, I like me a white pizza with broccoli.
Or, like, greens and, um, I don't know, cheese. Like, ricotta cheese.
And also, I just like a margarita. Like, basil, basil leaves. That's really good too.
Have you read The Seven Husbands of Evelyn Hugo?
I have not, but Rachel is obsessed with that book. She, it's her favorite book.
So, hopefully one day I will.
Broccoli? Y'all are hating on broccoli?
Ricotta does go crazy on pizza.
It goes what?
Can I eat the jjapaghetti on Yunjin's head?
It's blue. Would you be okay with that?
I don't have it.
Ribbons.
It's dessert.
I wish it would
Chopsticks.
The Però the Dragon Tattoo is good?
My mom used to have that book back at home.
How does it feel to perform at a festival after a long time?
It was really really really fun.
Really...
I kept talking to the members and they said it was really fun.
It was really really fun.
It was really fun and...
Really...
The energy and the heat
were no joke.
Really...
For me, when I watch a performance
or when I perform,
everyone in that space feels liberated
and really...
become one mind, one body
just...
Forget about that moment and just enjoy everything.
That's how I feel.
It's like...
Everyone enjoyed it so much
so it was really...
good and if we could give
a little bit of good energy,
I don't think there's anything better than that.
Really really...
I'm looking forward to it in the future
and I'll do my best.
Ah! I'll look forward to the Hoseo Festival!
I'll look forward to it!
I'll definitely...
go and see it!
The college entrance exam!
There's 47 days left, nuna.
Fighting!
Fighting fighting! Fighting!
Fighting for the college entrance exam!
I also...
The US...
college entrance exam?
A few years ago...
I really...
prepared for it.
But it was really...
really hard.
Studying all day long...
Really, the stress...
I tried to control it as much as I could
but...
I remember studying with a lot of stress
because it was so intense.
Really, all the students...
really...
I sincerely support you.
You're really amazing.
Being able to do something so passionately
is really really amazing
and cool.
So...
Have pride.
Don't get too stressed...
Fighting!
You can do it.
I'm still not...
Do you think pineapple belongs to pizza?
I don't know.
Do you think I belong...
Wait, no.
I was trying to say
do you think I belong on the syrup
but that would mean
I think pineapple belongs on pizza.
Yeah.
The answer is no
I don't think it belongs to pizza.
I'm used to pizza
I'm also good at
Ah! Oh, Yunjung, did you eat pho? I actually just had pho with Chaewon and Zuha.
Put some decorations up on my room?
This is actually the plainest part of my room. Like, my room is actually a mess. I cannot show you anything more.
Like, this is, it's such a bad, it's in such a bad state right now.
My ukulele's here, and like...
Oh, it's still fairly in tune. Oh, there's my guitar.
Oh, it's still not in tune.
Yeah.
Sounds like my morning alarm. Yeah, that is true.
Double take.
I'm gonna sing the crowds and listen from the crowds. I don't see nobody but you.
Also, this book.
I forgot, I brought it over just to show you guys.
This book is so good.
I've mentioned it a few times, but...
It's so good.
Very relatable.
Do I play Minecraft? I used to play Minecraft.
Like, the mobile version.
This is not a real plant.
Have you tried using Kymak?
K-Mak?
Have I ever tried Kymak? K-Mak?
I have.
It's very good.
I had it with Zuha.
Girl, buy a bookshelf. Those books are gonna take over.
That is a bookshelf.
It's a bookshelf, but like, it's just where you have the books, like, sideways.
So there's like a shelf there. You just can't see it because it's between the books.
I'm so scared of long-term flights. It's tiring. What are you doing in a plane, Yoonjin?
Uh, me? I...
I either sleep.
I usually sleep.
I either sleep or...
I don't know.
I think I listen to music a lot while reading books or listening to music.
Everyone, do you watch Black and White Cookers these days?
It's so much fun.
It's so cool.
Almost all the people who appear on the show are really, really cool.
Totally respect.
What song should I listen to?
Then...
Everyone, do you have a song request?
Last time, we were in the States.
Have you listened to this song before?
Yes.
I really love this song.
Here we go.
It's so cool.
I'm going to take a shower and go to bed.
I'm going to take a shower and...
Can I marry Rachel? NOOOOO
Oh, her hair looks mysterious.
oh well I did like science in high school
Oh well I did like science in high school
I wonder if she doesn't use these fun glasses.
I bought this plate at a vintage shop.
Glasses! Glasses!
What should I say?
I'm using this as a display.
I'm going to turn the BGM down and listen to some music.
What should I listen to?
While you're listening to this.
Glasses!
Now what should I say?
What should I say?
Try On?
I'll give it a shot.
This song is so...
Hayley Knox's Eleventh Hour.
It's in Stardust.
It's Heine Knox... Knox? Knox?
It's Knox.
I'm obsessed with her.
First glasses.
These are the glasses.
I have glasses like this.
I think I wore this once when I danced.
Chaewon wears this often.
This one, too.
I think I wore this in America.
By any chance...
Is the picture not good?
Is it done?
Is it okay?
Is it okay now?
I think it's okay.
I can't see it?
The picture quality?
I'll turn it back on.
Hold on.
Hang on.