bgm
Piano
this isn't a rehearsal right?
uh? i got it
Hi
Hello
Everyone
gather gather gather
I didn't even
expect it
I didn't even expect it
My hair is
doing the choreography
right now
It's a bit
but
All of a sudden?
All of a sudden
It's all good
The choreography
will be
tomorrow
Golden Wave
will be on
Right right
I practiced
What are you doing?
It's Friday afternoon
Hello
Hi
When we do
Confety
But
I want
This
I'm good. How are you? If you're not.
Hi.
Are you all busy right now?
There must be a lot of people who are going home after work.
Or are you still working?
Every day.
Just living is amazing.
We...
I'm studying, but I came to see you.
I came to see you.
No.
I'm going to study.
Right.
Next month.
I'm going back to Osaka.
Oh, is it getting a little colder in Japan?
It's been a little chilly in Korea lately.
Zoya's bangs.
This is the bangs.
Now.
Here's the bangs.
Bangs.
They're not bangs.
Banks.
No bangs.
基本용 sign효과RAYA
I really wanted to go to Italy
I really did go
Originally, I wanted to go to Italy or somewhere like that
I wanted to go to a country that I've never been to before
So I thought about it
I wanted to go to Paris for my first vacation
So I went
When I was studying abroad
What was it?
Before I started my quarantine
I had a vacation at a ballet school
So at that time
My mom and dad came to the Netherlands
So I was there for about a week
I took a train with my parents
I went to Paris for the first time
I have a really good memory
So I wanted to go again
So this time
On the last day
For lunch
I had to eat
At that time
2 years? 2 years? 3 years?
Was it 3 years?
At that time
I went with my mom and dad
What was it?
What was the name?
Cascade?
That kind of name
Pie
That kind of food
That kind of
I went
I went again
I don't know what I'm saying
So
I went again after 3 years
At that time
As a foreign student
With my mom and dad
For the first time
I went to Paris
We had dinner together
This time
The situation changed completely
With my mom
In the same restaurant
Eating the same food
I felt really weird
For me
A meaningful
Restaurant
I think
That was it
Tzuhaya
When is the Luniverse coming out?
Luniverse?
The Luniverse
You can really
Look forward to it
Luniverse is really
Really
Incredible
Really really
It's more loyal than loyal
The staff of the staff
Really thank you
Thank you. Thank you and I love you.
There will be a lot of fun contents.
As always...
I think we'll be able to see a new side of us in a variety of ways.
Today's fashion? Today's fashion is so comfortable.
The theme is comfort.
The shoe thief.
Right. That...
It came out suddenly.
I was surprised too.
But it turned out well.
As expected.
I took it like this with the flip-flops.
It's really funny.
I didn't even imagine it at that time.
I didn't know the shoe thief would take it.
It really became a thief.
Chaewon.
Yes?
I'm not playing games without you.
They were throwing their hands all over the table.
You'reiza.
Chaewon.
You should start off.
Then, do a favor.
When you hear Chaewon, you'll start touching it now.
Because you do it then.
socratic.
It came out
Unas episode
I took a tiktok with you earlier
Please wait a little
The monitor is the lighting?
Yes, it is
The monitor
My PC
The white background
Is my lighting
Right now
It's the white background
Like this
The blue background
The blue background is fine
No, the white background
The white background is too white
The blue background is fine
It's fine
The white background
Is definitely
Weakening the reflection
Your eyes are so shiny
Really?
Yes
No, really
No
What's the matter?
I was blah blah
I'm feeling bad
What are you naucing in front of this picture?
I'm a uber
Still
What's that?
Ah
Uh
As expected, I wanted to eat something warm because it was a little chilly.
Recommend me ice cream. Ice cream.
Pistachio ice cream.
Ice cream. I ate that last time.
The one they sell at the convenience store.
Dubai chocolate ice cream.
They sell it these days.
Yoonjin told me about it.
It was good.
I don't know what Dubai chocolate is.
I'll try it in the US.
The teacher bought it for me, so I ate it.
It was really good.
Dubai chocolate.
Is Dubai chocolate popular in Japan?
Is it popular all over the world?
I don't know.
TT
Is Dubai chocolate popular?
It's popular. It's popular.
That means it's already popular?
You've seen it, right?
You've seen it with the members, right?
I want to eat croissant.
Do you want me to imitate you?
Who do you want to imitate?
I want to see your short hair.
Short hair?
I want to try it.
I want to try it, but if I do it,
it's a little...
How should I put it?
I think I'll look ugly.
No.
I think I'll look a lot uglier.
I think I'll look ugly.
It sounds like a good thing,
but it's not like that.
I think my image will change.
That's how it is.
Honey, it's not short hair.
It's not short hair.
You're sure.
All right, then.
Honesty.
Is it in the back?
Is it that again?
Don't catch a cold.
Even if it's cold,
the season is changing.
Please be careful not to catch a cold.
My light.
It's gone again.
How tall are you?
I'm...
I haven't done it lately.
170...
Isn't it 70?
At the beginning of my debut,
I was 74.
It's not that big.
170...
Is it there?
Don't you know?
What should I say?
170...
I don't know if it's there or not.
That much.
It's hard. Korean.
Is it possible or not?
170B.
My height is 170.
Is it possible or not?
170B.
180B.
161B.
"18??"
ness.
181B.
18?
I'll try it
I'm really... Daehyeong baby
Recently, Eunchae
Seems to be o holding back
Did you work out today? I just came back from working out.
But it's been a while since I've done it, so I don't feel any strength.
It's not easy to work out.
I worked out thinking about soy sauce marinated crab.
I think I'm going to eat with the members later.
I did the hamstring thing.
The machine that you bend in the back.
I did that.
I got strength from doing soy sauce marinated crab.
As expected, the power of appetite.
I recommend you to do this.
Think about what you want to eat and work out.
That way, it works out well.
Uh-uh.
I'm sorry.
My MBTI is...
INFP.
But lately, I've felt a little bit of an issue.
What?
Uh?
There are times when I feel like I'm T
But I told that to Yunjin unnie
I said, I feel like I'm T these days
Yunjin unnie said, but Zuhua, do you know this?
F means I think I'm T
T means I don't think I'm F
So you're F
You said it like that
I see, then I'm F
I guess I'm F
I guess I'm F when I think about it
Jeon Mechoo? Should I say Jeon Mechoo?
I eat meat
What do you want to eat?
For me...
In Busan, Daegu
I ate makjang and daechang
It was so good
Originally
I really liked daechang
Makjang and
I said daechang
Not daechang
Makjang and
What's makchang?
Makchang and
Not that
What's makchang?
Tell me
Makchang
Right, right
There's makchang
There's daechang
In Daegu
Gopchang, makchang, daechang
Right
I ate Gopchang and makchang
It was really good
It was better when I ate it at the store
To Fiona
Today
I recommend Gopchang
You should try it
It's more такихank
As you can see
It's actually
're cooked
It's good
It's really good
This is
Gopchang
With the black pepper
마음에
I see
Cranberries
Black pepper
This part is
Cha eh
Yeah
You can
Eat it
in the smell
Cha eh
I wanted to go
of...
Oh
I really wanted to do that
Did you enjoy Zimline?
It's still a secret
Really?
We know everything
Really
Capture time
I don't know any poses these days, but what do you think?
Make a heart
Click
Protein smile
Ribbon heart
The person who thought of the ribbon heart is amazing.
What did you say?
It's just a pose even if you stay still.
You're cool.
Show me your cheeks.
Happy birthday.
I'm happier than I was before
Where have all the cheeks gone?
Belarus
I came to play with P extract points for a while
It took me 25 minutes to do it
It's really fast!
I'll be right there
My legs hurt excitedly.
Oh, it's coming out. It's really fast.
Something comes out at 5 o'clock.
I don't think it's going to be a big one.
I'll go now.
Is it big enough?
I'm sure there's something big enough.
Thank you for coming at this time.
See you again.
From tomorrow.
No.
Eat something delicious for dinner.
Bye. I'll have something delicious, too.
Bye bye.
I'll be back.