i love you
hi
Wait a minute. I was looking at the filter.
It's already in.
Is this better?
Hi.
I just...
I just got off in Korea.
I'm...
I'm waiting for my suitcase.
So...
I came to play for a moment, everyone.
I went to Japan.
It's not an airport, it's my room.
Before I go to bed,
I was lying on my bed.
I only did voice live.
At that time, Fiona always asked me to show my face.
Today...
It's not before I go to bed yet.
My face is ready, so I turned it on.
It got pretty cold in Korea.
To say that...
I've only been in Japan for a day.
Yes.
I think it's the second time 50 subjects.
If it's fun, I'll go to the tank again.
I'm a normal baby.
Did you watch the First It'sاشmso Lobby?
Why are you getting a lot of돈?
No, no, no.
The director said after the first episode of The huge paper...
Yong.
Don't say but...
Hmm.
Today, I was on the plane.
I usually sleep on the plane.
But today, I didn't sleep and watched the best baseball game.
It's my first time watching the best baseball game.
It was so much fun.
Almost all of them are watching the best baseball game.
When I watched the best baseball game alone, my heart was beating so fast.
I watched the best baseball game alone like this.
I watched the best baseball game and got off the plane.
Did you really succeed in ticketing?
When was the last time you learned Japanese?
Today...
I can remember.
When?
My hair is short.
My eyes look tired.
My eyes look tired?
Why?
Do my eyes look tired?
I can remember.
Today...
I can remember today.
Where is it?
This is my room.
Welcome to my room.
This is my bed.
Do you want to see it?
Ta-da.
Do you know this?
It's not the lion doll that was in our first documentary.
It's a lion doll with a hood.
It popped out of here.
I pulled it like this and my eyebrows split.
What do you want to see?
Come on.
I'm worried about поступating.
What do you want to see?
You talk on about what you want to see.
How do you watch TV to influence something?
Come again.
I watch K-POP.
Sorry.
Come.
Weeep!
Stay safe.
I had a good Groundhog Day this time.
Do you miss it?
Did you have a goodday?
I don't have much in my room.
Bed
The standby I got from the Reuniverse.
TV TV TV
Cosmetic table
I'm sorry to introduce the room.
I'm not ready yet.
Show me anything.
My room
There's a computer right next to the bed.
When I lived in Overwatch,
I didn't want to live without this computer.
I don't play games now.
So I'm just using it as a desk.
Did you cut your hair today?
I'm sorry.
I untied it.
Please say it in Japanese.
Kyou
Kyou mo
Nihon
Did you see it in Japanese?
I didn't know.
Love
I'm
Like it works..
Anyway
Today's TMI
I cut iron 님's bangs
"Am I good at Japanese?"
It's perfect night. Thank you. Perfect night.
Perfect night.
Perfect night tonight.
I don't care what's wrong.
I don't care what's wrong or right.
Please don't phone me no more.
There is an English class tomorrow.
Where will I go?
Fighting!
There is an exam tomorrow.
weightless
What are you talking about?
Capture time!
Capture time?
Since the camera is on, let's capture time
How should I do it? Capture time
Wink
Wink and read the comments
I think my wink skills have decreased
Why do my eyes look closed?
Right?
I can do it
But I can't do it prettily
Wink
I don't like it
V?
V