Hi
Hello, hello. Hi. What is it?
Is it me? Hi, hi.
The title of the song is
called Self-Strike. I'm just
going to play before I go
to bed because I'm bored.
If you have any questions for me,
please ask me. I'll answer them all.
I'm nervous. I was just wondering
if you had any questions for me.
It's not Eunchae's voice.
Whose voice is it then? It's mine.
What are you doing
now? I washed up.
I finished everything
and lay down.
How tall are you now? 170 cm? But I
don't think I'm tall anymore. I don't know.
Eunchae, are you sleeping
late today? I'm not sleeping late.
Fireworks? I didn't see it.
I saw it in the video.
TMI?
I feel good because I
scrubbed my body today.
What are you guys doing?
Do you see all the Fearnot
faces on the concert stage?
I can't see all
the Fearnot. But,
I think I can see almost
all the Fearnot on the floor.
Please sing me a crazy song.
"My answer is make
me super CRAZY".
Where are you?
I'm at home.
How was Daegu? The makchang
(beef last viscous) was really good.
Eunchae, did you catch a cold?
I didn't catch a cold.
Isn't it because it's been a
long time since I did a voice live?
Do you want me to give you a
spoiler? What kind of spoiler?
I didn't catch a cold.
This is where they are loverly.
급등 고 벽 수트 대우 레먼 했는데 너무 죄송 했다.
While studying.
Crazy next song?
Hey
Crazy next time.
Dialect?
It's hard
Japanese?
Today, too.
Fearnot...
Fan signing.
Thank you for coming.
Am I right?
I don't know.
Isn't it Eunchae ssi?
Eunchae ssi.
I'm going to make you laugh.
I did it first.
I won.
Crazy Red.
Back in the days.
The me that fell short of crazy
I will no longer bear false
witness before my attraction
A word in Japanese for Kkura.
Good night.
Birthday?
Who's birthday is it today?
Today, Nolto's Crazy came out?
Why?
I can't believe I'm writing.
It's not hard.
Oh, really?
Yoonjin Ah's part?
Where?
"Renewed the neuronal system
Broke out of the prison in my head"
Oh, here it is.
I ate meat today. But I
suddenly want to eat cherries.
I suddenly want to eat cherries.
I wanted to eat cherries.
I ordered cherries just now.
Is this a secret live broadcast?
Secret live broadcast? No, I
don't do it secretly. Be confident.
You said you were going
to sleep. I ordered cherries.
No, I'm going to play with Fearnot,
eat some cherries, and go to bed.
Ferrari girl
What? Who is this?
Why am I Ferrari girl?
You don't cry and you talk well.
Cafe
Ferrari girl
I can't buy a Ferrari, everyone.
I'm watching 초순지야 꼿티요 right now.
It's a little behind the scenes.
I'm watching it.
I know it's a lot.
That's right. That's a lot.
I know.
I didn't see the
Culinary Class Wars.
Culinary Class Wars
I don't know. They
say it's so much fun.
All the members around
me say it's so much fun.
They're all talking about it.
They're copying it.
And if I say I
haven't seen it yet,
You're still happy.
That's what they're saying.
I thought it was a
cooking and judging show.
I haven't seen it yet.
I'm not interested in it yet.
I've seen The Queen of Tears.
Eunchae sings: Touch.
So cute.
The comments are so cute.
Eunchae sings: Touch.
Eunchae, please teach me
how to speak English well.
I don't know.
Please.
Me, too.
Sing me a celebrity.
But when I was on
a celebrity stage,
I wrote the lyrics and sang it.
Something like this.
I sang it in the lyrics.
So...
But originally, I
didn't know the song.
The original lyrics.
I don't remember.
So...
That's what it was.
Smart.
Hong Eunchae
Do you like General Hong Yi?
It was my nickname when
I was in elementary school.
What is your nickname?
I sang it two times in one part.
Why didn't you make me sing
when you just sang a part again?
I borrowed it.
Hong Hee-jung, Hong-sam,
Hong-gil-dong, something like that.
You know, right?
Speak Chinese, please.
Thank you. I love you.
See you in China.
Please come to Jeola
Yume de kiss me.
Yume de kiss me
Is this right?
Your lover...??
Yume de kiss me
Is this right?
Na na na kiss me.
Watashi tu ru
Oso jo shi
Actually, I don't
know the lyrics.
Na na na
Please, please.
Yume de kiss me
I want you to wish me a
happy birthday in Japanese.
Happy birthday!
Nemo Nemo, Nemo Nemo sign.
Nemo Nemo, Nemo Nemo.
Bonchae Manchae
It's not a content if I sing.
Where the heck is Saki?
You're not ready to sleep soon?
Not yet.
It's not that bad yet.
I'm turning lights
on in my room.
What's your favorite
nickname these days?
I'm Hoonchae.
Hoonchae. Hoonchae
Hong Hoonchae.
Hoonchae.
Who made that?
I think it's well
made. Did you like it?
Hoon High School?
Do you call it Hoon High School?
Oh, it's not Daehari.
No, I'm sorry.
Daehari isn't my nickname.
Hoonni like Eunchae?
No.
It's Hoon Hoon Ha Eunchae.
Isn't it?
It's Hoon Hoon High School because
it's Hoon Hoon High School, right?
Hoonie Eunchae?
Are you making fun of me?
Hoon High School
student Eunchae.
to the training center?
What are you talking about?
Don't say anything.
It's Hoona~.
It's not Hoon Hoon High School?
Do you have a hobby these days?
Is it Hoon Hoon?
Oh, really?
Is it not Hoon Hoon-han?
I'm not sure.
Do you have a hobby these days?
Did you do anything?
치미는.
시몬.
I miss you, Eunchae.
I miss you, too.
How can you remember that there
are three nail clubs in your nickname?
Favorite manhwa? I
don't watch manhwa often.
Ah, Wait a minute. Say
something to the unnies
who bought white hoodies
because of Eunchae.
What is this? Really.
What is this? What is it?
What should I do?
At that time, that white hoodie unnie was
really awesome. I could only see that unni.
It's really funny.
Did you really buy
a white hoodie?
Oh, really.
It's not a plotting.
Are you crazy? Are you crazy?
Why? Why? What?
To be exact, it's not white.
Why did you buy a
bright gray hoodie?
It's not white.
The bright gray one.
You know what ash is, right?
자세이 높았네.
(?) The posture was high.
I didn't look closely, but
that girl was sitting in a row.
It's not a plotting,
it's really...
Everyone, I'll
explain what it is.
Don't say anything
and listen. I'll explain.
Do you want me to say
something? I'll explain.
It's been a long time
since we had a university
event, and there were
schools that went far away.
We're on stage,
but we've gained a lot
of good energy and a lot of good things.
We prepared our autographed
albums for each school.
I wanted to pick someone
who enjoyed it so much and
give them a gift, so I prepared
an autographed album.
So now, it's time to pick the person
to give the autographed album.
So, at that time,
the signed album,
Whoever shows the most love
But I'm not lying.
I'm going to start the anti fans
There was a person who caught my eye from
the moment I took the first pose.
But now that there are so many
people, it was really hard for us to
pick two or three people
for this autographed album.
So it's really hard to choose.
Oh, I'm really...
From the moment I came on
stage, they were so eye-catching.
I took a hard-core picture.
Because the people
were so cute in front of me.
What should I do when there are
so many people around me?
And when I say a word that suits
this song, I have nothing against it.
I'm sorry.
Are you jealous?
Hey,
don't be jealous.
Oh, I'm going crazy.
And it's a college festival, so if you're
a college student, you're older than me.
And the fact that I'm in
the first row means that
I'm the unnie of
my student at the school.
And I have a lot
of affection for you.
Guys, let's talk
about something else.
I wanted to treat you gently
rather than affectionately.
Also,
It's a fun atmosphere and
we're all of the same age.
I wanted to treat you gently.
Wemo Check!
???
Are you joining the (공육주) public
offering club? Public offering club?
Public offering club? Public offering
club... Don't you have any friends?
Turn it off?
Turn it off? That's it.
It's an October's birthday.
It's October 27th.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Miri.
Are you listening?
It's still October.
Although it's the 5th.
There are a lot of
birthdays when it's cold.
Congratulations, everyone.
Do you have a
challenge you want to do?
A challenge you want to do?
I want to do a touch.
I want to do a touch challenge.
What are the
challenges these days?
But not the dance
challenges of other groups.
What's the challenge that's
really popular these days?
Nemo, Nemo, Nemo, Nemo.
Is my mom good at this?
Good night
Entertainer?
What did you say?
What is Umbrini?
Back in the day challenge?
A lot of people asked me to do that.
Emergency ara ara
It's going to be cut off?
I wasn't talking yet.
The weather is really nice.
The weather is nice.
What movie do you recommend?
For me, Inside Out and...
It's not serious at all.
It's a cute and fun movie.
There's a movie called Yes Day.
Was it when I was
in elementary school?
It's a movie that my teacher showed me
in class when I was in elementary school.
My family went...
Once a year?
So we decided on Yes Day.
So on that day, we
can always say yes.
We can only say yes.
On that day.
So...
So once a year, once a day,
There are things I
really wanted to do.
can't even imagine.
Buying ice cream for each taste.
Eating ice cream for each taste.
It's a day like that.
Because I can only say yes.
I have to follow everything.
Anyway, there's a
lot of movies like that.
So it's just cute.
It's not really serious.
Just...
What should I say?
Just once.
When I'm bored?
It's quiet
It looks fun. When
I close my eyes?
I can sleep in peace.
Do you like croissant?
Yes, I like it.
Vacation story?
I think Fearnot already
knows about my vacation.
On Friday, I did the
last time with Weverse.
Most of all, I went
to the baseball field.
The article was so good
I was surprised.
I'm just like...
But still, the same,
the same as other
I got the ticket,
I didn't think I'd be able to get a lot of
sightings while I was
on my way to the concert.
But I didn't know there would
be so many articles about me.
I was so embarrassed.
I'm really bad at self-makeup.
But I won the day.
But the weather was really
nice and it was so much fun.
And I just went to the beach with
my mom and brother to get some air.
With my mom and my brother...
So I went to the
beach to get some air.
And I did it with my brother.
I did a lot of things, but my
brother was really bad at it.
So I won everything.
And I filmed it in
time-lapse mode.
I filmed it in fast-forward
mode, and it's so funny.
It's so funny.
And what else?
I just met a lot of
family members.
Other than my mom, dad, and my brother,
I've met a lot of relatives this time.
There are family members that
I see often,
but there are also people that I
haven't seen in years.
It's really been a year.
And you're the first
person I've seen on TV.
I think I've met a lot
of family members.
The moon photo was
at the beach in Sokcho.
On the way home from Sokcho, I
took a really cool picture of the moon.
I also played bowling.
Me, Eunchae, Eunchae's brother, 1st
cousin, 2nd cousin, and I played bowling.
Was it fun?
Screen baseball. I
played screen baseball.
It was fun. Screen baseball.
Do you have a favorite
baseball cheering song?
I sang along to all of them.
But I forgot to go.
I forgot.
Favorite? I just
like all of them.
You know all of them.
Fearnot, how do you know?
It's been a long time
since I exercised.
I exercised before the vacation.
I exercised after the vacation.
I exercised because
I didn't do anything.
I exercised a lot
when I was a trainee.
It's really hard to start over,
But I want you to try it.
I want to go to the beach again.
I want to go again.
I want to go to the
baseball field again.
It's a shame, but I really
have to go next year.
Really, on that day,
It was so awesome.
It was a fun game.
The weather was good, it was
interesting, and it was a fun game.
The seaweed soup
was really good, too.
Did you take a selfie
at the baseball field?
I posted it on Instagram.
Wow, 30 minutes have passed.
Wow.
It was Friday yesterday.
But it's been so long
since I've done another
schedule for the first time on Friday.
I'm a little...
I had no choice but to...
I felt a little bit sad.
I think it was the
same for Fearnot.
I just came to play today.
Did you have fun?
The rider said he
started delivering.
Oh, the Japanese
I've learned recently.
I always forget and always...
Fans asked me so much about
the Japanese I've learned recently.
I...
Now I'm trying to memorize
the Japanese that I've
learned recently while
talking with my unnies.
I try to memorize it and
when I ask again later,
I say I should answer
like this at that time.
Oh, but I really forgot again.
I learned... Oh,
there was something.
Do you know what is the
Japanese word for water crab?
Guys?
Water crab. It was a water crab.
What is a water crab?
That... Oh, really. What was it?
I always remember this
when it's really dark.
I remember, I
remember, I remember.
I do this, but...
Wa... wata ame?
Wata
It's not a water crab.
Mijino?
Water dog?
No, it's not.
Ajarashi.
I think it was ajarashi.
That's right.
Thank you.
Anyway, I think it was ajarashi.
What's your favorite
snack these days?
I really like fried rice cakes
and nurungji these days.
Nurungji.
I like nurungji and
fried rice cakes.
Fried rice cakes.
Yesterday, my manager bought
me a really delicious fried rice cake.
It was really delicious.
That's what me and the other
manager and two people...
The long bag...
You usually sell
that long bag like this.
I ate it all.
I ate it all on the spot.
It's not a human
fried rice cake.
It's really...
It melts in your mouth.
It melts when you
put it in your mouth.
It's really thin.
It's really sweet and savory.
It was really delicious.
Anyway, that's it, everyone.
Are you doing well?
Isn't it almost 12 o'clock?
It's almost 12 o'clock.
You should sleep.
Eunchae, I'm going to bed.
Yeah.
All right.
What are you doing?
Of course, I'm going to eat
cherries before I go to bed.
I'm going to eat cherries before I go to
bed, but you guys should go to bed early.
All right?
Did you have fun today?
I guess the
cherries are all here.
That's right.
We're almost there.
Bye.
Did you have fun today?
Good night.
Have a good dream.
Bye bye.
I'll be back.
Bye.
Bye, Chu.