Hi.
Wait a minute. I was looking at the filter.
It's already in.
Is this better?
Hi.
I just got off in Korea.
I'm waiting for my suitcase.
So...
I came to play for a moment, everyone.
I went to Japan.
It's not an airport, it's my room.
Before I go to bed,
I was lying on my bed.
I only did voice live.
At that time, Fiona always asked me to show my face.
Today...
It's not before I go to bed yet.
My face is ready, so I turned it on.
It got pretty cold in Korea.
To say that...
I've only been in Japan for a day.
Because there's no AC.
How did you feel when you stopped?
On the second week,
I saw Scorpion.
I saw it too.
So nice.
It's my first time watching the best baseball game.
It was so much fun.
Almost all of them are watching the best baseball game.
When I watched the best baseball game alone, my heart was beating so fast.
I watched the best baseball game alone like this.
I watched the best baseball game and got off the plane.
Did you really succeed in ticketing?
When was the last time you learned Japanese?
Today...
I can remember.
When?
My hair is short.
My eyes look tired?
Why?
I can remember.
Today...
I can remember today.
Where is it?
This is my room.
Welcome to my room.
This is my bed.
Do you want to see it?
Ta-da.
Do you know this?
It's not the lion doll that was in our first documentary.
It's a lion doll with a hood.
It popped out of here.
I pulled it like this and my eyebrows split.
I still have my eyes on it and I still wear it a lot
Is there anything you wonder about?
My room?
I don't have much in my room.
Bed
The standby I got from the Reuniverse.
TV TV TV
Cosmetic table
I'm sorry to introduce the room.
I'm not ready yet.
Show me anything.
There's a computer right next to the bed.
When I lived in Overwatch,
I didn't want to live without this computer.
I don't play games now.
Did you cut your hair today?
I untied it.
Please say it in Japanese.
Kyou
Kyou mo
I really want to thank you for
adding a keyboard to work today.
It's the best.
Very sweet.
I cut my bangs a little bit today.
It's a little long.
Perfect!
Are you good at Japanese?
I'm good at Japanese?
Apartment, Apartment!
It's a perfect night.
Thank you! Perfect night!
Perfect night!
Let's have fun!
"I have an English exam tomorrow, when is it?"
Fighting
I have an exam tomorrow
Make me super crazy
Do a capture time
Capture time?
Okay, since I turned on the camera, let's capture time
How should I do it? Capture time
Please read the comments after the wink.
I think my wink skills have decreased.
Why do my eyes look so closed?
I can do it, but I can't do it pretty.
V
Polaroid
Hurry up.
Capture time.
End.
I just came to say good night.
I'll be ready someday.
Thank you.
I love you.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
Bye, everyone.
Good night.