I think we should wait a minute.
Oh, it's up it's up.
♪ Korean HBD Song ♪
woo.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
It's our first time celebrating
a birthday together.
That's right!
I didn't get sick.
Finally.
Seriously...
It's unbelievable that it's our first
time celebrating a birthday together.
It's so nice to have everyone here.
It's the first time since debut.
I feel so so good.
The first time,
we were missing Eunchae.
- That's right.
- But back then, Eunchae was busy.
That's right.
Today was good timing.
The timing wasn't good before, but today
we are healthy.
Put it on your nose!
I'm going crazy.
How is this happening?
Just throw that away.
Wow, it's done!
Queen of positivity.
Why did you do that?
Is it good?
Yeah, it's like whipped cream.
Yeah, I think it's whipped cream.
It tastes like my hands.
It's really pretty because
it's my handwriting.
It's really pretty.
Yeah... Cute!
I'm glad I took a picture earlier.
Ah, I was going to show Fearnot.
Be careful.
This is...
It's so pretty.
I can't see it.
I'll show you a picture later.
- It's so pretty.
- Yunjin drew it.
That's right.
That's right. My hand painting is in it.
- It's so pretty.
- Thank you.
- Shall we do it?
- Yes.
- Firstly...
- What do you wanna do?
What should I do?
Please choose.
- It's really pretty.
- I think this is the color.
"It's so pretty,
but the jellyfish light also looks good."
That's right.
There's a jellyfish light,
and its friends are here.
What...
The sound...
Oh it died out.
It's lit.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear
Yunjin. Happy birthday to you.
Make a wish!
Retry!
I don't know.
- It's the first try.
- Let's do it on purpose.
Shall we do it now?
Let's do it for real.
I'll erase this.
It's my first time doing this,
Thank you. Ok! Ready, set,
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Yunjin.
What happened?
Can you show us your outfit again?
Happy birthday.
It's today's outfit, Happy birthday.
"Happy Birthday."
- It's my birthday.
- That's fitting!
It's my birthday.
It's your birthday!
It's just for today.
Huh? Huh? Eh?
What happened?
It's like a magic trick.
(Her straw disappeared)
It's fine.
Don't you care?
That's so funny.
Black magic.
Like magic.
Oh, thank you.
It's a special day.
- Yes, it's great.
- Yes.
Yes yes yes.
It's so nice.
What do we do now?
Oh, uh...
How did you spend your day today?
Did you eat seaweed soup?
I didn't eat seaweed soup, no.
Who will cook it for you?
Who will cook it?
I didn't eat seaweed soup,
but I had a delicious Pad Thai.
Pad Thai?
Yes, I had Pad Thai.
The managers got it for me.
Saero?
That's right.
Delicious.
I drank coffee.
I had a good meal, and I feel great.
You need to get a very fun photo.
The members sent some photos,
and they are so funny.
There's only funny pictures.
It's really pretty.
But they said it was okay.
So, you can post it.
I don't have a choice.
Because it's so funny.
Kiss?
Mwah.
Yunjin-ah.
Give us a ribbon heart.
Was it like this?
Oh, ribbon heart.
This is it.
You didn't get presents yet, right?
I gifted already.
Oh, you did?
Thank you.
And Yunjin gave us letters.
Ah, right.
She gave us letters one-by-one.
While we were by our self.
I can't believe there's someone like this.
Oh, me? Yeah!
Thank you.
It's your birthday.
She suddenly gave us letters.
Ah, but Chaewon was funny too.
"But wait, let me give this to you."
I liked it.
When I went to London,
I went to an art exhibition
with my favorite works...
what was it?
There were postcards or something
so, I bought it.
It was a planned letter.
Yes, it was a planned letter.
I should have written a letter then
[crosstalk]
We'd never do that.
Right.
It's N, NF
(INFJ)
NF
And there's J.
I'll give it to you.
Right and
the cover.
Ah, right, right.
It released today.
Right, it did.
[crosstalk]
(behind-the-scenes was old)
You can tell by the different hair color.
I think it was in June.
Right, right.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
But.
When was it?
This year.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, yes.
Chaewon knows.
What is it?
Yes, yes, yes.
Finally, it's out.
It's really good.
Yes,
yes, yes.
This turtle is cute.
I'll take the turtle.
It's so cute.
What's that?
What is this?
- This?
- Isn't this a crocodile?
Isn't this a crocodile?
악어.
It's a crocodile
It's so cute.
No, they're so cute, too.
What do you call this?
Eunchae
I don't know how
to say it in Korean.
えい, えい, えい
I was a kid at the aquarium.
えい
This is a "stingray".
I don't know how
to say it in Korean.
This is えい.
This is a whale. (고래)
This is whale. (고래)
What's this one?
Conch?
It's a conch.
Gaori (stingray)
Ah, 가오리.
It's a stingray.
This is a... hang on-
It has a wide forehead.
귀상어
Hammerhead.
It's a shark. How does it see?
There are jellyfish in the back.
Oh, yeah.
We haven't really talked
about your birthday.
There are so many things to explain.
Oh, right.
- We have to make a wish.
- Then
- We will pick one.
Nice
I like that.
The ring too.
It's cute.
Then...
I'll pick one.
Please pick.
Please pick one.
No,
- What?
- Start.
I got a flower hat.
I'm looking forward to it.
Party...
Is it okay?
Totally.
Stickers?
Here's a sticker.
I got a party whistler.
Party whistler.
I'm sunglasses
[crosstalk]
Pppppppp.
Oh, that surprised me.
Eunchae, don't you think it's
a little disappointing?
Me?
Yeah,
ppppppppppppp.
Oh, it matches your outfit.
Is that so?
Pppppppppppppppppp.
It's a perfect fit.
But this... this...
Eunchae,
I think this would be nice too.
It's up to you.
Pp pp pppppppp.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, everyone.
Perfect.
Eunchae, that looks like it's your hair.
It's really looks like hair.
- I should do that hair.
- You have to do that hair smiling.
Cute! Pretty!
She's Rudolph.
Oh, it's so cute.
Why is it so huge on you?
It's so cute. I like it.
It's really cute.
Okay, let's capture time naturally.
Oh, it's working.
The cake
pp
pppppp.
Why won't it work?
Good. Nice. Good.
Let's taste the cake.
- Why don't we try the cake?
- I want to try it.
I want to taste.
I think you have to cover your eyes.
Wanna wear a blindfold?
Oh, should I?
Okay.
Could you give me a bite?
Please give me a good bite.
Right.
Culinary Class Wars, the crazy chef.
It was so nice until the end.
Really?
I was watching with Zuha earlier.
There was a new dish.
Oh, it came out already.
Did it come out today?
I only saw it yesterday.
So the winner is...
Hurry up, before it's spoiled.
Sniff it.
What is this?
Smell it?
But I didn't look up to here.
I didn't look too long
I don't know.
Ahh.
Oh.
Hmm?
- Mmm.
- Is this how you do it?
I haven't seen that yet.
But it's really good.
What does it taste like?
First of all, the whipped cream.
How so?
- It's very light
- Light?
It's light.
- Yes yes
- Wow, that's awesome.
It's very light, the bread is moist,
the whipped cream is delicious.
- This is chocolate chip.
- It's chocolate chip.
Chocolate chip?
It's a chocolate chip.
Wow.
I really like chocolate.
There's a lot of chocolate chips.
I like the texture.
Yes, it's kind of...
I think it's like in a frappe, delicious,
The cake is delicious, yes,
Oh, the jellyfish cake,
when I thought of it, this.
About the the cake,
The fresh cream is important.
The fresh cream is very tight.
No, no, I can't say right now.
Jellyfish cake.
She said it very clearly and tightly.
Oh, that? What is it?
Jellyfish cake.
Top cake!
Thank you. I'm really enjoying this.
Seriously.
Isn't that show so fun?
Chef Jung Ji-Sun,
I'm a huge fan.
Chef Jung Ji-Sun nim.
Ah, don't spoil anything!
Thank you Park...
I want to eat that dim sum.
Dim Sum, Tiramisu, Mala Jjampong.
Macreme.
Don't spoil it.
- It's just a dish.
- It's fun. Right.
Please watch it.
I want to eat it.
It's based on when Yunjin watches.
I can't watch till the end.
I think we can watch it until the end.
Originally, I couldn't watch
shows till the end but when Yunjin,
is watching, it's
more interesting.
It's my first time
finishing a series.
Tiramisu is coming out.
I'll want it. Where?
We will do a Weverse live eating it.
Where?
I think it's sold by
the convenience store.
The convenience store.
You can buy it at the
convenience store.
I want to eat jjamppong today.
Napoli Mafia
I want jjampong now.
- The Nappoli Mafia.
- Who is the most famous chef.
Who was the most impressive chef?
The goddess of China.
She was the mentor of the two.
The teacher.
Yes, I thought their relationship
was so heartwarming.
I agree.
I have no idea what's going on.
Let's move on.
So, there's something
we have to do today.
Of course.
This one?
TMI Quiz?
How many questions do we have?
I'm out of my mind!
You have to raise your hand quickly.
With your name.
Today...
What time did I wake up today?
It was a little late today.
Right? It was late. But-
Chaewon.
9:00 am?
The closest person gets it.
Okay, okay.
I'll give no reactions.
Eunchae!
3:00 pm.
That's way too late.
Kkura!
No, no, you already said it.
It's so funny.
12:00 pm.
Zuha!
7:00 am.
What?
6:00 am.
Eunchae, Eunchae, Eunchae
[crosstalk]
The closest person is...
It's me, it's me!
Please, be me.
You must have slept for quite a long time.
I slept for a seriously long time today.
Good job.
I usually go to bed late
I always sleep really late these days.
Well done.
Good job.
Today...
I was going to wake up early and have a...
miracle morning.
Miracle morning?
Yes,
I was going to have a very busy morning
I knew it.
I was going to go to a cafe,
take a walk, and see an exhibition,
but then I just wanted to sleep.
I slept late.
- I should sleep.
- That's right.
Eunchae, 1 point.
You almost spent your birthday asleep.
I know, half of it
yea, yea.
Yeah, I like it a lot.
Next TMI.
What do I want to do right now?
Now?
Ah, today. Today?
Just recently?
Eunchae.
Go to a hot pot restaurant.
Okay, next.
I'm not sure what to say.
This is the last one?
The last one.
Zuha.
Go to eat with the members.
Isn't it too similar?
No, no, no, no,
but where are you going?
- Going together.
- But it's similar
- Even if it's not.
- Let's go eat with the members.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Wait a minute.
Go to eat meat
eating...?
Drawing.
You don't have it.
Why, why, why, why?
I think it's going to be real?
Drawing.
If you don't have it,
you don't have it.
No, no, no.
Zuha got it. That's right.
It's not hot pot. It's not meat.
Tell me.
Okay, okay, okay, whatever.
- I'm hungry
- One point
- What was it?
Fearnot is chewing?
Chewing?
All of a sudden?
That's right too.
What was it?
Can Fearnot ask a question?
Is there anything Fearnot is curious of?
What is there?
TMI is really hard
Um Let's try one more.
Let's try one more
One more.
Ah,
The birthday present I wanted?
Eunchae.
Not that one.
Kkura.
Just a letter.
Ah, okay.
Ah, Eunchae, that...
Even-if-it's-wrong, hand wash.
Oh, okay.
Ah, the one we talked about earlier?
- Ah,
- I don't know.
I've won.
- I think I can do it
- What else is there?
Meat.
You can only say meat.
Chaewon mentioned she
was hungry at the start.
Please understand.
What's so funny?
So funny.
Drawing.
I draw.
Me?
I drew it.
As a real sister.
I draw.
What?
Do you really want me to do it?
Good good.
What are you talking about?
It's so funny I like everything.
I like everything,
but I always get a letter. 저는 다 너무 좋지만.
Isn't that right?
One point.
Then, what should I do?
Then what should I do?
The last one.
The last one will Fearnot's.
No, do you really want that?
Body wash?
Hand cream? Hand wash?
- Body lotion.
- I love it body lotion.
I love it.
- Why?
- My body lotion.
Mm, what is that?
Oh, that? That... What is it?
What color hair do you want to try?
Eunchae.
Green.
Zuha! Pink.
Silver.
Chaewon
Brown.
For me... Wait!
- Hang on.
- No, no, no.
But green is...
It was the green that came
out when you lost your blue.
Yes, yes, yes
Eunchae!
Huh? Really?
I spoke to the hairdresser
a few days ago.
Right, right, right.
- So I was convinced.
- EUNCHAE was confident.
That's right
It's really unique.
When I fell in love
with the color white.
I fell in love with the
color green.
Oh, that.
Thank you.
Good good
Eunchae: No.1.
Do you know what it is?
Dibidibi-dip.
Then, this is just.
- You can choose randomly.
- Okay
- Great.
Okay, good.
Why?
- So cute
- Why?
- My favorite.
- Mine's the cutest.
Isn't it a dress?
- I like Jennifer
- This is my favorite.
Homemade.
This is pretty.
It's pretty when you laugh.
- It's really pretty.
- You are really pretty here.
It's the bangs.
It's bangs.
What's the name?
It's pretty.
- It's so cute.
- What do you have?
I like it now.
It's so pretty.
It's so cute.
It's like a Pokemon.
It's pretty.
Fearnot must be jealous.
I'm jealous of you.
- I envy Fearnot
- I envy you.
Can you show it closer?
This is really cute.
It's little.
It's so funny.
It's cute.
It was cute.
Thank you.
It's already been a year.
That's right.
It was so sad.
But with Fearnot.
It's so nice to be
able to do it live.
It's pretty.
It's so nice to be
able to do it together.
It's so nice.
I'll choose one,
and give a really
good message to you.
I'll give it to you as a gift.
- It's random, right?
- Do I have to do it too?
We'll give it to you.
It's not easy.
It's not easy?
You have to go first.
It's me.
I'll do it first.
Let me be the first.
I don't think I can do it.
Is it just one sentence?
Yes, in one sentence.
You're playing for the first time?
Do you say it with the words?
- Including our words
- Can I do it?
Can I do it?
"From the moment I first saw you."
I think I should've gone first.
Please enjoy this.
Next! Next! It's your turn.
"From the moment I first saw you."
"She was a princess."
Ah, it's over...
Prin...
"You were like a princess."
- Okay
- I can't go either.
No, you can do it like
this and then at the end.
That's right,
the word should be somewhere.
- You were a princess
- Like a princess.
You were a princess.
Like a princess...
I'll do it then.
- You're done
- What is it?
- Show us Zuha.
- Tell us.
"As if she were a princess, I will
love Yunjin for the rest of my life."
[Sakura giving suggestions]
Zuha, Zuha, let her go.
"From the moment I first saw her, I told
her that I would love her like a princess."
"You said you would love me
forever like a princess,
so today I made you Kimchi Jjigae." (?)
Please eat.
It's Kimchi Jjigae.
How do you use this?
But... This is my style.
You have to put it like this.
Is it supposed to be like this?
- It's hard.
- I think it's too much
- I want to talk about it.
It's so colorful.
I want to talk about it.
Last time it was really...
It was perfect.
It's been a long time
since I've seen you.
It was fun. It was good.
Thank you so much.
It was good.
Thank you so much
I decided to love you forever.
Tofu Kimchi Jjigae.
It's TMI It's PS PS.
It was good.
It was so good.
I can't even imagine.
Let's check the comments.
"This is live, right?"
Yes, It's live,
It's not prerecorded.
This is Weverse Live.
Is this right live?
Yes.
It's not Sanhok.
Let's give a round of applause
Why?
It's a good day.
Thank you.
Okay.
Let's do these.
It must be really good. Oh.
From today...
with the love I received...
"I will try to become a member
who is proud to grow every day."
Oh, it's so perfect.
It's not from today,
but it's already like that.
Already perfect.
Thank you.
From birth!
From the time I was born.
How old are you?
I'm 23 years old now.
Then from 23 years ago.
That's right.
When were you born?
Me?
- If I reveal it, it's a little...
- Oh, really?
Send me a message via Kakao Talk.
I'll send you a
message via Kakao Talk.
Do you know what it is?
Dangerous period.
Oh, Busan-like.
I'm sorry.
I've been to Busan.
Busan-like?
It's hectic!
It's like this.
Ppppppppp.
"Yunjin is so cute."
"Hug all together."
Hug me.
Let's hug.
It's quiet.
It's so funny.
"Did you make the
jellyfish light yourself?"
Yes.
Yes, I made it myself.
Wow, you did a great job.
This balloon never fell.
Isn't that great?
The world is helping.
I think it's going to fall.
I worked really hard.
Actually, I made up a lie.
But,
there are so much jellyfish in the world.
Yeah, but there are a lot.
They're all cute.
Should I like it too?
Yeah, I like it a lot.
I like it too. Shouldn't I like it?
Should we like it together?
"Let's love together."
I love you.
Is there Fearnot whose birthday is today?
Happy birthday!
There are a lot of
birthdays in October.
Congratulations!
Rachel's birthday
is also in October.
Really?
Now?
"The cover was so good."
Thank you.
Is there a reason why
you chose that song?
I...
wanted to try a genre
called Bossa Nova.
The lyrics are so good
and the song is so good.
I got to be close with Laufey.
I thought it would be nice to
cover the song of that friend's sister.
- I'll look at the lyrics.
- It's so pretty.
The mood itself is so pretty.
And she also majored
in classical music.
Really?
Yes, classical.
She's a classical
vocalist and a cello player.
She's so talented.
She's very talented.
I love it.
"Who was first to
celebrate your birthday?"
Zuha!
That's right.
At first, Zuha sent it to me
first and at the same time,
everything went in a flurry.
As soon as I saw 12 o'clock,
it was a flurry.
What time did you wake up?
Yesterday?
At about 5 o'clock?
4 o'clock
I didn't sleep much, did I?
I just slept well
I slept very well.
"Do you like bossam?"
Does Bossa mean bossam?
Yes, Bossa means bossam.
Bossam Nova, yes, yes.
You like Bossa, right?
Bossam, Bossam Nova.
"Crazier is a really good song."
Thank you.
No, that was on our
recording behind-the-scenes.
That was so funny.
The forehead.
It was definitely the forehead.
I gave up on that.
I really gave up on that.
I gave up as I directed.
It was so funny.
It was really fun.
It was cute.
Was that summer?
It was summer.
When was it?
It wasn't summer.
Because we were practicing.
The hair.
Did you grow it?
Yes.
Cute.
She kept saying.
It was cute.
I think this is really cute.
It's so neat.
I think we can capture it.
It's so cute.
What is this?
It's here.
That's right.
It's the mouth.
It's cute.
"Eunchae marry me."
Sorry.
Not yet.
It's cute.
"What is your favorite
word in English?"
Happy birthday.
In short, it's HBD.
HBD.
It's text.
Happy birthday.
생.축.
Saeng Chuk.
Thank you.
Many people want
to congratulate you.
That's right.
Thank you.
But your birthday isn't over yet.
It's not over.
You can press it.
Okay.
Right, I thought it was a month.
I will start from the 10th.
I'm a month.
Okay.
We can do it.
Oh, I know.
I'll leave it.
Okay.
Congratulations.
The last word.
I love you.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye.
[Please Consider Subscribing]